I want to try and gather
the unrestrained winds
I’ll run toward the horizon,
alongside the wave crests
I’ve made my decision,
even if there’s a long way to go
on that road.
I’ll continue towards the future I’ve planned
Time rushes us
The heartbeat speeds up
When I woke in the middle of a dream
I kept searching for that same light
Under the shining star-lit sky with
countless constellations and shadows
There was something beyond that…
What were you gazing at?
I guess the storm is
going to come soon…
Let’s hurry and head back
to the curry shop.
Oh my.
That thunder right now…
came from the direction
of the Katabami Gold Mine…
Raiga's Counterattack
B-Boss.
R-Ranmaru!
Hey, wake up, Ranmaru!
Quit joking around.
I’m not laughing…
Hey…Ranmaru…!
You… What did you do
to Ranmaru?
N-No! He…
When Ranmaru held your hand…
you revived and…
And then…Ranmaru…
Ranmaru…
Why is Raiga up?!
I must stop him.
Thunder?
Could it be?!
You’re slow!
Are you…that brat’s comrade…?
If it’s a wooden weapon, then…
But I can’t hold it over my head…
You’re annoying!
You little fly…!
Quit buzzing!
I’m…not smart, you know…
Huh…?
I don’t know why this happened…
Hey, whose fault is it? Yours?!
N-No! That’s not true!
Perhaps…the guys from the Leaf…
Oh yeah…
lf they didn’t come,
then Ranmaru and I would
have been together forever…
Where are they?!
You know, don’t you?!
lf you don’t know, I’ll kill you!
I know…
Maybe…!
Take me…where they are…
Go!
Yes!
Hold on, Ranmaru.
For your funeral…
I’ll offer up their corpses for you.
Ranmaru…
This child… Did he give up his life
in order to revive Raiga?
Rai…ga… Rai…
Ranmaru! You're alive!
Hang in there! Ranmaru!
Ranmaru!
It started raining.
But we’re almost done.
Oh my, I’m happy that
you all did this much for me.
Oh no!
Mom! Something horrible happened!
Oh my… What happened, Karashi?
Tenten is…!
What happened to Tenten?
She…fell from a cliff and..
What?!
What do you mean?!
I was running with her and
Tenten said that she would train me
in place of Lee…
But there…when we were
approaching the Lightning Pass,
the lightning struck and
a tree came falling and
Tenten fell from the Pass
to the bottom of the cliff!
Oh my! Then you must go
help her out immediately!
Let’s go to help, Tenten!
Yeah!
Umm… No, I will…
I will come after you guys
with the first-aid kit.
Okay.
Let’s go, Naruto, Lee.
– Yes! 					– Right!
Oh my, Karashi?
Mom, we’re running away
from here.
What are you saying, child?!
Never mind that!
I’ll explain it later,
so hurry up and get ready.
I will wait at the Lightning Pass.
Bring them for sure. If not…
I’ll offer up you and your mom’s corpses
to Ranmaru…
Mom, please!
I don’t want to!
I'm going to wait
until everybody comes back!
Mom! You are so stubborn!
Just come with me!
Do you think that Tenten would
fall off a cliff
merely because of the thunder?
Huh? What do you mean?
That Karashi…
lt seems like he wasn’t trained enough.
I’m sorry…
Then…
Perhaps…it’s some kind
of trap again.
Or he’s been threatened
by someone…
But the Kurosuki Family is…!
Maybe my eyes were cloudy…
No way!
It’s him…
He’s burning up with fever…
Raiga…?
He revived, so you should too…
It’s all right. I’m going to die
soon anyway.
No way! I’m not going to let you say
that you're going to die so easily!
The people who were killed by you
and Raiga died against their will!
I’m not going to let it go your way!
For the sake of those
whose freedoms you took away.
I’m going to have you
take responsibility!
Are you okay?
The storm… It’ll be dangerous
to stay here…
To Grandma’s place.
You’ve come!
Raiga!
So he is alive.
This time I’ll take you down for sure!
Let’s go!
That’s not good! Lee!
What are you…?
What is this?
It’s in a whole different level
from before…!
Probably that attack was
lightning made of Chakra.
But this one…
Real lightning is used as the source…
If he can utilize the power of nature,
unlike Chakra, he’ll have no limits!
Get down!
Byakugan!
If we dodge through
the electric shock and
take this to a close-range battle…
Naruto!
I know it!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Good job, Naruto!
Gentle Fist!
Neji!
You brats! Is that all you know?
Unlike the natural thunder power
I’m using,
Chakra has its limits!
Huh…?
You’re an idiot!
There’s an idiot here!
Is that what you say to an opponent
who fought with all his power?!
Huh?
You again…
This time I’m not going to
have a funeral for you!
I am angry.
Oh my, what are you doing?!
Please Mom, come with me!
There’s no time.
No, I’m going to stay here!
Oh Tenten!
Oh my! This stupid son of mine!
I couldn’t help it,
because the boss came back to life…
If we stay here,
we’re going to get killed.
The only choice we have
is to run away!
If you want to run away,
then go.
I’m not running away.
I’m not going to give up,
I will save this child.
I will feed this boy
the curry of life!
Grandma…
It’s the curry that revived Lee.
Yes.
If anything happens,
it’s not my fault!
You!
One, two…
One, two… One, two…
This is bad…
This is really bad!
Eat this…you’ll feel better.
Please.
You messed up on
mixing the spices.
Oh my?!
Karashi, could you have memorized
my recipe of the curry of life?
Karashi…
This is the true curry of life.
Here, please eat this.
You can’t even eat
if you’re not with Raiga?
Why…?
Why…for a person like me?
Does one need a reason
to save someone?
To save you,
Grandma Sansho and Karashi
did their best to make the curry.
Don’t you feel anything seeing
those two trying their best?
If you don’t feel anything,
you’re a horrible human being!
Human beings support each other
in order to live…
If there are people who need help,
don’t others naturally lend them a hand?
Isn’t that being human?
Anyway, one bite is fine.
Why don’t you try it?
Was it good?
That is what it feels like to live.
Raiga …
I want him to eat this curry too.
Let’s go.
I’m far from finished…!
This guy…
What is up with him?
So many things happen
on this endless road, huh?
Although you’re strong-willed,
your voice wavered on the phone today
What dreams did you chase to get here?
Even I have times when
I just don’t understand, baby
When you’re sad, I’ll be close to you
Even on nights when we’re apart,
I’ll be close to you
Damn it! What in the world
happened to my body?!
It is pitch black in front of me,
my entire body is numb,
and my body doesn’t do
what I want it to do.
What is this feeling…?
It’s warm, my entire body
is burning,
and what is this taste that brings energy
up from the bottom of my stomach…?
Next episode: Run! The Curry of Life!