Connecting old words
that have been used up
I just want to convey
my simple thoughts
That day's faint wind blows away
at the castle ruins of yesterday
I'll laugh with you
and live for the moment
Still that incident
will continue to trouble you, right?
That's why it must be good-bye
Leaving nothing behind,
let us share what is left
In time, we'll realize
that it was everything
And sadness will touch our cheeks,
creating a river of tears
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex
and melting away
Sasuke!
Are you going to
run away from me?!
Yo…loser.
A Cry on Deaf Ears
It’s you this time, huh?
I couldn’t do it.
I was not able to stop Sasuke…
I think…
the one who can stop Sasuke…
the one who can save Sasuke is…
Naruto…you are the only one.
Naruto…this is my…
once in a lifetime…favor to ask…
Please… Please bring Sasuke back!
I also told this to Sakura, but…
Don’t mind me anymore.
What's with that face?
Iruka Sensei, why on the earth
does an outstanding person like me
have to be on the same team with him?
Sasuke graduated with
the highest grade out of all students…
Naruto, you are at the bottom!
When you even out
the team’s strength,
then it naturally becomes like this.
Try your best not to slow me down,
you dunce.
I am fine without eating!
I am absolutely fine.
I’m…fine…
Here.
You asked Sakura for a hint the other day,
what did she tell you?
Shall we go?
Yup.
Wh-What’s with that face…?
You loser…
Why…?
You… I hated you, you know.
It’s none of your business!
Who knows,
my body moved on its own.
You rescue Sakura, no matter what!
Sasuke… You…
I could still distract him for a little while…
I lost everything once.
I don’t want to see my precious comrades
die in front of me anymore.
Why…?
Why is it…Sasuke?
Why did you become like this?!
You!
Whatever happens to me,
what does that have to do with you?
I have my own way.
No matter who it is,
nobody has the right
to tell me what to do.
I will tell you the truth.
I’m done fooling around with
you guys of the Leaf.
Go home.
I’ll take care of him!
Choji…
Go everyone!
Go, quickly! I’ll catch up with you.
Neji…
Okay!
Hold on!
Kiba…
Kiba! Akamaru!
Now! Naruto!
Shikamaru…
The strategy…a success!
What are you doing?
Please go quickly!
You also promised Sakura
with a Nice-Guy pose, Naruto.
Bushy Brow…
I’ll defeat this person.
It’s a promise.
Everyone…
Everyone risked their lives
to come after you, you know!
Good job for them.
Lastly, I will tell you
the most important thing.
Sasuke is neither a close friend
of mine nor is he someone I like.
But Sasuke is a Shinobi of
the Village Hidden in the Leaves…
A comrade.
That’s why we will rescue him
by risking our lives.
This is the Leaf way.
How do you take
your comrades of the Leaf ?!
Comrades, you said…
Did I become stronger staying
with those so-called comrades?
I am going to where Orochimaru is.
Orochimaru is the person who killed
the Third Hokage
and tried to crush The Leaf Village!
Do you think he will
give you the power freely?
He just wants your body
as a vessel!
You might not be able to come back.
You might get killed.
You think I’d easily let you
go to such a place?!
That doesn’t matter to me…
If my goal is accomplished,
then that’s all that matters.
If you intend to get in that way…
Then it can’t be helped…
You’re not gonna be able to!
I’ll take you back even by force!
Why are you laughing?!
You were laughing at that time too.
That time…?
What’s funny?
It’s not funny. I am happy.
Thinking about…
how I can finally defeat you here.
That time you wanted to fight me, right?
You were thrilled weren’t you?
At first!
But, you were different.
That was…
Hurry up and come.
But first, put on your Headband.
I’ll wait.
I don’t need such a thing…
Just put it on!
You won’t be able to
put one scratch on my face.
That’s not it!
I’m saying that this is a sign
that we fight as equal Leaf Shinobi.
That is what I call a stuck up!
You think you and I are equal?
Yeah, I think so.
I’ve never thought I was inferior to you.
You’re so obnoxious!
Stop!
That was…
That was not the kind of fight I wanted.
Even now…this is not…
I don’t care about
your circumstances.
What…is this power?
Power is flowing out…
So this is the power that
the guy was talking about.
Furthermore, the power
is growing into my body.
If it is like that now…
if I release this curse mark…
I wonder how much power…
Wh-What power…
He’s not the same as before…
Wake up already!
I awakened long ago…
From my idiotic self who dreams about
a lax peaceful future…
hanging out with comrades.
That’s why I left the village!
That’s why I sought power!
My dream is not in the future.
My dream is in the past…
That’s the only place it exists.
Wow, Brother!
You hit the target right in the middle,
even the one behind the rock!
All right, me too!
Sasuke, let’s go home.
Geez… You said that
you would teach me a new shuriken jutsu.
There is an important mission tomorrow
and I need to prepare for that.
Liar…
Forgive me, Sasuke…
Another time.
Brother, watch me!
Hey! If you push yourself…
Why is the one who twisted
his ankle laughing?
Could it be that you are trying
to take the easy way?
That’s not true...
I’m happy thinking about
how I’m finally going to
the Academy starting tomorrow.
I’m going to do my best
when I enter the Academy.
So even that father will approve of me.
He will count on me
like he does on my brother…
Sasuke… You really are…
I told you…
I don’t need a future
with you guys anymore.
Fire Style: Dragon Flame Jutsu.
For the first time, I spoke to you
And you smiled
For the first time, I was able to speak
In my own words
Would you think it was
a bother if I approached you?
Despite my doubts,
I worked up my courage
My clumsy attempts with words
You listened without turning away
No wonder I get carried away by you
But you don’t feel anything for me, do you?
I feel so sad
But…
For the first time, I spoke to you
And you smiled
For the first time, I was able to speak
In my own words
For the first time, I spoke to you
And you smiled
For the first time, I was able to speak
In my own words
For the first time, I spoke to you
I feel power surging
through my body…
It's as though I can't lose.
It's power I'd never have gained
playing comrade with you guys from Leaf.
But it's not enough.
lt's way short of enough, Naruto!
Strength…hatred…and desire!
Next episode:
"Brothers: Distance Among the Uchiha"