Hey boys, listen up!
Humans aren’t such a big deal
Who needs tomorrow anyway,
so don’t hide your fists
You’re not old enough
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
Hey boys, you’re the only ones
who can pull the trigger in your heart
All the kids said
We’re living in this senseless, ridiculous,
awesome world right at this moment,
All the kids said
Don’t forget every truth or lie
We’re way too young to die
In this empty town lined with empty faces
All the kids took off
into this windless night
Because they want to change something
The Secrets of the Mangekyo Sharingan
No matter what darkness
might lie ahead,
I will rush into it headfirst!
No matter what happens,
I will get my hands
on that power!
It’s getting late…
What was that?
I thought I sensed
someone there just now…
The lights…
It isn’t even close
to bedtime yet…
This is…!
Wh-What is this…?!
What the hell is this?!
Uncle… Aunt…
Father… Mother…
Father? Mother?
There’s somebody in there!
Move!
Father! Mother!
Big Brother!
Father and Mother are…!
Why? For what reason?!
Who the hell would do
something like this…?!
Big Brother…what are…?
What are you doing, Big Brother?!
You pathetic younger brother…
Mangekyo Sharingan!
Stop! Big Brother!
Don’t make me see
this kind of thing!
Why…?!
Big Brother, why did you…?!
Why…
Big Brother… Why did you…?
In order to measure my vessel…
To measure your vessel?
Is that all?
Only for that reason…
you killed everybody…?
That is what is important.
What the hell is that?
You gotta be kidding!
I’m scared…
I’m scared!
Don’t kill me…!
I don’t believe it!
This is too unlike you, Big Brother.
I mean…
The reason I acted as the big brother
you desired was…
because I wanted to
measure your vessel.
You have the potential
to become my opponent
in order for me to measure
my vessel.
You hated me…
and you continued to have
the desire to surpass me.
That’s exactly why
I will allow you to live…
for my own benefit.
You are someone who could be able to use
Mangekyo Sharingan just like me.
However, on one condition…
That you must kill
your closest friend…
Y-You’ve gotta be kidding…
Just like I did…
Regarding Shisui Uchiha
who committed suicide last night
by throwing himself into
the Nakano River…
The other one that did not show up
to the meeting is Shisui…
If I remember correctly…
you adored him like
he was your real older brother…
That was…your doing…?
Big Brother, you…killed Shisui?!
That’s right…and because of
that I obtained these eyes.
The main hall of Nakano Shrine…
Underneath the seventh tatami mat
on the far right
is the secret gathering place
of the Clan.
There you will find recorded
the secret of…
the raison d'être of
the Uchiha Clan’s Visual Jutsu.
The secret of the raison d'être…?
If you attain these eyes,
you will become the third person
including myself
to utilize
the Mangekyo Sharingan.
If that happens…
then there will have been meaning
in my allowing you to live.
However…at present…
You are not worth killing.
My pathetic younger brother…
If you want to kill me,
then begrudge me!
Hate me!
And live in an ugly manner…
Run away…run away…
and cling to life…
And one day, when you have
the same eyes as I do…
come and stand before me!
A dream…?
Yes…that’s right.
The only one who survived…
is that boy.
Didn't he have
an older brother?
Yes, but he’s gone missing…
It can’t be true…
That elite Uchiha Clan…
Hi, Sasuke! What did you
come to buy today?
Sasuke, are you on your way to school?
Yeah.
I saw Itachi earlier,
but he’s very admirable, isn’t he?
He’s already become
a top-class Shinobi.
He graduated from the Ninja Academy
at the top of his class at age seven
and attained the rank
of Chunin at age ten, didn’t he?
He was able to use Sharingan
when he was eight!
That’s true, isn’t it?
That boy is truly the pride
of the Uchiha Clan.
Welcome home…Sasuke!
Sasuke…!
Wait a second…
What is it?
Mother?!
Then why only Big Brother!
Your brother's your brother.
And you are you.
Father cares deeply
about both of you.
The main hall of Nakano Shrine…
Located underneath
the seventh tatami mat on the far right
is our clan’s secret gathering place…
I see… So that’s what it is…
Ninja Academy
Hey, Shikamaru…
Wanna go to the candy shop
after school?
Huh… No way.
You can do that ‘cuz
your mother’s nice,
but if my mother found out that I bought
myself a snack before going home,
I’d be in big trouble.
Did you hear the news…
that entire Uchiha Clan
was apparently murdered?
Yeah, my dad told me.
Apparently he’s the only one
who survived…
That’s my boy.
With me, you’re all
your father talks about…
I wonder…what kind of things
Father was saying to Mother…
If you want to kill me…
Begrudge me! Hate me!
If it’s for the purpose of killing you,
I will rush headfirst into whatever
darkness which may lie ahead!
I will obtain that power no matter what!
From this point onwards,
I am an avenger!
Sasuke is now
in depths of darkness…
If you stop in a place like this…
you won’t be able to catch up
with Sasuke.
Neji, it’s just like you said.
That guy looks like he’s in
the depths of darkness right now…
He really hit me with
his full strength! Damn it!
Don’t you consider me…
your comrade any longer?!
Don’t all those things we did together
in Squad Seven mean anything to you?!
No.
I will get my hands on
that power no matter what.
It wasn’t meaningless…
To me, you became my…
closest friend.
We've become…friends?
Then…why?!
All the more reason why…
there’s meaning in taking
you down.
I don’t fully understand but…
I understood that you want to
fight me with your everything!
Sasuke…!
When I recalled the parts one by one,
I felt as though
I had understood everything
Faded words which I kept so close to me
Speechless nights, a hint of warmth,
and this distant yearning for you
I live, simply repeating this cycle
Held in my two hands
A droplet of time
Softly clutching forgotten memories
Lost words
I’ll keep these thoughts…
Are you trying to take me
down for real?
I don’t know any longer
whether you really meant
what you said earlier or not!
Could it be that it was only I
who thought we were friends?
If that’s the case,
I’m just a really lame guy…
Aren’t I? Sasuke?
Next episode: “For a Friend”