We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers
don't care what people think about them
follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh! Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
Down a difficult road
filled with endless struggles
Where do you think you are going
following someone else's map?
An insightful crow comes along
to tear up the map
Now open your eyes and
take a look at the truth (Yeah!)
There's nothing to lose,
so let's GO!!!
We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers
don't care what people think about them
follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh!
Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
We're gonna do it and do our best!
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
We're gonna do it and do our best! BANG!
Tsunade's Warning:
Ninja No More!
Good work, Akamaru!
You nailed it!
Midair Dynamic Marking!
Next, three twists!
Aim carefully!
Can one call that a walk?
No, I don’t think one can.
I can’t gather insects at ease.
It’s so great…
that the three of you have things
you’re good at and that you love…
I hope you’ll find
something like that too, Hinata.
You're right…
And, what is it?
You had something
to tell me, didn’t you?
Umm…
Yeah…
So, using that as a hint,
think about the fastest way
to get to the destination.
Start!
Everyone!
I’m sorry this happens all the time,
but class is over for today.
Yippee!
– Why? 					– Huh? Not again.
The handout is your homework!
– What?! 					– Huh?!
I’m so happy we didn’t have
the class for Taijutsu.
But these days,
class either finishes in the morning
or we have the whole day off…
I wonder if that’s really okay.
What’s up with acting like
a serious student?
Right, Konohamaru?
Huh?
Konohamaru?
Konohamaru!
What do you think you’re doing
with Grandpa's things?!
Honorable grandson…
Those belong to my Grandpa!
Where are you taking them?!
Uh…you mean these?
They are no longer used,
so I thought I’d put them into storage
in a different location.
No longer used, you say…
You think it’s okay to take Grandpa’s
things away without permission?!
The Fifth Hokage will be using
the chambers, you know.
The Fifth Hokage?
Y-Yes.
The next Hokage
has finally been decided.
The village can have peace of mind now.
That person apparently
doesn’t smoke tobacco…
What do you mean, Fifth Hokage?!
It’s too soon for that!
When you depended on
the Old Man up to recently!
What a lovely fragrance…
Huh?!
Wh-What are you doing?!
That’s exactly my question for you!
You perverted kid…
I dare you to say that again!
Huh? You want me
to say it again?
Per-vert-ed kid!
Don’t call me that!
Lady Tsunade!
The elders are all waiting,
so we had better hurry.
Yes, I know.
Be careful, little boy.
Please be more conscious
of your actions.
I’m the person
who has to deal with the complaints…
Okay, okay.
I’m not a little boy!
Who the heck are you?!
That’s my question…
Naruto!
Konohamaru?
Long time no see!
Hey, more importantly, have you seen
a big-boobed, scary old lady…
I mean, young lady?
I did see her!
– Where did she go?!
– Who the heck is she?!
Who is she?
She has to go
to the hospital straightaway!
Hospital?
That lady may not look it,
but she’s an awesome
Medical Corps Ninja!
She finally came back to the village
to become the Hokage, so…
what is she taking her sweet time for?!
Hokage…
The Fifth Hokage.
She better do what
she promised to do.
You’re lying…
Huh?
I don’t believe you!
It’s a lie!
What?
There are seven birds within 50 meters
behind me in the direction of the “2.”
Tenten…?
Neji!
I just heard that that Lady Tsunade
has returned!
It’s the real McCoy.
Wanna go see her?
Sorry.
But I’m not interested.
Huh?
So there were…
eight birds, huh…
Listen carefully, Tsunade.
We must call the feudal lords
and announce the fact that
the Fifth Hokage has been chosen.
We will start preparations today
for the inauguration ceremony in the village.
Feudal lords and ceremonies
are just a big pain.
Tsunade!
Yes, yes, I know…
This is also the job of the Hokage.
– Genma! 					– Here!
– Aoba! 					– Here!
Issue an official notice and
convey this matter to those in the village
within the next few days.
We must introduce the Fifth Hokage.
– Yes, ma'am! 					– Yes, ma'am!
I hate you, Grandpa!
Why did you have to die?
The Fifth Hokage…
Gimme a break,
my shoulders are so stiff.
I wish I could just down
a nice cup of hot sake and relax.
Lady Tsunade!
Wait a second!
Before you do that,
you have something else you need to do,
Old Lady Tsunade!
What was it?
I told you, didn’t I?!
About Kakashi Sensei and
Sasuke and Bushy Brow!
Oh…right, right.
Hey, if it isn’t Naruto!
Huh? Shikamaru?
Why are you in a place like this?
That’s my question–
I have no idea why,
but my father told me
to come along with him.
What’s up with that?
Long time no see, Lady Tsunade.
Oh, the kid from the Nara Family, huh.
Are you taking proper care
of the deer?
The antlers of the deer from
that area make very good medicine.
Yes, I’m somehow managing.
Hey, Naruto, who’s that person
who acts like such
a big shot when she's so young?
That’s apparently the new Hokage.
Huh?!
Despite her appearance,
she’s an old lady in her fifties.
Yikes!
Well, see you again sometime.
Yes, ma’am.
All right, to the hospital!
See you later, Shikamaru.
I’m will show you an awesome
new technique I learned!
That’s the new Fifth Hokage…?
Hey, Shikamaru.
That person is the strongest
and most beautiful person in the world.
Huh?
I mean, she’s the lone female
amongst the Legendary Sannin.
Huh… A female Hokage?
I’m not very comfortable with women…
Huh?
Even though they're unusually frank,
they always hang around and
you're never quite sure
whose side they're on.
They always think they can make
men do whatever they want.
Anyway, they’re just a pain.
Hey Shikamaru…
Without women,
men wouldn’t be born.
If women weren’t around,
nothing good would come of men.
No matter how hard-edged
a woman might be,
she’ll show her gentle side
to the man she loves.
I can’t believe that Pa’s saying that…
when he's tied to Mom’s apron strings.
You’ll understand once
you reach that age.
Oh no!
Let’s hurry up and
get our business done…
because Mom will chew us out
if we’re late.
Hurry up, Shikamaru!
Looks like nothing will come
of some men
even if they have a woman.
Konoha Hospital
I’m coming in.
Who are you…?
What a beautiful woman…
Sakura, Sakura!
Everything will be all right now!
I brought along an awesome person.
Sasuke will be fine now!
Naruto…
Those two flowers aren’t from
the same day.
So this kid is coming here
every day, huh…
I heard from Guy Sensei…
Please save Sasuke.
OK, leave it to me.
Sasuke!
Sasuke…
Sasuke, you…!
Hmm, despite his appearance,
that Naruto is pretty considerate.
Huh?
Next! Next!
How disgraceful!
To be taken down by
just two insurgents.
And here I thought you were a genius.
I’m sorry…
All right! Kakashi Sensei’s done!
Next, Bushy Brow!
Please hurry up and
take a look at my disciple Lee!
Lee!
I brought Lady Tsunade here!
That’s your disciple?
Yes! My beloved, beloved disciple!
I see…
Naruto.
Huh?
Is it really okay for you
to be idling away your time here like this?
Uh, I almost forgot!
I had an appointment to
meet Iruka Sensei!
Go on!
OK! I’ll leave the rest in your hands!
All right!
Hey, Naruto!
You’re late, Iruka Sensei!
Sorry, sorry.
There were lots of things to do
with respect to the Fifth Hokage.
I guess…
Thanks for waiting!
I’m digging in!
Naruto.
Huh…?
You have really developed compared
to the time when you wanted this.
I have, haven’t I?
You think so too, right?
This headband that I received
from Iruka Sensei
suits me perfectly, don’t you think?
Stop being so cocky!
You still have a long,
long way to go!
You have lots of work to do!
Listen carefully, Naruto!
The Leaf Village is in
a very difficult situation right now.
Starting with the Third Hokage,
we lost many fine Shinobi.
The current strength of the Leaf
is less than half what it normally is.
Despite that, we must continue
to carry out our missions.
Why is that?
If you don’t have enough manpower,
you should turn it down.
No, that won’t do…
If we turn down our missions,
it would be like announcing
to other countries our weakened state.
Even Kakashi Sensei who is still ailing
will probably be assigned to missions.
I see…these are difficult times.
Hey! This concerns you too!
You need to play an active role
and carry out your duties
in order to aid Lady Tsunade.
Yeah.
But, before I do that,
I need to satisfy my stomach.
That’s just like you.
Do your best!
Seconds!
Hey, hey!
How'd you finish so fast?!
I'll be straight with you.
Give up being a Shinobi.
L-Lady Tsunade…
don’t joke like that.
There are numerous bone fragments
in the area around important nerves.
Moreover, they are deeply embedded.
You’re not physically capable
of carrying out the missions of a Shinobi.
Come now, Lady Tsunade,
don’t joke like that…
Even if I were to operate…
Don’t be fooled, Lee!
That Lady Tsunade is an impostor!
You changed yourself
using the Transformation Jutsu,
you evil woman!
Who the heck are you?!
Don’t I have any…chance?
There is no one besides me
who is capable of doing the surgery
and it would take too much time.
Furthermore, there is a huge risk…
Risk?
The probability of
a successful surgery is 50% at best,
and if it fails…
You’ll die.
Guy Sensei!
I’m not at all ready
to throw in the towel!
Guy Sensei, what’s this god-awful
bitter rice dumpling?
They are Youthful Vigor Herbal Pills.
If you eat one hundred of them,
they should heal your wound.
I see, if I don’t eat
one hundred of them,
my wound won’t heal, right?
N-Not in a single day!
It’s better that you give up being
a Shinobi and look for a different path.
Lee…
If I knew this was going to happen,
I shouldn’t have brought you to him.
Don’t say that…!
I am painfully aware of how you feel,
but it’s better to be clear.
Because it’s something he’ll have
to understand sooner or later.
The longer we wait…
the harder it will be for him.
I believe your promise,
its a true heart give me courage
Always I feel it
the precious time with you
On your still shoulder
I feel the wind that blows
towards tomorrow
The city lights are like pieces of stars
That hold us together
“Each one of us glows differently,”
you say laughingly
but you look most dazzling
Like a comet,
like the rainbow after the storm
You bring light into my heart
Being lost can be the answer
Let’s promise we won’t cheat
Uh... like a shooting star,
we do go ahead.
Konohamaru, just come out
from there already!
Shut up!
Listen, I'll treat you to
a bowl of ramen!
Don't want any!
OK then. I'll add pork slices and eggs.
You're such a pest!
What did you just say?!
In that case,
I'll pull you out by force!
Be ready for that!
Next time:
"The Will of Fire Still Burns!"
Don't miss it!