Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost, let’s start walking
One more time
Are you really happy
when you're always meeting
to someone's expectations?
Even if you change to
who you really wanna be
Will you always have a great smile?
Dreaming of only “the beginning,”
I wake up
and someday, I'll live on my own.
Yes, precious things are never in shape
You never know what it is
when you get it or lose it
Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost,
let's start walking
One more time
You shouldn’t lower your guard, Sensei.
I’ll bury you and correct
old mistakes, now!
Whatever you do now, it’s too late…
I’ve won…
The Leaf Village will crumble!
I am the man who carried on the Leaf Will
of the First and Second Hokages…
The Third Hokage!
Orochimaru! Now I will perform an
ace Jutsu that even you don’t know!
Behold! Sealing Jutsu!
Forbidden Secret Technique:
Reaper Death Seal!
A Jutsu I don’t know…
Must hurry…
This darkness is dangerous.
I’ll have you show it to me.
What’s the matter?
Are you planning to be killed
slowly by your predecessors?
Please perform that Jutsu, quick.
Not yet…?
It looks like…I was just in time.
What’s the matter?
You’re already stumbling…
Now all that’s left…
is to catch them!
I got you!
I won’t let go!
Appear!
The darkness has disappeared…
What’s this Jutsu?
Sarutobi!
I’m sorry…Sarutobi…
We caused you trouble…
Please forgive me…
Lord First Hokage!
Lord Second Hokage!
Seal!
Your own subordinates…!
All members in
the Leaf Village are a part of me.
The villagers believe in me,
and I believe in everyone.
That’s what the Hokage is.
Saru… Protect those who love
the village and believe in you.
And bring them up as individuals
to whom you can leave the next era.
As of tomorrow, you are the…
Hokage!
Toying with even the lives
of your own subordinates…!
Subordinates’ lives?
Stop the endless nonsense!
Didn’t these kids believed in you?
Come! Enma!
You’re mine!
Striking Shadow Snake!
Dang it! You little--!
It’s over!
What is this sensation…?
This is bad…
– Die! 					– Die!
We have to hold them off here somehow.
Isn't our back-up here yet?!
This is out of our hands!
Ninja Art: Summoning!
Bring Down the House Jutsu!
This Jutsu…
Long time no see, Ibiki.
Jeez, is that body
the only thing that grew?!
I can’t stand to look!
Master Jiraiya…
Jiraiya…! One of Sannin,
the three legendary Shinobi?!
Peeps, open up those little eyes
of yours just this once and observe well.
How wonderful!
The devil region beyond heaven
of Jiraiya, the fantastic sage Ninja…
will rage!
Snakes that have been antagonized
by the frog. Begone!
So that Orochimaru has finally started, eh?
Where’s the Third Hokage?
The Exam arena.
I see…
Don’t die…old man.
Why…didn’t you dodge?
Dang it!
The Reaper Death Seal…
In this Sealing Jutsu,
in exchange for the effectiveness
of Jutsu…
one’s own soul is handed over
to the Grim Reaper.
It’s a Jutsu that costs your life…
My Jutsu doesn’t activate…
There’s no need to dodge.
I will die, anyway.
At the same time the Sealing ends,
my soul will also be devoured.
It’s a Jutsu of the hero
who once saved this village.
From now, you will also die…
by this Jutsu!
So this Jutsu also sealed
that Nine-Tailed Fox, huh?!
And now, your soul will be dragged out…
and sealed!
My body…won’t listen to what I say!
You’ll probably be able to see it soon.
Your soul is also already
about halfway out, so.
Those who have their souls sealed
by this Jutsu
will suffer inside the belly
of the Grim Reaper for eternity
and will never attain peace…
Those who seal and are sealed
have their souls intertwined,
and will hate each other,
and continue to battle for eternity!
What…?!
This is… the Grim Reaper?!
Knock it off! You old dotard!
I won’t let you do as you like.
Hurry up and…die!
Okay, everyone. Line up!
Quiet, everyone!
Konohamaru!
Konohamaru, it’s not going
to collapse, is it?
It’ll…it’ll be okay.
The structure of this face rock path is old,
but is of strong construction.
My grandpa said so before.
So it’ll definitely be okay.
Someone’s coming!
Which one…?
Uchiha, huh?
Then, what about Temari?
Don’t run away like that…
Fine.
I’ll be your opponent this time.
Wait!
Temari!
I assumed you’d been
creamed by him.
So you’re okay?!
Yeah. Somehow…
But…
it didn’t turn out to
be much of a delay.
No, it’s time necessary for
Gaara’s recovery.
Besides, it’ll lead to
his consumption of Chakra.
This is…
Shampoo, again?
No, it’s Sasuke.
There are several smells near him.
He caught up…
At last…
Sasuke.
He’s totally stopped moving.
Is he going to fight with them?!
Sasuke…
Let’s hurry!
What’s this clump of countless smells
coming from another direction?
Hey! There’s something besides us
tracking Sasuke!
What?!
An enemy? An ally?!
I don’t know. But…
But?
It’s not human.
Huh?!
Go! Kankuro! I’ll take him again…
Temari, you take Gaara
and go on ahead.
What?
You’re at your limit…
I don’t need a hindrance.
But…!
Go!
Hurry up and go!
Okay…
It can’t be helped…
I’ll be your opponent!
Humph! I don’t care who it is!
No!
Your opponent is me!
You…!
Shino?
Why are you here?!
I put a female beetle on you
before you left the arena.
The females have almost no smell…
Only a male can sniff out
the subtle smell of the female.
Though the male itself
has a strong smell…
Sasuke Uchiha…
You pursue Gaara.
Because the battle between you
and him hasn’t been settled yet.
I’ll fight him, because originally
I was his opponent…
I withdraw!
Please go ahead with the match.
Leave this to me here! Go!
You’re very confident.
But are you going to be okay?
No need to worry.
I’ll go back you up if
I have just ten minutes.
Humph. By then, I’ll be done too.
None of you know anything at all.
You guys probably don’t know
of the real terror of this world.
In that case…
you’ll teach me that terror?
No…
If you defeat me and chase Gaara,
you’ll be forced to know.
That is, only if you can defeat me.
Everyone makes mistakes
lt’s nothing to be ashamed about
Don’t let this scar be for naught
Walk with a smile
Yes, breathe in the air
Lift your face to the sky and jump
If it rains, take a break
Go where the wind takes you
So many regrets
Don’t let this scar be for naught
Let’s go carve the badges in our chest
Yes, it’s Show Time, life begins now.
Everyone makes mistakes
It’s nothing to be ashamed about
Don’t let this scar be for naught
Walk with a smile
Transform sadness into the wind
and continue to forge on
Forge on strong
You who are strong…
You who are called Uchiha…
You who have friends…
You who have a purpose…
You who are like me…
By killing you, I can truly exist!
Uchiha, you are my prey!
Next time: “Astonishing Truth!
Gaara’s Identity Emerges!”