Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost, let’s start walking
One more time
Are you really happy
when you're always meeting
to someone's expectations?
Even if you change to
who you really wanna be
Will you always have a great smile?
Dreaming of only “the beginning,”
I wake up
and someday, I'll live on my own.
Yes, precious things are never in shape
You never know what it is
when you get it or lose it
Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost,
let's start walking
One more time
The winner is Temari.
Oh, I’m tired…
Oh, what a waste!
Why?! He had a chance to
become a Chunin!
Shikamaru is Shikamaru…
Really… Does he or doesn't he
have the motivation?
Even I’m not sure about it.
But his intelligence and strategies
are no longer at the Genin level.
If it had been an actual mission
for a basic platoon,
the win was decided when
he captured Temari…
So, I suppose he won the competition,
but he lost the match…
It’s unfortunate he shows no
signs of being motivated,
on the other hand, he won’t get too
emotional or fall into a panic.
And that’s exactly why…
he’d be able to calmly pull back if
he viewed a situation as totally hopeless.
That could be attributed to
calm judgment.
Shikamaru probably possesses…
the most important psychological
element required for a Chunin…
the disposition of a leader!
In order to evaluate someone
as a leader of a platoon…
it’s much more important to
protect the platoon from danger,
than to carry out a mission.
Yeah…it’d hardly be worth mentioning
a completed mission
if everyone was annihilated.
The risks and the mission
should be put on a scale,
surviving should be thought of first,
and then action should be taken.
A person who can’t do this isn’t
qualified to become a Chunin.
Hyuga and Naruto from earlier
fail on that point.
Although they are all right
as insignificant Genin.
Well, I do feel like Shikamaru
gave up too soon too.
What do you think?
What do I feel…?
He has more of a chance
than Naruto, for sure!
Shoot…!
Why the heck did he give up!
Is he an idiot?!
This ticks me off!
I’m gonna really give him
a lecture!
So the one that’s gonna
become a Chunin is…
You idiot!
Shut up, super idiot!
Why the heck did you give up?!
Let’s not talk about that anymore,
all right?
It’s not all right! It was a match
you were close to winning!
– Let's just watch the next match.
– But you just gave up! Unimaginable!
Simply unimaginable!
Huh? The next match?
Sasuke…!
"Dancing Leaf, Squirming Sand"
At last, Uchiha’s match is next.
Oh, but who’s this opponent Gaara?
I wonder…
But compared to Uchiha,
he’s nothing much.
Do you know?
I hear Uchiha’s gonna
withdraw from this match.
Really?!
Yeah, he apparently sustained a serious
injury while training before the match…
Are you serious?
And to think I took time off
specifically to see this match!
I’m counting on you, come on!
As you’d expect, this match
will be won by Uchiha.
No way, I’ve got high hope
for the new one of the Sand.
He won’t let this one slip by.
As they say about the world
of competition…
It’s impossible to predict
what will occur…
Lord Hokage, about Uchiha Sasuke,
he has not yet arrived at the arena.
Umm…it’s unavoidable…
We can’t make the guests
wait any longer.
Another ten minutes.
Why don’t we wait just
another ten minutes?
But…
The guests are looking forward
to the next match above all else.
Cancelling it would be cruel.
Since it’s come to this,
waiting another ten minutes wouldn’t hurt.
Lord Hokage…?
Umm…
Uchiha, where are you!
What's keeping you?
Hurry up!
There is some truth to what
Kazekage says.
So shall we extend it for
ten minutes from now.
So…let Genma know of this.
Yes!
If it stays like this, Uchiha will really
be forced to withdraw.
I see…a ten-minute extension…
Sasuke…
Hey, isn’t that…
Y-You are…
But, what’s that idiot doing!
He’s still not here?!
Sasuke…!
Please!
Good of the two of you to make it!
Come now, hurry into the arena!
Yeah!
All right! Here we go!
Oh! Yeah!
Most of the first round is finished,
and the only one left is
Sasuke Uchiha and Gaara.
H-How about Naruto and
Neji’s match…?!
Well, the interesting thing is…
That Hyuga lost…
Naruto beat Neji…
I see…
You did it!
Naruto!
You’re such a…
good guy really…
– What’s going on with the next match!
– Let's get on with it!
Isn’t Uchiha up yet?!
We want Uchiha! Uchiha!
Uchiha!
Hey, it’s almost time.
Is he really gonna come?!
He’ll come…
He’ll definitely come!
Oh Sasuke, what’s he doing!
What the heck is Uchiha doing?!
It seems the rumor that
he’d had a serious injury was true.
If there’s a win by default,
then this match is mine.
Thirty more seconds…
Uchiha!
Sasuke…please come!
Sasuke!
Hurry up and come!
It won’t be good if it stays this way!
The time limit is up.
So this is it.
Because the time limit has expired,
the last match…
See… Here he is…
Well, I’m sorry we’re late…
Sasu…
Your name?
Sasuke…Uchiha.
Sasuke!
It looks like he made it in time.
Lee!
Darn… Causing others
this much trouble…
and thinking himself so important!
Huh! You’re pretty late!
I thought you weren’t coming
‘cause you were scared to take me on!
Who the heck was it that
said he’d come for sure?
The first round…did you win?
Of course!
Don’t get too carried away…
Loser!
Well, I know it’s somewhat rude
to be showing up all flashy like this…
but was Sasuke…
disqualified?
So your habit of tardiness
rubbed off on him? Cripes…
And…what about it?
It’s all right, Sasuke’s match
has been postponed anyway.
Your arrival was barely in time, but…
he hasn’t been disqualified.
That’s good to hear!
Don’t lose to a guy like that!
Yeah…
I want to fight you too…
Sasuke!
I want…to fight you too!
Yeah…
Yay, Sasuke!
Uchiha's match is gonna start!
Shikamaru gave it so much,
but already it’s Sasuke…
Poor Shikamaru…
Hey, is that Uchiha?
I‘m just second fiddle…
Well, I guess that’s just
the way it goes…
I’m looking forward to it too.
Your team is sort of amazing, Sakura.
What is?
Well, Naruto did beat that
Neji Hyuga and…
Sasuke is an elite member
of the Uchiha…
and it seems like everyone’s
anxious to see Sasuke’s match.
Sasuke will face that Gaara
of the Sand whom I couldn’t beat…
And Naruto beat that Neji
that I had hoped to take down.
Why is it so…
Why am I so…
frustrated!
Lee…!
At last…
Gaara, come down here!
Naruto! Let’s go up!
Yeah!
When we go up,
we’ll leisurely take the stairs.
What’s up with you!
Are you still upset that
I pushed you down?!
T-This isn’t good…
It’s been quite awhile
since I’ve seen Gaara like this.
H-Hey…Gaara.
Keep the strategy in mind--!
Don’t talk to Gaara right now!
You’ll be killed.
Right!
Let’s go!
Hey, hurry up!
Nothing good’s gonna happen
in your life if you panic.
What’s wrong?
Huh?
Low-level tournaments like this
Chunin Examination are ideal
as gambling matches.
A number of feudal lords
are here for that purpose.
So…would you lose this match for us.
Hey, come on,
at least give us an answer.
Too scared to say anything…
H-Help!
S-Stop! Stop!
If those two in front of us
hadn’t been there,
we probably would’ve been killed…
This is the first I’ve seen anyone
kill people without hesitation like that…
This isn’t looking good
even for Sasuke.
Sasuke…
So now…at last…
Everyone makes mistakes
lt's nothing to be ashamed about
Don’t let this scar be for naught
Walk with a smile
Yes, breathe in the air
Lift your face to the sky and jump
If it rains, take a break
Go where the wind takes you
So many regrets
Don’t let this scar be for naught
Let’s go carve the badges
in our chest
Yes, it’s Show Time,
life begins now.
Everyone makes mistakes
It’s nothing to be ashamed about
Don’t let this scar be for naught
Walk with a smile
Transform sadness into the wind
and continue to forge on
Forge on strong
Darn it!
What kind of guy is that?!
Gaara is totally not normal!
He doesn't even look at us.
If anyone fights with him like that…
Darn! Hey Shikamaru!
We've got to go see Kakashi Sensei!
We've got to stop this fight,
no matter what!
Next time, "Bushy Brow's Jutsu:
Sasuke Style!"
If nothing's done,
Sasuke's a goner!