Press down hard on the gas
That’s right, there’s no compromise
We'll slip through the night
At the final moment push hard
That's right, all the way to zero,
Until we wipe away the days
Gently open your heart
If you pull it close to you
It will reach you, without a doubt
It will come, closer
Now
We’re speeding through life,
squeezing it for all of its worth
Our feet are tied
But we still keep going farther
Even if I take it back, and grasp it
If you’re not the one
There will be no meaning
And so we’ll go far off into the distance.
The waves of pain are coming faster...
Sasuke, you should quit
the preliminaries!
Huh?!
L-Look, you haven't been yourself
ever since you got worked over
by that Orochimaru guy!
Yoroi Akado vs. Sasuke Uchiha
To think it’d be so soon…?!
I couldn’t ask for more.
For the 1st battle,
Yoroi Akado and Sasuke Uchiha
have been selected.
No objections, right?
- Right!
-No!
The pain won’t go away!
It appears the Curse Mark hurts.
Don’t use the Sharingan.
So you knew?
If that Curse Mark on
your neck gets out of control,
it could endanger your life.
I believe it.
Well, the match will be
called off at that time.
I’ll be coming in to stop it,
so good luck.
Called off, you say?!
It seems this Curse Mark thing
is responding to my Chakra.
In other words, in this match,
I can hardly use even
my regular Jutsu,
not to mention the Sharingan!
However… Yoroi’s ability is
the worst for you, Sasuke.
Now then, please begin.
You… my Chakra…
You just noticed now…?
Bushy-Brow's Jealousy -
Lions Barrage Unleashed!
You… my Chakra…
You just noticed now…?
Yes…Yoroi has unorthodox ability
to absorb Chakra.
It’s a magnificent art that
absorbs spiritual and physical energy
simply by holding his palm against
an opponent’s body.
And, if all of your Chakra
is absorbed, Sasuke,
you’ll be forced to rely upon
the power of my Curse Mark…
Now, release that luscious power…!
That is the only way
you have to survive.
You…little!
To think you still have strength left…
Though you’re just a guinea pig.
That was a close one…
Put your mind at ease…
I’ll end this right away!
What’s the matter, what’s the matter?!
You already finished?!
His aim is one, close-quarter fight.
What should I do!?
At this rate, things will go downhill…
Sasuke Uchiha…
ls this the best you can do?
Sasuke…
Sasuke!
You call yourself an Uchiha with that?
Don’t be looking so lame!
Give your best!
That guy…
That’s it!
Oh!
You can’t afford to be inattentive!
I’ll finish you with this!
Is this as far as it goes…?
He…vanished?!
That’s my…!
What?!
Huh?
But then…from here on is my original.
It’s over…
The Dancing Leaf Shadow…?!
Eat this!
Dang it…!
lt’s responding every time…
Please…!
I’m begging you…
Stop!
You! Sasuke!
Don’t be looking so lame!
To think they’d be worried about me…
Is this it…?
I won’t be swallowed up…
by this thing...
No way!
The Curse Mark receded!?
Here I go!
You’re weak!
You’re weak.
I’m not done, yet!
Lions Barrage!
There’s no need to check.
I’m stopping the match from
going any further…
Therefore, the winner of the
first battle, Sasuke Uchiha…
passes the preliminaries!
Yes!
Well. Good job…
Before that Lions Barrage,
your movements were that
of Guy’s Taijutsu…
So you copied it with the Sharingan
when you wrangled that one time
with that Lee kid?
Sasuke! You, you…
won in a lame way!
Look at you, all battered up!
You idiot!
Man, that loser…
Sasuke…Thank goodness.
Okay, I’ll win, too!
Lee… Because of you,
I’ve managed to save my neck.
Things would’ve gotten hairy
if I hadn’t seen your technique
in close-quarters combat.
But it doesn’t appear to be a technique
that I can use heavily.
I see… So before, he copied a part
of the technique I only used once?
Sharingan!
That’s your ability…
Sasuke… you’re quite a person.
You get rapidly stronger…
I kind of…feel a bit of fear.
For a sequence of
high-speed Taijutsu Lotus movements,
it’s impossible to acquire this
without training
that whittles away flesh and blood.
No matter how much you
use the Sharingan,
it can’t just be mastered in
a short space of time…
Moreover, his idea for that
finishing move…
Kakashi… this boy reminds me
of when you were a kid…
Last year’s number one rookie
was Neji Hyuga.
This year’s number one rookie
is Sasuke Uchiha.
I wonder which one is stronger…?
Really, he’s something else.
To think he’d develop the true power
of the Sharingan in situation like this…
What’s most to be feared…
is the Uchiha ability?
That was surprising…
To think he brought the Curse Mark
that was getting out of control
into submission with his will…
Tsk. Again?
It just make it more interesting!
Yeah! He is Sasuke after all…
This is as far as we’ll go…
I’m hungry…
W-Wow!
Nothing special.
Magnificent…
Sasuke Uchiha...
We medics will give you
the best of treatment.
You guys are out of your territory.
Huh?!
I’ll take him under my care…
Now, I’ll take you into the back…
and seal the Curse Mark.
Can we wait until
the preliminaries are over?!
I want to watch the matches
of those who will remain in the main battle.
No!
Don’t get so heated.
If we let things be
any further,
the situation might become irrevocable.
I won’t accommodate you anymore.
Now then, come on…
Sasuke…
Hm?
Sakura... Speaking of which,
during the match…
did you see something that looked
like a strange wound on Sasuke’s neck?
What?
Please promise me…
Don’t say anything about
this bruise to Naruto.
What?
Listen… this is also teamwork.
It won’t do to have him
unnecessarily worried.
I-I don’t know either.
I see…
Umm, now then…
We will get right to it and
begin the second match.
Abumi Zaku vs. Shino Aburame
Which weakling is it?!
Both of you, come forward.
We will now begin the second match.
That’s the Sound Ninja…
The guy who had both
his arms broken by Sasuke!
It seems like you’re proud
of your arms…
You!
S-Stop it!
He’s going to fight with those arms?
I wonder if Shino is going to be okay…
He’s fine. He’s strong!
What…?
I’d square off with anybody except him…
Now then, please begin.
Now, Zaku…
How you fight will be a sight to see…
If you fight here,
you’ll be finished…
Withdraw!
Somehow, this one still works, so…
One arm is enough to take care of you!
You can’t beat me with
just one arm.
Stop pestering me!
Take this!
Slicing Sound Wave!
Okay.
Hang in there.
lt’ll be over right away.
Curse Sealing!
Next time, even if that Curse Mark
starts kicking in again…
the power of this Curse Sealing
should suppress it.
However, this Sealing Jutsu makes
the strength of your will its foundation.
If something happens like
you not believing in your own strength
and that will were to weaken…
the Curse Mark will
once again start to rage.
Out of character.
It appears he’s quite tired…
To think you’ve become able to
handle Sealing Jutsu…
You’ve grown, eh, Kakashi…?
You…
Long time no see, Kakashi.
Orochimaru…
Hey, can you hear it?
The clear, blue sky goes on and on
The ocean spans limitlessly
Please keep that smile on your face forever
Or else I’ll cry
You won't have to search around you
It’s all ok now.
Everyone is inside
this hand
when you want to cry,
and you want to run away
When you forget what happiness is
Just sing.
Light is born, and darkness was born
The two are one
Harmonia, feel the telepathy
Hey, can you hear it?
This is surprising.
I never thought you’d appear.
Why are you after Sasuke?
What’s your purpose?!
Even though you’re one of
the legendary three Ninja,
I must not retreat.
I’ll stop you here,
even if it costs my life!
Next episode: “Kakashi and Orochimaru:
Face-to-Face!”
Well, it’s sink or swim.