I want to try and gather
the unrestrained winds
I’ll run toward the horizon,
alongside the wave crests
I’ve made my decision,
even if there’s a long way to go
on that road.
I’ll continue towards the future I’ve planned
Time rushes us
The heartbeat speeds up
When I woke in the middle of a dream
I kept searching for that same light
Under the shining star-lit sky with
countless constellations and shadows
There was something beyond that…
What were you gazing at?
The Enemy of the Byakugan
They blew up…
They blew up and died!
As I expected, I’m not sad.
You really can’t hold funerals
feeling like this, huh…
Four of them are still alive.
Can’t be! After being hit
by my Lightning Fang…
No…
If you say so, it has to be true.
One…is troublesome…
The enemy was nearby…
But I couldn’t see anything.
It’s strange…
Even if it’s the Hidden Mist Jutsu,
my Byakugan should be able
to see through it.
Byakugan!
For sure this time…
I can see it!
Southwest 52 degrees 2!
Southeast 12 degrees 3!
Southeast 8 degrees 1!
Northwest 24 degrees 11!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Let’s go!
Leaf Hurricane!
No way!
Why?!
U-zu-ma-ki Barrage!
I missed!
H-Help me!
Bushy Brow…?
Th-The enemy disappeared!
It can’t be…
The false images with Chakra Networks?
One at the middle of the cliff,
one at the bottom of the cliff,
one on the right, one on the left.
We can’t hold funerals,
but I’ll take care of them
without leaving any trace.
Thunder Funeral: Feast of Lightning!
The corpses are warm.
We’re strong…you and I.
No, it’s you.
Ranmaru, you’re strong.
With you I’m also strong.
Wait… They aren’t dead yet.
They’re just unconscious.
They’re stubborn.
Okay, if grilling doesn’t work,
then let’s chop them.
Flesh and even bone…
I’ll crush them nicely.
Ranmaru…! Are you all right?!
Hang in there, Ranmaru!
Ranmaru…!
I’m okay.
Raiga…
This person…is still unconscious.
What did you say?
It’s amazing…
He is fighting
only with muscle memory.
It’s a nice face.
lt burns into my heart.
Let’s hold a funeral for him…
I am sure it will be one
that will make me cry!
From the right!
What’s with this guy…?
He’s hard to read. The moves…
But for your sake, Raiga,
I’ll do my best.
Together, okay!
Left!
Right!
From the front! Jump! Now!
You…you…you!
What?
How can this guy…
get to this point?
B-Bushy Brows…
Lee…
Could he have lost consciousness…?
Tenten! Neji!
Raiga! Turn around!
What…? That voice right now…?
Wha–?!
Raiga!
Ranmaru!
This is…
Neji…
Ranmaru!
Move!
Huh? Somehow…it felt like
I was fighting in my dreams…
Ranmaru…
You!
Heh! Naruto Uzumaki arrives!
Naruto…
Just die already…
Hey! I have something
I want to ask you!
You… I heard you’re one of
the Seven Ninja Swords Men of the Mist.
So what if I was?!
You know Zabuza, right?!
You also know…
one called Kisame, right?!
I…hate them!
Who wants to remember them?!
I hate you too!
Then!
I’ll make you tell me by force!
A clone?!
You… You’re weaker
than a moment ago.
Wh-What…?
Lightning Ball!
Damn…
Huh, you are tough…
Lightning Ball!
Seconds, please…
Grandma Sansho?
What’s wrong?
Oh my. That’s bad lightning.
It was flashing like that too when
Karashi went to the village.
Oh my…that light is like poison…
Naruto!
It’s not…working at all.
I’m not going to
remember your smile!
Die!
Ranmaru…where are you?
What is in this bag…?
Byakugan!
There’s…in here…
Could it be?
This powder was…
hiding the Chakra Networks?
It’s even creating the Chakra Network!
Naruto!
Do the Shadow Clone Jutsu!
But he saw all the shadow clones…
Don’t worry.
His eyes are right here!
Ranmaru! I’m gonna come save you
after I defeat this guy!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Come bring it on!
Lightning Ball!
What? Was the one before a lucky hit?
Stop messing around.
All I have to do is defeat you all, right?!
Let’s go!
We’re not done yet!
You…
At this rate…my Chakra will…
The mist…
The Hidden Mist Jutsu is fading away…
Damn! I’ll finish them off at once!
Damn!
I am not going to let you get away!
Wait!
Ninja Art: Boulder Avalanche.
Naruto!
Naruto…
Did you see that…?!
Yeah, I saw it!
Prepare yourself!
Stop it!
I can’t stop!
I…did it.
This is…Raiga’s eye…?
Such a big eye ball!
Huh?
You’re wrong…
lt’s a human being!
Huh…?!
In my dream…
I guess you were the one
I was fighting against.
It wasn’t me…
lt was Raiga and me together…
Together…?
Always…since that time…
Don’t act like you’re asleep.
You are going to die…
Don’t move!
There is a spy in this village
who snuck into the Hidden Mist Village…
We came to kill those guys, but…
I got confused about who I had to kill.
That’s why I am doing it randomly…
Wh-What are you saying?
It’s fine…
lf I am going to be killed by you.
Huh…?
Why is it fine for me to kill you…?
You were…always crying…
Huh? Me…cry?
In your heart…
seeking the meaning of living.
I was always watching…you.
What…are you?
I am the same as you…
living is painful.
I don’t understand
the meaning of living.
Because of my sickness,
I couldn’t go outside…
Shunned by everyone,
all I could do was to take
a peek of the world from this blanket…
But …if with my death,
if you are able to feel
the meaning of life even a little…
My life was not needed
from the beginning.
Please…
Are you…alone?
Come with me.
From now on,
you and I are two as one.
From that day on,
I became Raiga’s eyes and ears.
Raiga became my hands and feet.
The outside world that I dashed
into for the very first time…
it was filled with things
I had never seen or heard before.
It was fun.
Whenever and wherever,
I was with Raiga.
No matter when it was,
there wasn’t a time
that we were separated.
We were trying to find the meaning of life
by living for each other.
We were convinced that
was the meaning to living.
That’s why…
If Raiga is not around,
I no longer have the power
to live by myself.
I’ve lost the purpose to live…
Do you have someone
precious to you?
I want to protect
someone important to me…
I want to make his dream come true,
and that’s my dream.
Often people have it wrong…
mistakenly believing that showing mercy
to an enemy is kindness.
They spare the foe
whose life is in their hands.
It’s not mercy to me at all…
Do you know the agony of just living
without dreams and being unwanted?
What are you saying?
Zabuza has no use for a weak Shinobi.
You’ve taken away my reason for living.
I no longer need to live.
Don’t say such stupid things.
Naruto… Please kill me!
Huh?
What are you doing?
Now, quickly.
Why are you hesitating…?
With my arms and legs torn apart,
I have no means to resist, you know.
You should carry out your mission….
Hurry and deliver your finishing blow.
Our mission is to force out
the Kurosuki Family from this village…
Without Raiga, he cannot be
of any threat to this village.
The problem right now is that
the Kurosuki Family members
have lost their leadership.
Once the hoop comes off,
we don’t know what they will do.
For this mission…
this is the finishing touch.
Yeah, but what are we
going to do with him?
Is he a villain worth tying up?
No, he is not.
He might kill himself, right?
Once the mission is over,
we will come save you right away…
A Chakra Sealing tag?
We can’t help it.
He is an enemy, after all…
We should assume he has other Jutsu.
Just in case!
So many things happen
on this endless road, huh?
Although you’re strong-willed,
your voice wavered on the phone today
What dreams did you chase to get here?
Even I have times when
I just don’t understand, baby
When you’re sad, I’ll be close to you
Even on nights when we’re apart,
I’ll be close to you
Rokusuke and the others
went back to the village,
so I say the mission is complete.
Except Lee.
Oh, oh yeah.
Bushy Brow said he was
going to straighten Karashi’s spirit.
I wonder if it’s going to be
that easy.
It seems like
there will be some trouble.
Hey, why are you saying that?!
No, not Karashi, but this weather.
Next episode:
“The Dark Creeping Clouds”
I see. There’s going to be a storm.