We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers
don't care what people think about them
follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh! Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
Down a difficult road
filled with endless struggles
Where do you think you are going
following someone else's map?
An insightful crow comes along
to tear up the map
Now open your eyes and
take a look at the truth (Yeah!)
There's nothing to lose,
so let's GO!!!
We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers
don't care what people think about them
follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh!
Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
We're gonna do it and do our best!
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
We're gonna do it and do our best! BANG!
What’s the matter?
After pursuing me like that,
what’s up with you?
You’re not even able to touch me…
What a laugh!
Sakura…
I don’t know how far I can go, but…
I have to give it…my best shot!
Naruto’s Ninja Handbook
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Here goes!
From this moment on,
Secret Ultimate Taijutsu technique!
Naruto Uzumaki…
Clone Body Slam!
– Now! 					– Now!
Okay!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Once again…
Take this!
Leaf Village Secret Ultimate
Taijutsu technique
learned from Kakashi Sensei!
A Thousand Years of Death!
An enema?
Boom.
Sasuke…?
That was a splendid blow.
D-Did that get him?
Gaara…
Doing all that work…
And managing just one blow, huh?
S-Shut up!
He attacked the base of the tail
which has the weakest defense…
Even though I’m not wounded,
I can’t absorb the impact.
Did I underestimate him too much?
Hey, Naruto…
Sakura… Go rescue her
if it’s the last thing you do!
And after you’ve rescued her…
take Sakura and
lose no time in fleeing.
You, if anyone, can do it!
Sasuke… You…
I still have the ability…
to hold him in check for a while.
If things end here…
it would just mean that
was the extent of the man I am.
I lost everything once…
I don’t want to see…
any precious comrades die
right before my eyes again.
Precious…comrades…
I will not allow my comrades…
to be killed, no matter what.
I see…
That’s right.
Because he resembles me…
Because he has gone through life
with the same loneliness
and sadness as I have…
That guy who continued to fight
in solitude for himself,
I thought…he was strong.
Naruto…
But that’s not the meaning
of true strength…
If one fights just for
oneself in solitude…
one can’t really become strong…
Is there someone who
is precious to you?
When a person wants to protect
someone who is precious to him…
it’s then that they truly…
become…strong.
You will…become strong.
He’s releasing such
massive amount of Chakra!
That’s…Naruto?!
No matter what, I will…
protect you!
Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
He’s pretty good, this one.
I’ve kept you waiting
a long time!
The spiraling series of Naruto Uzumaki’s
Ninja Handbook starts now!
W-What’s up with this…
large number of clones?!
What the heck is this?
T-This is…amazing!
You are pretty promising.
You… This is…
Sasuke, you get yourself
a good rest.
Leave the rest to Naruto Uzumaki!
This guy is…
All right! Everyone! Here I go!
that Naruto?!
Jump!
Naruto’s…Ninja…Handbook!
Everywhere…
Shuriken!
My body hasn’t fully recovered…
My only choice is to
use Sand as a defense!
– Na! Ru! To! 2K Uzumaki…!
– Barrage! 					– Barrage!
T-This guy…!
– This time, I’ll use both legs…
– and go for a 4K Barrage!
Who the heck is that…?
Suddenly…
Unbelievable…
To get Gaara in that state…
Where does that strength come from?
No way! 					There's no way…
No way I’ll…lose to…a guy like this…!
W-What’s…that?
It finally…emerged.
The Perfect Possession!
This is…
the monster inside that guy.
I didn’t think you would
expose this form!
Naruto!
Darn…my body…!
My Chakra has…
with all those clones earlier on…
Sakura!
D-Darn…!
I, Inu, Tori, Saru, Hitsuji…
This will mark your end…
– Sand Burial!
– Summoning Jutsu!
It’s amazing that he can utilize
a Summoning Jutsu in that state…
I will protect…
Sakura!
Naruto Uzumaki…
You continue to give me
such pleasure…
Naruto… 					What in the…world…?
My hours of practice
are finally paying off!
I can do it!
– What is this? 					– Huh?
Not you again!
What in the world do you want?
Huh?!
That must be…
the Shukaku of the Sand.
Chief Toad!
Come join me in this fight!
No way!
What?!
Why would I go out of my way
and fight a guy like that?
That’s idiotic!
Why?!
You told me the other day that you
would make me your henchman!
It’s only natural for a chief
to help out his henchman!
That’s respect and duty, right?!
It’s true I told you
I’d make you my henchman…
But we haven’t even exchanged
cups of sake to seal our relationship yet…
Gimme a break! I’m still underage!
I can’t drink alcohol!
Don’t say that and just listen
to what this guy says, Pop!
Huh?! Pop?!
Why are you here, Gamakichi?
I had lots of time on my hands,
so I came to visit…
Huh? Huh?
You’re father and son?
Then that guy over there
tried to bully me!
What was that?!
When that happened,
this guy here rescued me…
He clashed with that monster…
Pretty interesting guy.
I see…
Kid… I recognize you
as my henchman…
and I’ll show you what duty
and respect means!
I’ll make you pay the price
good and proper, you underling!
Hang on tight!
How’s that?!
Awesome…
What a guy…
He’s so heavy,
I could barely manage to
thrust my dagger through him.
If I don’t hurry up,
this battle will change
the shape of the landscape.
Hey! Hey! Chief!
Sakura is over that way,
so don’t move that way!
Please lure him in this direction.
Sakura…?
That’s his girlfriend, Pop.
I’ve got to take that guy down.
Otherwise, I won’t be able
to rescue Sakura!
Interesting!
This is interesting!
Naruto Uzumaki!
T-This isn’t good!
That Gaara…
He’s intending to do that thing.
I better get out of here!
Huh…? That is…
That’s…the medium…?
To thank you for entertaining me
up to now…
I’ll show you the real power…
of the Sand Spirit!
The circles under his eyes…
Those are symptoms of
insomnia which indicate
that the medium is also possessed
by the Shukaku of the Sand.
Insomnia…?
Those who are possessed
by the Demon Raccoon Shukaku
are unable to sleep soundly
through the entire night.
Because of the terror…
If one sleeps, Shukaku will slowly
eat away at their personality
and eventually that person
is no longer himself.
Because he normally
doesn’t get much sleep…
the medium’s personality
tends to…become unstable.
Oh…
Therefore, usually while
the medium is awake,
the power of Shukaku is
normally controlled.
However…
when that medium sleeps…
Playing Possum Jutsu!
He’s done it…!
W-What’s gonna happen, Chief?
If one sets Playing Possum Jutsu
into motion…
…the Shukaku will appear!
I’m finally able to emerge!
That’s the Shukaku?
He’s pretty funky…
Right away!
The guy I wanna kill! You!
I’m gonna jump…
Huh?
Wind Style: Air Bullets!
Water Style: Water Bullets!
That’s practically a storm…
What kind of a battle is this…?!
Chief! I told you,
not in that direction!
Shut up! I know!
Air Bullets!
Water Bullets!
Too bad…
This isn’t good, Chief!
There's one shot left…!
Yeah! I killed it…
I killed it!
That hurts…!
How dare you shoot me
with bullets containing
stupid amounts of Chakra!
Even I can’t take that many shots!
What should we do?!
For a start,
wake up that medium kid!
It will release that Jutsu!
How do we go about waking him?!
Give him a good punch!
Water Bullets!
Like I’ll take that!
Now!
Chief, I can’t hit him
unless you hold him down!
This Toad doesn’t have fangs or claws
to hold that guy’s movement.
What should we do then?!
We’ll use the Transform Jutsu to
change into something that has those!
But with that said…
I’m not particularly good
at transformations.
Huh?
So you will act as my will
and make the Sign!
Whaaaat?!
Time for a combined transformation!
Uh…Okay!
We got to have fangs and claws!
Umm…
Let’s go!
Wait…
Say, w-wait a second…!
F- Fangs and claws… Fangs and claws…
Fangs and claws!
Transform!
Transform Jutsu!
That’s the…!
A cycle of hardship, right?
Inside, we were crying, right?
But the one thing we won't give up
is the dream we've chosen, right?
It's a secondary role,
a role in the shadows
But in reaching for that dream,
let us stay centered,
let us stay true
Over and over,
we hung on without giving up
we kept coming back up
Over and over,
we believed and dreamed
I don’t know about your past,
and my past doesn’t matter either!
I only have people who I must protect.
Hey you with no eyebrows!
Let’s just end this as similar fighters.
I will finish this with my next hit.
This will be, absolutely and totally,
the last one!
Next time:
“Beyond the Limit of Darkness and Light”