Press down hard on the gas
That’s right, there’s no compromise
We'll slip through the night
At the final moment push hard
That's right, all the way to zero,
Until we wipe away the days
Gently open your heart
If you pull it close to you
It will reach you, without a doubt
It will come, closer
Now
We’re speeding through life,
squeezing it for all of its worth
Our feet are tied
But we still keep going farther
Even if I take it back, and grasp it
If you’re not the one
There will be no meaning
And so we’ll go far off into the distance.
I’ll show you there are walls
which effort alone can
never break through.
Sakura Blossoms!
Huh?!
Your Jutsu is indeed fast.
But our Jutsu exceeds that
and is the speed of sound!
Lee!
My left ear...
There’s a little gimmick I have.
Evading won’t work...
on my attacks.
What is he going to do?!
It’s sound.
Even though you evaded my fist,
sound assaulted you.
Sound?
Do you know what sound is
all about in the first place?
Vibration?
Correct. In other words,
hearing sounds means,
that the eardrum is
catching vibrating air.
And the human eardrum breaks
with sounds over 150 Mhz.
Also, by assaulting the semicircular canal
which is located even deeper,
I can make you totally lose balance.
You won’t be able to move your body
freely for sometime.
Something old and tired
like Taijutsu don’t work on us.
Well, you were doing good
up to a certain point,
but I brought forth my Jutsu.
It’s just not gonna work anymore.
I freely manipulate ultrasonic waves
and air pressure,
and have the power to
obliterate even boulders!
Primary Lotus!
I can send air into the ground
and change the dirt into
a cushion as I please.
It’s different from
your silly Jutsu.
Blast it!
Lee, it is all right to use
this Jutsu
to protect someone precious.
Protect... someone precious?
In any case,
I’m impressed that you
were able to master it, little man!
You did it quite well, Lee!
Darn it!
Okay, then!
Next is...
You!
Darn it!
He’s coming!
What?!
No way!
Lee!
Leaf...
Hurricane!
It looks like my earlier attack
is having an effect!
I’m somewhat surprised...
but there’s not even a trace of
that flash of combo Taijutsu you showed!
This arm amplifies sounds
from within to its maximum.
It’s a speaker of sorts!
Lee!
And the assault sound isn’t limited
by the direction of my arm...
it always converges on
the targeted prey by my Chakra!
Lee!
Now then... 					The final blow.
I won’t let you!
Oh, well.
Hey, let’s get outta here!
Those guys are pretty dangerous!
It looks like Sasuke and Naruto
are only unconscious, but...
even that guy Lee’s been
messed up and Sakura’s alone.
What’re you gonna do, Ino?
What do you mean?
Well, Sakura’s in deep trouble!
You’re all right with that?
Huh?!
You two were once close friends,
weren’t you?
By the way...
What Sakura, don’t be so stiff!
Well...
Ino, I hear you also...
What is it?
...like Sasuke.
Then, that means from now on,
you and I are rivals.
Why... why am I recalling things
from that time?
Hey, Ino!
What’re you gonna do?!
I know, but there’s nothing I can do!
I can’t heedlessly
go out there, can I?!
Even if I went out now...
I’d be taken down without a doubt.
I also...
I also...!
Air pressure!
The shurikens got bounced back?!
Your hair’s shinier than mine.
Hey! If you have time to worry
about your hair,
you should practice!
Getting all spiced up like a woman...
Why don’t you kill that Sasuke guy
right in front of this sexy bug, Zaku?
Yeah! That sounds great!
Hey hey...
I won’t let you do such a thing!
Don’t move!
Sakura.
My body... It has no strength.
I...
Again... I’m just pulling everyone’s feet!
I’m always being protected.
It's so frustrating!
This time for sure...
I had thought!
I must protect people precious to me...
so I thought!
So...
Let’s do this!
Hey! Sasuke and Naruto are
gonna get it, too!
W-What should I do?!
That’s pointless!
That won’t work on me!
What are you saying?
Huh?
What?!
I always...
act as if I’m a full-fledged Ninja.
I always say that I like Sasuke.
I always act like I know everything
and lecture Naruto.
I always just... watch them from behind.
And yet...
Tazuna, get back!
Get back!
Now then...
Let’s get wild!
This is the only way to
take him down!
Sasuke!
Here it is!
Those two always covered
my back and fought for me.
Lee, you say that you like me...
I’ll protect you until I die!
Primary Lotus!
With me at your back...
you risked your life and
fought for me.
I have a feeling that you taught me...
Sakura!
Humph!
I want to be like all of you!
This time...
I want all of you...
to watch me...
...from behind!
Sakura?
Sakura...
Kin! Kill her!
Huh! That sign...
Substitution Jutsu!
On the right, huh?
You think I’m a fool?
With such a simple and basic Ninjutsu...
you think you can come at me?!
Kin, get out of the way!
Useless!
Air pressure 100 percent,
ultrasonic waves 0%, output...
Is that all you can do?
Slicing Sound Wave!
You’re easy to spot...
You’re above!
I’ve said it two or three times that
that won’t work!
This is enough... for you!
Where next?
Huh?!
What...?!
This time... it’s not a substitution!
Get off me! Hey!
Sakura...
You’re always being called
“Billboard Brow” and being picked on.
Who’re you?
I’m called Ino Yamanaka.
How ‘bout you?
I’m... Sakura.
Huh? I can’t hear you.
Say it louder.
Sakura Haruno!
Huh, I see.
You have a wide forehead.
So, Billboard Brow, huh...?
That’s why you hide
your forehead with your bangs.
Like a ghost...
Sakura, was it?
Uh-huh...
Come back here tomorrow.
I’ll give you something nice.
Huh?
Darn, let go!
See! You look cuter like this, Sakura!
I’ll give you that ribbon.
T-Thanks.
But...
But what?
My forehead...
You hide it, so people make
more fun of you, you know?!
You have a cute face Sakura,
so you should be more confident!
More confident!
Ino...
Hey, who’s that?
Who’s she, Ino?
Her name’s Sakura.
Hey, say hello!
Hello...
Listen everybody! Listen!
There’s someone I like!
Who do you think it is?
Hurry up and tell us!
Don’t say it’s Sasuke?
Huh? Why’d you know?
What’re you talking about?
Sasuke’s really popular,
he’s the most popular!
Huh? Is that so?
Oh no! I’ll have a lot of rivals.
What should I do?!
Hey, Ino! Sakura’s been upbeat lately!
She’s just acting brave
and romping around!
Ino! I’ve heard Sasuke
likes girls with long hair.
...likes girls with long hair.
Sakura...
I’ve heard you like Sasuke, too, Ino.
From now on, we’re rivals.
Your hair. It’s grown quite a bit.
Ino...
Why...
Why are you on the
same team as Sasuke?!
I will not lose anymore... to you, Ino!
Me too! I won’t lose to you, Sakura.
No matter what!
...Sakura!
I will...
Give it up!
It’s really bad...
Hey, Ino...!
I must... protect everyone!
You punk!
Huh?
Huh! More strange ones.
Ino...?
Sakura! I promised
I wouldn’t lose to you, didn’t I?!
Hey, can you hear it?
The clear, blue sky goes on and on
The ocean spans limitlessly
Please keep that smile on your face forever
Or else I’ll cry
You won't have to search around you
It’s all ok now.
Everyone is inside
this hand
when you want to cry, and you want to run away
When you forget what happiness is
Just sing.
Light is born, and darkness was born
The two are one
Harmonia, feel the telepathy
Hey, can you hear it?
Wow! This is Ino team’s battle?!
What a formation based on calculations!
I hate to admit it,
but they’re strong!
Even the Sound Village ones
would be no match for them!
We’ll protect Sasuke...
Huh?! What’s this feeling?
Next episode: "Battle Formation:
lno-Shika-Cho!"
What in the world is going on?!