Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
The distance created between us
became too big,
because we were always together
Your honest reply, “See you…”
coming from that brash mouth
makes it sadder.
If you are in an unfamiliar town, crying
Then I want to deliver you a smile,
even if I’m not by your side
Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
I can feel it so close,
Our two hearts
This is as far as you go.
Give Matsuri back.
You think you’ve got me cornered now?
Don’t get the wrong idea.
You’re the one who’s been cornered!
What?
Byakugan!
He has the final enemy cornered
in a dead-end valley.
The area around the valley
is eerily calm.
I don’t see his comrades.
Is Shikamaru’s final move finished?
No.
We can’t state definitively that
they’ve reached a deadlock.
It’s because it’s possible that
the battles thus far were diversions.
Just a little more, Lee.
It’ll be over once I connect
two or three more muscles.
Sakura’s Medical Ninja technique
is really becoming…
And yet I…
The treatment is over for now.
How do you fight to get like this?
I’m sorry.
You saved me.
Thank you, Sakura.
You’re welcome.
Oh, you can’t, yet.
As one of the Medical Team members,
I prohibit you from fighting any further.
No, please let me go.
I can’t just leave Gaara like this…
We’re Team Return-the-Favor, after all.
The Ultimate Weapon Reborn
Gaara, you may very well be
called the ultimate weapon,
but have you not used up all of
your sand in the fight earlier?
This is my weapon.
Indeed I have used up almost all
of the sand with Chakra built up inside.
But…
No matter what Jutsu you use,
I must not lose in a one-on-one battle.
There’s nothing scary about
a Shinobi with no weapon!
Come, Infinite Kujaku Armor!
Fang Release: Dark Sword!
Flying Double Edge Sword!
You’ll realize that the likes
of a mere Ninja
is no match for the Ninja tools
created by us artisans.
Fang Release: Dark Sword!
It seems your own body’s Chakra
has run out.
You’re carrying
a monster inside you, right?
Now, isn’t it about time
you used the power of Shukaku?
You okay?
Gaara Sensei is…
Yeah, I know.
Listen up.
You hide in a safe place somewhere.
Right.
Although Gaara received
Sakura’s treatment, he's still…
That’s as far as you go,
ultimate weapon of the Sand Village!
Damn it.
Use the power of the Shukaku already.
Hey!
Hold it!
Who are you?
I’ll be your opponent from here on.
You’re in the way, boy.
Kujaku Hurricane!
Damn it!
Leaf Shinobi, you watch.
The era of control by
the Five Great Nations will end.
No, it won’t be just that.
If the ultimate Ninja tool created by
the Artisan Village is completed,
the existence of the Ninja
will no longer be necessary.
What’re you talking about?!
We are people from the Village
of Artisans who for many years
have equally shared
exceptional Ninja tools
with you in the Five Great Nations.
However, each time relations
worsened between fellow villages,
the Village of Artisans would be attacked
over fear of Ninja tools crossing
over to the other village.
You Ninja of the Five Great Nations
have forgotten
that you are kept alive by our power,
and have returned the favor
with vengeance time and again.
Although we the people of
the Village of Artisans have advanced skills,
we have had to survive by currying favor
from the Five Great Nations!
However, that era will now end!
First, I will take out the Leaf Village.
Fang Release Dark Sword!
How long can you run away for?
I’ll stake you like a shrike!
What?!
You!
Gaara Sensei!
Gaara Sensei’s sand
protected the Leaf Ninja.
That dome created with hard minerals
in the ground mixed with sand…
can’t be smashed by such junk.
I’ll protect him until the end…
with my power!
Gaara Sensei!
Don’t make me laugh!
You, who are called the greatest creation
of the Sand, a terrifying weapon,
are going to protect someone else?
And you’re going to use
what little Chakra you have left
for the sake of a comrade?
But that will be your death!
Gaara Sensei!
With this,
all preparations are complete.
Damn it.
Oh!
Gaara!
We were contacted by someone
from the Village of Artisans.
It seems ones calling themselves
the Four Celestials,
bearing long-withstanding hostilities
against the Five Great Nations…
have completed forbidden research and
are attempting to resurrect
the ultimate weapon of folklore
in the village.
It seems the villagers got
wind of the crisis
and have evacuated to
a different location.
I see. So that’s why the village
was completely empty.
So what exactly is this ultimate weapon?
The resurrection of Seimei,
the founder of the Village of Artisans.
Seimei?!
Are you saying
they’re trying to raise the dead?!
I see. It makes sense that
the mausoleum was violated.
As for us, we must prevent
the resurrection
of the ultimate weapon at all costs.
I understand. I’ll be off.
Oh, hold on.
Yes?
I’ll be having one more person
accompany you on this mission.
What? Who would that be?
What we wanted was
the Shukaku’s Chakra.
What did you say?
How we’ve waited for this time.
Now Gaara, turn into the Shukaku now.
And infuse me with that power.
Gaara!
I’ll save you now.
Naruto!
Matsuri, take this.
My rope javelin.
The optic nerves have connected…
Open…
third eye!
Hey, you.
What the heck do you intend to start?
I’ll show you.
The ultimate Ninja tool created
by Lord Seimei,
the founder of our Village of Artisans.
Ultimate Ninja tool?
Now is the time of its completion.
Gaara!
Oh, Lord Seimei.
Please take possession of my flesh
and complete your resurrection!
Oh!
What’s going on? He vanished.
The dead body came back to life!
My name is Seimei.
The founder of the Village of Artisans.
A hundred years have passed and
I have now been resurrected
as the ultimate Ninja tool
of the Village of Artisans!
What in the world is happening here?!
My long-awaited wish has at last
come to fruition.
With this, my Village of Artisans will reign
over the Shinobi apex.
I see…
So the monster from the Sand Village
became the source of my power.
Say what?
Hoko said this.
There is a monster lying
within the body
of the one called Gaara
from the Sand Village.
Once that person is in a cage,
soon he will become
a complete monster, the Shukaku.
I will take away what you could
consider infinite Chakra from the Shukaku.
I won’t let you do that!
Damn it!
Just wait, Gaara.
I’ll get you out now.
What a waste…
Vortex Wind.
I’m just getting started!
What a fool!
I’ll get you out now!
Damn it, damn it!
Gaara! Can you hear my voice?!
Gaara, answer me!
What’s going on in there?!
Gaara!
N-Naruto…
Shikamaru!
What?
Where are Gaara and Naruto?
Neji, Hinata, tell me the situation.
There’s a cage behind an area
surrounded by rocks…
There’s a massive amount of Chakra
being extracted from there.
Gaara must be inside.
Hey, Shikamaru!
What?
You know there’s a terrifying power
lying dormant inside Gaara, right?
Yeah, generally.
Something terrible will happen…
if Gaara has Chakra extracted like this
and he loses himself!
The Shukaku that had been kept
under control will go out of control.
Once it starts going berserk,
there will be no way to stop Gaara.
For real?
I must not waste any more time.
The entertainment ends here.
Hot-hot-hot-hot.
Damn it! Just wait, Gaara!
I’ll get you out now!
You’re a pest!
Give it up already!
I’m just getting started!
Solid Blanks!
Oh, how I have waited for this time.
Now, Shukaku! Give me power!
I feel it. This is an amazing power!
Cut out the futile resistance.
The power of the Shukaku
is already mine!
I declare war on the Five Great Nations.
The Shinobi in the Five Great Nations
who made light of the Artisan Shinobi
will fully realize the 100-year grudge
of the Artisan Ninja.
And they will inevitably
become our sacrifices.
Knock it off!
What?!
We won’t hand over our power
to the likes of you.
I won’t let you take away any more
of Gaara’s Chakra.
You got that?!
How can that person fight
while getting that beaten up?
Why do you go this far, kid?
What is the monster of
the Sand Village to you?
Gaara…
Gaara is an important comrade to me!
He said he fights for
those important to him.
Fights for someone important.
Very well. Then die!
What’re you doing, little girl?
I finally figured out what
Gaara Sensei taught me.
Weapons took away the lives
of my mother and father.
But I can also protect those important
to me with a weapon!
Foolishness.
Damn it!
It has finally begun, huh…?
Gaara Sensei…
Gaara!
Gaara.
The Key to the rusted heart’s door
Will always be smiling right near by
Even if rains of spears were to fall,
I will run through it
Because I want to find the joy
without a shape
This big dream of mine that
cannot be translated to words,
I will make it come true,
even if it were to deepen my wounds
We stand here today because of
what we believed through,
That is why I will continue running forward,
never looking away
Even if I’m told that
there is no bright future
I’ll change it right away,
lighting it with all my feeling
The wind is probably testing our hearts
In my heart, I gently grasped my hands
You are probably searching for
the answer to your tears
Your dream is always waiting near by,
with the answers in its hands
The Key to the rusted heart’s door
Will always be smiling right near by
Hey, that’s…
– We were too late.
– Then, you mean…
Yes. He is starting to transform
to Shukaku.
Damn! What should we do?
This is bad.
lf Gaara loses his conscious in that state,
the true Shukaku will come out.
When that happens
he won’t know a foe from friend,
he will just destroy everything.
All we can do is just stand here
and watch?!
Next time: “Departure”