C'mon!
Running like a fugitive,
Being chased by something
Inside my heart is pounding
My throat dry like it's withering
For no single one,
To none does belong,
This time is ours, right now...
Unraveling the pain,
Unraveling our hearts,
Unraveling shadows
Stifling our breath,
Reaching for beyond,
Tearing through the dark
In fighting and in love
To the distant light above,
Yes, we are on the way
I wanna rock...
Rockin' my heart
Such intensity...
If I take a breath or move my eyes
I will be marked and killed –
that's what I'm feeling..
If I'm stuck like this for an hour,
I'll go mad.
Facing a Jonin intent to kill…
This sensation is like having
my life held in limbo...
No way! I'd rather die
to escape this feeling!
Sasuke...
Don't worry. I'll protect
you all with my life.
I absolutely won't allow
my comrades to get killed.
I don't know about that...
It's over.
Sensei! Behind you!!
Die!!
The Water Clone Jutsu...?
It can't be.
Don't move!
The Oath of Pain
It's over.
W-Wow!!
Did you say it's over?
You don't understand, do you?
You won't be able to beat me
just by making like a monkey…
No chance.
But, I must say you're good.
My Water Clone Jutsu was
being copied at that point…
I absolutely won't allow
my comrades to get killed.
By letting the clone talk as if it were you,
you succeeded in distracting me.
And you used Hidden Mist Jutsu
to hide yourself to see what I was doing…
But…
I'm not a fool.
That one was a fake too!
Now!
Makibishi spikes…!
How foolish...!
Sensei!
Oh, I can't believe that
Kakashi Sensei got …
kicked away like that….
His Taijutsu skills are also
extremely good.
W-What's with this water...?
lt's awfully heavy.
Humph... Fool!
It's the Water Prison Jutsu!
Darn it.
My temporary escape
into the water…
was a huge mistake!
You're caught…
It's a special prison that makes
it impossible for you to escape!
It makes things harder
having you able to act.
Now…Kakashi.
I'll have to settle things
with you later.
First, I will finish those guys off.
Water Clone Jutsu…
Didn't expect this level of skill…
You're acting big,
wearing a headband like a Ninja…
But…a real Ninja is one
who has hovered between
life and death numerous times.
In other words,
only those who are worth being listed
in my Bingo Book
deserve to be called Ninja.
Guys like you can't be
called real Ninja.
He's disappeared again!
You're just a kid!
Naruto!
You three! Take Tazuna and run!
You have no chance
against this guy!
As long as he has me trapped
in this Water Prison,
he won't be able
to move from here.
And he shouldn't be able to use
the Water Clone Jutsu
if he's far enough away
from his real body.
In any case, just run for now!
Run away?
You've got to be kidding me.
That option was gone
from the moment you got caught.
Even if we ran,
without you, sooner or later
we'd be defeated by Zabuza…
and we'd all be destroyed.
Even if we were to reform
the Manji defense,
it would be impossible
to block his attacks.
In the end…
we'll have...
no options left.
In order for us to survive,
our only option is to rescue you.
We'll just have to do it!
There…!
Too easy.
Sasuke!
Sasuke…
T-This is the Jonin level…
A real Ninja…
We've got to run…
At this rate…
Seriously…! Seriously…!
We'll be killed!!
I'm going to swear on
the pain of my left hand!
I'll never get into another situation
from which I'll have to be rescued…
I'll never be afraid or
be a coward.
Are you hurt…scaredy cat?
I won't lose to Sasuke.
Can I borrow that
Leaf headband for a while?
This?
This is worn only by those who have
graduated from Ninja Academy.
Naruto, come over here.
I'd like to give you something.
Congratulations on your graduation.
That's because you're
all squirts
who don't have the qualifications
to become Ninjas.
Missions are all risky assignments.
You pass!
I'm not that little prankster
that you think I am!
I'm going to surpass the Hokage!
And so I'm going to get
the entire Village
to acknowledge my existence!
That's right…
I am a Ninja now. And...
I decided that I was not going
to run anymore!
That I wouldn't run away…!
Y-You fool! Stop it!
Oh, Naruto! What are you thinking?!
Humph! Fool...
What are you thinking…
charging off on your own?!
Even Sasuke is no match for him…
No matter how hard we try,
we Genin are no match for him…
Huh...?!
The headband….?!
Hey! You, with no brows...
Record in your Bingo Book…
about the man who will one day
become the Leaf Village's Hokage.
Leaf-style Ninja…
Naruto Uzumaki!!
Naruto…
When I first saw that little kid,
he seemed so unreliable…
Sasuke! Lend me your ear!
What is it?
I have a plan.
You want to discuss plans
under these circumstances…?
This guy...!
Humph!
You are talking of teamwork?
W-What is this feeling…?
Was Naruto so…?
Now...
Let's get wild…
Now, let's get wild!
Such loud snorting,
but do you have a winning plan?
T-This isn't good…
What are you guys doing!
I told you to run!
It was obvious what was going to happen
once I was caught!
Hurry! Run!
Listen to me!
Our mission is to protect Tazuna!
Have you forgotten that?!
Old man….
Well...
This is a seed that I planted…
I can't say that
I want my life to be spared.
Sorry, you guys…
Fight as much as you want!
You hear that?
Are you ready?
You guys really haven't learned
anything, have you?
W-What?!
You're still playing at being Ninja?
When I was your age,
this hand was already
stained red with blood!
Zabuza, the Demon!
Ohh…? It seems that
you've heard of me.
A long time ago, in the Mist Village,
often called the town of Blood Mist,
Ninja candidates faced
their biggest hurdle.
So you also know about
that graduation exam…
That graduation exam?
What is it...?
This graduation exam
that you're talking about...
The students killed each other.
What….?
Classmates who had shared rice
from the same pot
formed pairs and tried
to kill each other.
It didn't end
until one of them died.
Partners who used to talk about
each other's dreams and aspirations…
How cruel…
Ten years ago,
the Mist Village's graduation exam
was forced to undergo drastic reform.
That was because an evil demon
had appeared on the scene the previous year.
Reform?
What about the reform?
What had that evil demon done?
With no scruples or hesitation…
a young boy who didn't even have
the qualifications for being a Ninja,
annihilated over a hundred examinees.
That sure was…fun…
Sasuke!
Die!
Darn!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Ah... Shadow Clone Jutsu,
and there are quite a few of them.
Here I go!
It's impossible, after all…
There is no way that
you can defeat the guy!
There is only one way left
to defeat this guy!
Sasuke!
I see!
So that's your plan, Naruto!
That's pretty good for you!
Demon Wind Shuriken,
Windmill of Shadows…
A Shuriken won't work on me.
I see. This time
it's aiming for my real body…
But...
It's not so easy!
A Shuriken in
the Shuriken's shadow...!
This is...
The Shadow Shuriken Jutsu!
A second Shuriken
in his blind spot!
But...
Still too naïve...
He dodged it!!
Here it is!
Yes! The plan worked!!
That Zabuza had no clue
as to what I was thinking,
and I fooled him!
Ninja must be able
to see through the obvious.
Did you see that – the Leaf-style fighting
of Naruto Uzumaki?!
Kakashi Sensei,
the rest is up to you.
Next episode:
"Kakashi, Sharingan Warrior!"
I'm going to kick butt once again!