C'mon!
Running like a fugitive,
Being chased by something
Inside my heart is pounding
My throat dry like it's withering
For no single one,
To none does belong,
This time is ours, right now...
Unraveling the pain,
Unraveling our hearts,
Unraveling shadows
Stifling our breath,
Reaching for beyond,
Tearing through the dark
In fighting and in love
To the distant light above,
Yes, we are on the way
I wanna rock...
Rockin' my heart
This is quite some fog.
I can't see ahead.
The bridge should be visible soon.
When we reach the side of the bridge,
we'll be in the Land of the Waves.
Wooow! 					 It's huge!
H-Hey! 					Please keep it down.
I took this boat out under cover of fog.
And I cut the engine
and am rowing by hand.
If they find us,
we'll be in deep trouble.
Mr. Tazuna.
I want to ask you something
before we arrive at the pier.
The identity of your assailants,
and the reason why they are after you.
If you don't tell us…
our mission may end
when you make landfall.
The Assassin of the Mist
It appears I have no choice
but to tell you.
Frankly, I'd like you to listen.
Just as you said,
this may be beyond
the scope of your mission.
Actually, I am being targeted
by a terrifying man.
A terrifying man?
Who?
You guys have probably heard at
least his name before.
A shipping magnate
by the name of Gato.
What? Gato…of the Gato Company?
One of the world's richest men?
Who? What?
Yes…
On the surface, he's the chief executive
of a shipping company…
But underneath,
he is into drug-trafficking
and deals in contraband
using gangs and Ninjas.
Moreover, he runs a despicable business,
ruthlessly taking over nations
and enterprises.
It was about one year ago…
when that man first set his eyes on
the Land of the Waves…
He used his wealth and violence
to enter this country,
and before anyone knew it,
he had taken complete control of the island's
maritime transportation and shipping.
Having a tight grip on the ocean, in an
island nation like the Land of the Waves,
means having control of finance,
the government, the people... everything.
The one thing Gato fears...
is the completion of the bridge...
that has been under construction
for some time now.
I see.
Since you're the one building the bridge,
you've become a hindrance.
Then, those Ninjas from before
were Gato's men…?
But I don't understand.
Your opponent is a dangerous one,
who will even use Ninja.
Why did you hide that fact from us
when you made your request?
The Land of the Waves…
is a very poor nation,
and even feudal lords have no money.
Of course, we ordinary citizens
have no money either.
We cannot afford to make requests of
Rank B or higher...
Well, if you pull out
of the mission when I land ashore,
I will, no doubt, be killed.
Killed sometime before I make it home.
But there's no need for concern!
Should I die, my cute grandchild
who will turn eight...
will only cry his heart out!
Oh!
And... my daughter will only blame
the Hidden Leaves Ninja
for the rest of her life
and grieve in solitude!
Oh, it's not your fault at all!
Well...
I guess we have no choice.
Let's continue as his bodyguards.
Oh! I am most grateful!
I won!
We'll be arriving soon.
Tazuna.
It appears we haven't been noticed
up until this point…
Thanks.
This is as far as I go.
See you around.
Yeah. You've been a big help.
Be careful.
Okay!
Get me home safely.
Right.
When they next attack,
it won't be Chunin, but elite level Jonin.
Cripes!
I won't let this guy do
all the fun stuff anymore!
There!
Heh… Just a mouse.
Quit trying to show off!
There was nothing there
in the first place!
Please, Naruto.
Don't use Kunai Knives recklessly.
They're really dangerous.
Hey brat!
Don't be doing anything confusing!
Huh? I sense a presence there!
No, over here?!
There!
Stop it, already!
S-Someone's really been targeting us
the whole time!
Yeah right!
Knock it off, you!
Naruto!
What have you done?!
It's a bunny!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to…
I'm sorry, bunny.
It's just a rabbit, eh.
That's a snow rabbit.
But that doesn't explain
its fur color...
The coat turns white only during winter
when there is little sunlight.
Which means...
that snow rabbit was raised indoors
without sunlight to be used as a substitution.
Guess they're already here…
I'm sorry…
I see… The Demon Brothers wouldn't
be enough to take on these guys.
The Copy Ninja from the
Village of the Hidden Leaves.
"Sharingan" Kakashi is with them…
Everyone, get down!
If I'm not mistaken, he's…
Here we go!
Here we go, here we go,
here we go!
I'm going to do it this time.
I won't lose to Sasuke!
Well, well.
If it isn't the Rogue Ninja
of the Hidden Mist, Zabuza Momochi!
Rogue Ninja? Whatever.
What's important now is…
Ready…
Go!
You're in the way.
Get back, you guys.
Why?!
He's on a totally different level from
the guys from the other day.
His being our opponent means…
Huh?
Oh.
that things might be tricky
as I am now.
I assume you are Kakashi,
the Sharingan user…
Sorry, but…
I'll have you hand over the old man.
Huh? Huh? Sharingan?
What's that?
What? What is he talking about?
Is this guy strong?
Sharingan…
Get in Manji battle formation, you guys.
Protect Tazuna…
Don't involve yourselves in the fight.
Huh?
That's the teamwork
in this situation.
Huh?!
Fight me.
W-What's this eye…?
Well now...
I never expected to see
the rumored Sharingan this soon…
This is an honor.
Everyone's been saying Sharingan...
What is it?!
…Sharingan.
Power that the light of the eye generates,
and the pupil emanates.
The user of
the so-called Visual Jutsu (Art)
is said to possess the vision to see through
all Genjutsu (Illusionary Art),
Taijutsu (Physical Art),
and Ninjutsu (Ninja Art),
and is able to deflect them.
The Sharingan is a type of eye
that is unique
to the user of the Visual Art.
However, that is not the only power of
the Sharingan.
Well said.
That is not all.
What's more frightening is that
such an eye
can assess an opponent's techniques
and copy them.
When I was in the Anbu Black Ops
of the Hidden Mist,
search information
about you was in the Bingo Book
I would carry around with me.
There was also something
else in the book...
About the man who has copied
over one thousand skills…
Kakashi the Copy Ninja.
What? Kakashi Sensei
is that incredible a Ninja?
W-Wow!
What does this mean?
The Sharingan…is a special trait
that appears in only a select few
even among the Uchiha clan.
Could it be, that this guy…
Let's end the talking here.
I must kill that old man immediately.
But, Kakashi, it seems
I have to defeat you first.
Over there!
And he's even on the water?
He's building up quite a bit of Chakra!
Ninja Art, Hidden Mist Jutsu.
He's vanished?!
Sensei!
He'll probably come to erase me first…
What is he?
Zabuza Momochi.
He's a Anbu Black Ops member
in the Hidden Mist and
is known as "the silent killing"
technique expert.
S-Silen...?
As the name suggests…
it's a killing skill that's implemented
in an instant in silence.
By the time you realize it,
it's possible you may find yourself
in the afterlife.
I haven't totally mastered
the use of my Sharingan.
So don't lower your guard, you guys.
Well, if we fail, we'll only die.
How can you be so carefree?!
The mist is steadily getting thicker!
The Land of the Waves
is surrounded by ocean.
So mist rises very easily.
Sensei!
Eight spots.
Huh? What?
The larynx, the spine,
the lungs, the liver...
The jugular and the subclavian veins.
The kidneys, the heart.
Now then, which vulnerable spot
would be good?
What an intense thirst for blood!
If I take even one breath,
or move my eyes,
I will be marked and killed -
that's what I'm feeling.
If I'm stuck like this for an hour,
I'll go mad!
Facing a Jonin's intent to kill…
This sensation is like having
my life being held in limbo…
No way! I'd rather die
to escape this feeling!
Sasuke.
Don't worry.
I'll protect you with my life.
I will not allow
my comrades to get killed.
I wonder about that...
It's over.
Sensei! 					Behind you!
Die!
The Water Clone Jutsu?
It can't be!
In this mist…
did he actually copy me?
Don't move.
It's over.
O-Oh no!
Even Kakashi Sensei fell under
Zabuza's Jutsu.
I've got to escape.
I'll get killed, for real.
This pain.
What am I doing?!
I'd decided, hadn't I?
Not to run away no matter what happens.
Next episode:
"The Oath of Pain!"
I'm going to kick butt once again!