Gaara.
Kankuro.
Primary Lotus!
Damn it! Can’t hold any further.
You can’t even howl like a loser?
Die!
You’re mine!
Don't you be smiling
before you're going to die!
What?!
Who’re you?!
Heh… It seems
you’re an ally this time…
Who are you?!
A Sand…
…Shinobi…
…ally of the Leaf!
Well, be careful going home.
Okay.
If something happens again,
I’ll come to your rescue again…
Just let me know, crybaby.
You always say too much.
That’s why girls are…
I’ll return the favor twice the amount
from that time.
Hey, Shikamaru.
What’s the matter?
We’ll stand by here for a while.
Stand by?
We don’t have time fooling around
in a place like this!
Be quiet for a second, Naruto.
That’s right.
Shikamaru’s got a proper plan.
Right, right.  Naruto, you have to
be sure to obey the leader.
Fine.
Shino, I’m counting on you.
Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
The distance created between us
became too big,
because we were always together
Your honest reply, “See you…”
coming from that brash mouth
makes it sadder.
If you are in an unfamiliar town, crying
Then I want to deliver you a smile,
even if I’m not by your side
Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
I can feel it so close,
Our two hearts
Sand Alliance with the Leaf Shinobi
So, Kujaku? What’s going on
with our pursuers?
Yeah, we went to the trouble of
leaving footprints as we go.
We need them to follow.
It’ll be okay. They’ll be within
firing range immediately!
There are three pursuers.
One of them is Gaara!
As for the extra two, we'll leave one
for each respectively
and deal with them with
One Shinobi, One Kill…
I’ll isolate Gaara and drive him into
the Reverse Scale Position.
I’ll take the first person.
All right, go.
It's not necessary to drive him
into the Reverse Scale Position.
There are only three of them.
I can handle them by myself.
Flying Kujaku Double Edge Sword:
Whirlwind!
What?!
What is this?
A wind user, huh?
Interesting!
– Splendid.
– Not bad, Temari.
Naturally.
Not half bad.
To think you’d blow away my Whirlwind.
What, you’re still just a kid?
– You guys go on ahead.
– What?
Hey, Temari. You okay with this?
Will you be okay?
Well, we’re fellow wind users.
I should be able to handle her alone.
Hurry, Gaara.
She’s your student, right?
Thanks.
– I’m counting on you.
– Be careful.
Right.
You won’t get away.
I’m your opponent.
Cyclone Scythe Jutsu.
Wind Slash.
This wind is…
These double swords alter the wind
at my will to suit the attacks
and amplify the power to the extreme.
It’s too late to regret.
I only need a little bit of Chakra
as long as I have these swords.
How long can you pesevere with
the limited Chakra you have?
How about testing that out?
Matsuri.
We caught up.
Where are we?
So you’re awake?
Heh. You’re like prey plunged on
a branch by a shrike.
You’re the bait to lure him out.
What?
Gaara Sensei.
Dragon Eye: Fang Release: Dark Sword.
What?
Darn it.
Did you see that? This is the Dragon Eye:
Fang Release: Dark Sword.
You’re just a kid!
I see.
It’s an adjustable sword with daggers
connected by an iron wire
going through the center.
Like a Bamboo Snake?
How nostalgic.
I used one a lot with puppet games
when I was a kid.
It can look like a living snake
depending on how it’s controlled.
But there’s no point
once it’s been identified.
Though we both use Puppets,
compared to mine, it’s just a kid’s toy.
Go, Gaara.
Can I leave it to you?
Yeah. I don’t need your help for this.
I’ll catch up right away.
I’m counting on you.
Now, bring it on. I’ll play with you.
What’re you doing acting tough?
You’ll die if you take me lightly!
That goes for you!
Then die, Kabuki makeup jerk!
Here I go.
That’s no good.
Come on, that was too easy.
Too bad. This sword
isn’t just an adjustable sword.
The sword itself amplifies Chakra
in response to my Chakra
and changes into the form of a dragon.
Gaara, I’m sorry.
This might take a little time.
Suiko, you ambush him here.
Draw him into
the Reverse Scale Position. Got it?
Yeah…
You won’t get through here.
Gaara, fight me.
Very well.
Bring it.
Hey, Shikamaru. How long are we
going to stay like this?
Shut up. There are many difficulties
with ambushes.
Right now, Shino, Neji and Hinata
are taking on those difficulties for us.
What? They are?
Did you find them?
Byakugan!
In that direction, right?
Got it. There are three battle areas.
It’s the scent bag of
the female Parasitic Insects.
With this, the insects will find you
no matter where you go.
Right. I’m counting on you, Shino.
Then, we’ll be going on ahead.
Be careful!
Oh, information has arrived.
I was getting sick of waiting!
All right, I’m counting on you guys.
This is bad.
lt’s already begun.
All right, Kiba and Choji,
you take the western forest.
Ino and I will take the northeastern hills.
Naruto and Lee, you take
the northwestern forest.
We’ll take on back-up
in two-man cells.
Now then, let’s begin
the favor-returning operation.
– Right. 					– Right.
I was waiting for this time!
Scatter.
What is it?
Hold up.
If the guys who are fleeing will take on
pursuers with One Shinobi, One Kill,
the battle area not being
a straight line means…
Could it be a Barrier?
What?
Just to be safe.
That should do it. Let’s go.
Right.
Now, there’s nowhere left to hide.
What will you do?
To think she’d evade all of my attacks.
Since it’s come to this, I’ve just got to
use that technique!
Wind Style: Sea Dragon!
What’s that? Nothing’s happening.
How pitiful. It seems the wind
doesn’t like you.
I don’t know about that.
The wind is my friend.
This battle is just starting.
Wind Reversal!
Die!
Darn it! Hey, let go!
Done already? I thought
we could play a little more…
That’s the spirit!
What kind of toy is it this time?
That’s funny. You think you can
defeat me with junk like this?
The junk is your sword.
What?! A three-headed dragon!
You’re just quick to escape, eh?
Darn it.
Sure enough,
Crow is at a disadvantage
unless teamed up with Black Ant.
Not bad, Gaara of the desert.
How much Chakra is built up
in that sand?
You want to test that out?
However…
It’ll be in exchange for your life.
Sand Coffin!
Impossible.
That’s a nice sand bath.
You, the sand’s Chakra…
Exactly. This armor sucks up Chakra.
Aw, is this good night?
Just sleep as is! For all eternity!!
What?!
That was a close shave,
but Shadow Possession Jutsu
was a success!
Die already!
Uh, oh!
What?
You guys.
Who are you?
Who are you guys?
– An ally of the Sand.
– Leaf Shinobi.
– Leaf Shinobi
Believe it!
He’s not here!
– They're further ahead.
– Right!
Guys, fight as much as you want.
I don’t see any Chakra abnormalities
in the basin…
There’s no Barrier.
Good luck, guys.
I’ll protect you.
Gaara Sensei.
Just wait, Gaara!
We’ll return the favor, no matter what.
The Key to the rusted heart’s door
Will always be smiling right near by
Even if rains of spears were to fall,
I will run through it
Because I want to find the joy
without a shape
This big dream of mine that
cannot be translated to words,
I will make it come true,
even if it were to deepen my wounds
We stand here today because of
what we believed through,
That is why I will continue running forward,
never looking away
Even if I’m told that
there is no bright future
I’ll change it right away,
lighting it with all my feeling
The wind is probably testing our hearts
In my heart, I gently grasped my hands
You are probably searching for
the answer to your tears
Your dream is always waiting near by,
with the answers in its hands
The Key to the rusted heart’s door
Will always be smiling right near by
Damn it.
This was their aim from the start.
To think they would take advantage
of the terrain.
Damn. At this rate,
Gaara will be in danger.
That’s been said,
we can’t move from here.
Please hurry, Naruto, Lee.
You two are the only ones
who can help Gaara now.
Next time:
“Sealed Sand: the Counterattack!”