Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
The distance created between us
became too big,
because we were always together
Your honest reply, “See you…”
coming from that brash mouth
makes it sadder.
If you are in an unfamiliar town, crying
Then I want to deliver you a smile,
even if I’m not by your side
Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
I can feel it so close,
Our two hearts
A Past to Be Erased
That mark…
I saw the same one on the guys
that attacked this village!
That’s a lie!
It’s not a lie! This mark…
Same from that night…
N-No! Spare me!
Stop!
This is the same mark from
that time.
No way!
But this wasn’t in
the medical team’s report.
Byakugan!
It seems this is a particular mark
that only emerges
when he sweats…
You guys get out!
Why?
I’m going to take care of him.
Say what?! I won’t let you do that!
Why do you protect him?
ls the Leaf Village also in cahoots?
No, that’s not it!
He doesn’t remember
a thing from the past…
He has no memory.
No memory?
It’s memory loss.
We came in search of his memory.
Then you should know now.
He’s a dirty bandit!
Whether or not he has a memory
makes no difference to me!
Calm down!
It would only be in vain
to kill someone
who has no memory of
committing a crime.
Shut up!
If you really want to have
your revenge,
do so as much as you like
after getting his memory back…
I won’t stop you at that time.
I won’t let you do that even if
he gets his memory back!
It’s as Neji says.
We’ll also find out the identity
of the guys who attacked
if his memory returns
and we get him to talk.
We might be able to save the village
if we can use him to cut a deal…
We have to keep him alive now.
We won’t run away or hide!
Keep quiet… He won’t let Menma live
unless we tell him this.
I’m going to sew up the wound.
Hold his arms and legs.
That girl is…
I just can’t believe it.
He’s the embodiment of good nature…
To think he’d be a comrade
of the bandits.
I wonder if he became a good guy
after losing his memory.
He just has the same mark as those guys
due to some sort of circumstance.
Even if he lost his memory,
he wouldn’t become this good-natured
of a guy if he was a bad person.
Either way, we’ll know everything
if he get his memory back.
I was…a comrade of the bandits,
wasn’t I?
You heard us talking earlier?
Don’t worry about it.
We don’t know any of the details. Okay?
Heal that wound for now…
I’m going to have
a look around the area.
You understand, right?
Your friends and that guy will die
if you try anything funny.
Do as you like when that happens.
It’s done…
Fuki…
You heard, didn’t you?
I can’t stand it, after all!
Let’s get him. Let’s avenge everyone!
Stop!
It’s still not certain that
Menma’s one of their comrades!
You’re just as much to blame
if you protect him!
– Right! 					– Right!
What’s the ruckus?!
Naruto?
Tenten…!
Why did you let him out of the hut?!
Sorry. I dozed off…
I got careless thinking
he couldn’t move…
Guys, stop! He has no memory!
So he doesn’t even know if
he’s one of their comrades or not…!
We warned you before!
You guys are just as much to blame
if you protect him any further!
Get them!
Stop it!
We should get away for now!
I’m…fine…
What?
Of course, everyone’s angry.
I…should be punished.
You’ll be killed!
That’s fine!
What’re you saying, Menma?!
Byakugan!
It’s them!
The bridge! Raise the bridge!
Right!
Got it!
Be careful of the Leaf Ninja and
secure an entrance route!
– Yes, sir! 					– Yes, sir!
Now’s our chance.
Everyone hide!
You, too!
We can take care of this ourselves!
Come on, Fuki!
They’ve come from two spots!
Where’d they go?!
They vanished.
Be quiet!
The wind…
I get it.
They’ve trapped us
in a Genjutsu
with a different tone mixed in
with the sound of the wind!
Be careful!
We’re now inside their Jutsu!
You noticed too late!
M-My body…
It’s heavy…
This is bad… Is it Paralysis?!
Canceling Sound!
The Paralysis is released.
You backstabber!
Here they come!
I’ll leave those guys to you!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
It’s futile!
Heh, what’s the matter?
Finished already?!
I don’t even have a scratch on me…
This is what I was after!
Wha--?!
What’s happening?
I’m getting an amazing power.
Here I go!
Rotation!
Now, prepare yourself!
You won’t get away!
Here…
This is precious to you, right?
Behind you!
You jerk!
Your voice… It’s back!
Th-Thank you…
Now, let’s go back to the others.
Right.
Menma! You okay?
Yeah…
We took care of most of them!
What about their leader?
What about Shiin?!
I chased after him,
but he got away…
This is bad…
Now that Shiin knows the villagers
won’t abandon their homes and get out,
he’ll use his last resort.
There is a dam built upriver to secure
water resources during a drought.
There is enough water for the village
to last a year, even if it doesn’t rain.
The dam has been rigged to blow up
and to sweep away
the entire village with a flood.
All they care about
is the mine.
We can’t stop something like a flood
unless we move mountains
or something!
Mountains…
That’s it.
We should move mountains!
Naruto! Take me to the mine.
Wha--?
There should be a bunch of
Letter Bombs in the mine!
Letter Bombs?!
What’re you going to do with those?!
I’m going to blow up
the mine itself.
The crumbled dirt and sand will
fill up the valley
and the flood can be stopped.
Damn it! He’s started!
Let’s hurry, Menma!
Naruto… There’s something
I have to tell you.
Make it later!
I haven’t lost my memory.
Yeah… But stopping
the flood comes first!
No, I’d like you to listen now.
I lost my parents when I was little
and was raised in Shiin’s clan.
They were a small Shinobi clan even
in the Land of Rice Paddies.
But they still had ambitious plans…
However, a Shinobi village was created
in the Land of Rice Paddies
about a year ago.
It was the Village Hidden in the Sound.
The Village Hidden in the Sound!
Clan members confident in their skill
drifted over to Hidden Sound Village
one after another.
Eventually jobs from
the feudal lord stopped coming.
Shiin the leader of the clan that
had lost its means of livelihood
set his eyes on the mine in this village…
The plan was to just threaten
and chase off the villagers.
But I encountered
unexpected resistance,
and I got scared and tried to escape…
What’re you hesitating for?
Hurry up and take care of him.
Father! Father!
Stop it!
You… You jerk!
Look out!
I’m a member of a clan that
has committed crimes.
It would’ve been better if
I’d just died like that…
How easy things would’ve been
if I could’ve died then…
I got scared thinking about
the villagers who died…
I wanted to forget.
And so I cowardly escaped into
a Jutsu passed down through the clan
that erases memory.
However, the Jutsu didn’t work
very well…
I only temporarily lost my memory
and it came back in a few hours.
Then you had your memory
the whole time?!
I’m sorry…
Knock it off!
Then why didn’t you tell me about
that honestly from the start?!
If you had, it would’ve been…
I didn’t have the courage to make
the crimes of the clan public.
But I thought the clan must
not commit any further crimes.
So I pretended to lose
my memory.
And to prevent the clan from
adding to their crimes…
I wanted to bring some of you
Leaf Shinobi here
and have you help out.
I knew of Shiin’s next plan.
There must not be any
more village casualties.
Stopping that is my duty
for having survived.
Duty…?
I needed the help
of the Leaf Shinobi
before Shiin could
execute his next plan…
I wanted to round them all up
during the attack earlier.
But since things have come this far,
I’ll stop the flood.
Thanks, Naruto…
I leave Shiin to you.
Find and stop him, no matter what.
You… This…?
This is goodbye.
Somebody has to blow up
the Letter Bombs inside…
If you do that, you’ll…!
Thanks to you, my life has
taken on more meaning…
What’s that sound?
There are intermittent explosions
occurring upriver…
The village will be engulfed in
a mudslide if the dam breaks!
No…!
Neji…
It’s coming!
Goodbye…
Naruto…
Menma!
Wh-What happened…?
It seems the crumbled mountain
stopped the mudslide…
Then, that means the village is saved?
Yeah…
– Thank goodness!
– That’s a relief…
H-How can that be?!
Menma!!
That jerk…!
He won’t get away!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Hold it!
Interfering with our plan!
You think such a Jutsu will work
on me… Huh?!
Die!
I’ll stop you in Menma’s place!
What?!
Rasengan!
He sacrificed his life to save
the village, huh…?
No matter what his past was,
he was a good guy at heart…
Mister…
I wanted to say a word of apology.
Not being able to remember
anything until the end
might have been salvation for him…
It was a promise, right?
To eat this with you.
You don’t need
to say anything to him?
He’ll be fine if he has an appetite.
I know how he is.
He’ll overcome it on his own
as time passes.
For a while he’ll probably remember
each time he eats ramen…
That’s fine.
People can get stronger
precisely because
they have feelings
that are never forgotten…
That’s what’s called growth.
Damn… This is good!
Menma…
The Key to the rusted heart’s door
Will always be smiling right near by
Even if rains of spears were to fall,
I will run through it
Because I want to find the joy
without a shape
This big dream of mine that
cannot be translated to words,
I will make it come true,
even if it were to deepen my wounds
We stand here today because of
what we believed through,
That is why I will continue running forward,
never looking away
Even if I’m told that
there is no bright future
I’ll change it right away,
lighting it with all my feeling
The wind is probably testing our hearts
In my heart, I gently grasped my hands
You are probably searching for
the answer to your tears
Your dream is always waiting near by,
with the answers in its hands
The Key to the rusted heart’s door
Will always be smiling right near by
The Village Hidden in the Sand
requested an auxiliary force?
Ones who call themselves
the Four Celestials
took one of Sand Village’s Ninja
candidates as a hostage
and escaped towards
the Land of Fire.
Presently, Gaara and others
are chasing them.
That means an ambush, doesn’t it?
I will leave the strategy up to you.
Take some Genin you can use
and leave within half an hour.
– That’s all.
– Hold on please.
What is it?
Let me borrow Sakura.
Next time: “The Targeted Shukaku”