Rock away your existence,
Shouting that you are here…
A new journey begins now.
As we survived through
the changing seasons,
we gained knowledge and strength,
(just looks like a survival game)
But the forgotten memories,
of the feelings abandoned within
the flows of time,
have also been lost.
When sinking down,
we learned loneliness.
But now we’ve met each other,
we are no longer alone.
Unveil your feelings,
Those high emotions
Those tears will change your fate.
Pound your heartbeat
against the darkness,
We’re sure to meet,
Under the same flag of pain
A Limitless Supply of Ninja Tools
Naruto!
You’ve come back, Choji!
Yay!
Are you okay, Naruto!
I’m okay, but I’m not okay
with your heavy weight!
I’ll get him right away!
Stop it Choji!
lt doesn’t work on him!
What?
This water absorbs all the shocks and
it gives me an iron-wall defense.
Oh, really?
Shoot!
Flower Ninja Art: Bloom!
Myriad of Flowers!
I’m saved.
Where’d that guy go?!
After a bonfire, you should put it out.
There is a limit to your Kunai Knife,
but my water that the earth
gives me is infinite.
His Ninjutsu is endless.
So for now…
Wanna run away?
Say that you’ll withdraw!
You can’t get away.
Summoning Jutsu!
After them!
This way!
If you get caught by that water,
it’s over for sure!
It’s coming around from
this side too.
It’s trying to trap us!
Run! Run! You’re all going to
get eaten if you get caught!
At this rate, we’re eventually
going to be defeated.
Looks like we’ve gotta beat him up,
after all.
But how are we going to beat him
if the attack doesn’t work on him?
Damn!
Huh?
Don't you think
there's something weird about him?
Wh-What is?
Hmm… I wonder?
Don’t be joking at a time like this!
Perhaps, is Naruto talking
about his tonfa?
Oh yeah, he’s holding his tonfa
like a dowsing rod.
That’s it!
It’s called dousing.
If you concentrate on the item
you’re looking for,
it will react to that item and inform you
when you get near it.
Dowsing?
I see! Naruto, Choji!
We might have a chance to win!
Huh?
If that tonfa is the secret of
this Jutsu then…
Naruto!
Let’s rap up the chase!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Idiot.
I’m not going to let you get away!
I've got you!
Seems like you tried to get close to me,
but too bad
Damn it!
I’m going to prepare
a special one for you.
Wh-What Naruto?
Hurry up and run, Choji!
Yurinojou!
Yurinojou! Choji!
Choji!
Behind you!
Look behind you!
I said look behind you!
Choji!
The fight is over.
First, the big one,
I’ll eat you first.
Certainly the fight is over.
A fight where you’re going to lose.
What?!
Right now Choji!
Drink up the water!
Useless, useless.
Water will gush out from the ground
with no limits.
Why isn’t the water coming out?
Like I said, it’s useless.
What happened?!
The water that will protect
you will not come out of here.
Look carefully at the surroundings..
Yes, water does not come out
of this craggy place.
I’m full!
Yurinojou has realized your secret.
I also thought something was strange.
When I went to check the trap,
I decided to take the shortest route
through the craggy area.
It wouldn’t have been strange
to run into you there…
but that didn’t happen.
The answer to that is easy!
You made a detour because
you avoided craggy areas
where the water wouldn’t come out.
The tonfa you hold is a weapon
and was a way to find the water
through dowsing.
You lost them and you went away
from your advantageous places.
You mean… The reason why
you cracked my tonfa was…
Of course, it wasn’t a coincidence.
It was planned by Yurinojou who
calculated your actions.
Damn it…!
This one will be heavy because
of the water!
Human Boulder!
You did it! Choji!
Yurinojou!
My ribs are injured, but…
I’m okay.
But there should be three of them,
so hurry and get the princess!
I got it!
Choji, please take care of Yurinojou.
Okay!
I’ll catch up to Hinata!
Let me rest a little.
I got it.
Let’s wait for everyone here.
There’s no need to wait.
After we rest a little, you are going
to take me to a safe place.
But Naruto and the others are not yet…
That doesn’t matter!
In the first place, everything became
like this because of you guys.
Instead of taking the long way,
if we had used the merchant people
as decoys,
then we would have escaped by now!
Decoys…?
But Kikusuke has already…
What about it?
If your mission as Ninja is to risk
your life in the line of duty,
then Kikunojou should be satisfied.
Even though Kikunojou is dead,
if I am still alive, then it’s possible to
revive the Land of the Green.
Princess.
Hinata, you won’t understand how
I was separated from my parents
to be held as hostage in
a foreign country
and how much I was bullied.
I realized then that only fools would expect
to live off of human compassion.
Especially someone like Naruto
who is easily influenced by
people’s emotions
should be disqualified as a Ninja.
He loses his rationality in his goal.
Princess, what do you know
about Naruto?
Naruto has lived without his parents
since he was a child.
He has always lived alone.
To be accepted by everyone,
to become the next Hokage…
he has worked hard…really hard…
Despite all that, he didn’t give up
and he would never think of
living at the expense of others.
He tried and tried.
Naruto and I are in different positions.
I’m sorry. You’re right, Princess.
Hinata… Do you like Naruto?
I understand.
Let’s wait for everyone here.
Princess…
That bag must be heavy.
I will relieve you
of some of the burden.
Oh, thanks.
I cannot die in a place like this.
Don’t you look nice, Ruiga.
Jiga… Help me… Brother…
Whatever.
If you die, Brother Renga and I could
split the Land of Green’s profits.
Jiga…
Don’t blame me.
W-Wait!
S-Stop Jiga…!
Hinata!
Hinata.
N-Naruto…
Where is the Princess?
That’s what I was going to ask!
I said let’s wait here and the minute
I turned around…
Why does a Ninja like you
get beaten by an amateur?
S-Sorry.
Then right now she should be alone…
Naruto, we should first go back
to the village
and get advice from the Hokage.
No!
There’s no time for that.
There are still two Janin left.
She’ll get killed if she gets caught.
But this really isn’t an official mission.
We might not be able to
handle the other two…
You’re right…
As you say, this may not be
an official mission but…
she’s trying really hard to escape
by herself right now.
The things she says and does
may be wrong,
but somehow,
I can’t leave her alone.
Naruto, I’ll also…
Hinata!
Yurinojou got hurt.
You and Choji,
please take care of Yurinojou!
See you later!
Oh!
Be careful, Naruto…
Right there!
I see, you have good instincts.
I’ll praise you for getting Ruiga.
Are you the second Janin?
Oh, I feel honored that you know
about me.
Then you should brag about it
in the other world.
That Mr. Jiga killed you,
so it couldn’t be helped.
Shadow Clone Jutsu.
What?
That wouldn’t work.
This guy…
What kind of Ninjutsu is he using?
A Hidden Leaf Ninja, huh?
How interesting.
I’ll put them down as
one of my next targets.
I won’t let you do that!
How did…?
Yup.
My Ninjutsu is Ninja Art Magnet.
It’s like this!
I will live, no matter what…
This is your graveyard.
I will return those words
right back at you.
You!
Then.
There!
Damn! 					What’s going on?!
What should I do?
I can't find Choji.
I'm sure that he's somewhere
hiding his presence, but…
This is… Naruto’s forehead band.
Naruto…
I grew up drinking iron.
That’s why I can use the iron
that has accumulated in my body
and turn myself into a magnet.
This rocky mountain contains
lots of iron,
making it my invincible battle-field.
Change yourself into magnet…?
By the way, I could also change
the things I touch into magnets.
I’ve already changed the rocks behind you
into powerful magnets.
So what are you trying to do?!
I mean this!
Ninja Art Magnet: Infinite Meteors!
Second hit! Third hit!
Naruto!
Your friend… I’ll take good care of her.
Hinata! Don’t come!
He is…
He is…a dangerous…opponent…
Naruto!
Yesterday’s Call Sign,
was all from my cell phone.
In a strange park,
I play the Fuzz Guitar without enthusiasm.
Yellow Moon.
Even now, counting to three,
I open my eyes
Shadow Moon I am still dreaming.
Look at my eyes, look at my eyes,
as we face one another’s back
Look at my eyes, when can we meet?
EveryDay EveryNight
With every word I can think of
Right away, my messy feelings as is,
A magical chord change, in a restless city
A daily JAZZ Guitar played
in a soft minor key
What should I do?
My Gentle Fist won’t work against
his Ninja Art.
It’s frustrating, but I can’t win against him
if I fight him head on.
At this rate, Naruto will…
No, no, I won’t let that happen.
I will discover the weakness
of his Jutsu.
I won’t give up!
I’ll stop him, no matter what!
Next time:
“The Byakugan Sees the Blind Spot!”
I’m going to risk everything
in this single attack!