Rock away your existence,
Shouting that you are here…
A new journey begins now.
As we survived through
the changing seasons,
we gained knowledge and strength,
(just looks like a survival game)
But the forgotten memories,
of the feelings abandoned within
the flows of time,
have also been lost.
When sinking down,
we learned loneliness.
But now we’ve met each other,
we are no longer alone.
Unveil your feelings,
Those high emotions
Those tears will change your fate.
Pound your heartbeat
against the darkness,
We’re sure to meet,
Under the same flag of pain
The Powerful Helper
Old Man Genno…
Yes! This is quite good!
Isn't it?!
Why’d he do something like this?
Now this detonator won’t activate.
Excellent, Tenten.
Now we can sigh with relief.
No, it’s still too soon to be relieved.
Right… When Genno realizes that
the detonator here has been removed…
he might activate
the Paper Bombs with
some other method and blow up the Leaf.
Oh, right.
You jerk. Don’t scare me like that, Choji!
Sorry.
At the moment,
it seems there’s no one here
who’s picked up on our movements.
All right, then put things back
the way they were.
Got it.
Now then…
You guys do the Kunai Knife practice
like before.
Don’t hit the center.
We know.
But we were sure lucky…
Nobody hit the center.
But I hit it right in the center yesterday.
I bet you were off by a little.
What? I don’t know about that..
It hit, I tell you.
To think there’d be this many.
Lady Tsunade, let’s evacuate
the villagers as quickly as possible.
Hey, you’re joking, right?
What do you mean?
If you do that, Genno might…
blow up the remaining Paper Bombs
right under the cover
of the evacuation confusion.
I see.
Naruto and the others are removing
the Paper Bombs now.
Could you wait for their report?
Akamaru?
Did you find one?
There it is!
All right!
Attaboy, Akamaru.
How’s it coming?
Just a little more.
Yes!
I leave the rest to you.
Leave it to me.
Did you get it yet, Naruto?
Just a little more.
Just a little more, I tell you.
H-Hang in there, Naruto.
Damn it, you little…
Hey, what’re you guys doing?
Oh, umm…
Some money got into the opening.
Oh, I’ll get it out for you later.
No, no. That’d be dangerous…
I mean, there’s no time to waste with
eating ramen.
Th-That’s right.
Ichiraku is sure tasty, isn’t it?
Well, hang in there.
Yeah, thank you.
Thanks.
Phew, we got through it well.
Excellent, Naruto.
We’d like more manpower.
It takes too long just with us.
But there aren’t any other Shinobi
left in the village.
Well, there are some here, though.
People of leisure who do nothing
but tell about old stories and
complain about
what the young people do.
Huh?
Could they be…?
Did you get that foul mouth from
the Third Hokage?
It’s the job of us advisors to
give advice to the youngsters.
What’s wrong with complaining?
It seems you have a good nose for
village crises due to your longevity.
You’re plenty older than
you look yourself.
Wh-What did you say? You old bag!
Watch what you say, eh, Fifth Hokage.
We’ve grasped most of the situation.
Where should we head to?
Then there’s a place
I’ve been saving for you.
Oh ho. I can’t wait.
To think the Fifth Hokage would be beaten.
That’s a powerful supporter.
Wow.
But scary.
Hurry! Youth, full power!
The enemy’s in the Leaf!
I appreciate it,
but I can’t stand those two.
But the removal operation
will proceed swiftly
once Guy Senpai and the others who
headed for the Hidden Waterfall get back.
It’ll be nice if things were to
go conveniently like that, but…
Shikamaru, have you got something?
I mean, it’s not ordinary stuff.
When and how the hell
did he set them?
There are too many Paper Bombs.
An abnormal amount of it.
No doubt about it.
Uh-huh.
And there’s one more thing
bugging me.
We’re overlooking something huge…
I really get that feeling.
Almost.
What’re you doing?
You’re not supposed to hit the center.
That’s right.
I’m next. I’ll miss.
In your case,
you’ll probably miss even if you aim.
How’s it going, Neji?
The Paper Bomb removal operation
is going smoothly.
I don’t see anyone
resembling Genno either.
I wonder where the enemy is.
Making us walk all the way to
the outskirts of town.
She must’ve gotten this slave driver
tendency from the Third Hokage.
A place that wouldn’t be unusual
for old people to tell old stories.
I’ll rake her over the coals
when we get back.
But what is that Genno fellow thinking?
There’s no point to setting
Paper Bombs in a place like this.
Is that what you really think?
What?
There was a plan to build
a shopping district
around here before, right?
That talk was over thirty years ago.
Hmm?!
What’s this?
H-Hey, isn’t that…?
Yes.
Look at this.
What is it?
The Jutsu form written here is different.
You’re right.
Now that you mention it, there’s no doubt.
It looks the same to me, though.
Where are your eyes pointing?
It’s the first time I’ve seen this.
It’s nothing new to us.
Speaking of Paper Bombs,
that’s what they were in the old days.
Then this is an old version?
It seems most of the Paper Bombs
that have been set in
the village are of that type.
Everyone, please look closely once more
at the locations where
the Paper Bombs were set.
Although this is
a residential area here,
there are hardly any Paper Bombs set.
On the other hand,
a large number of Paper Bombs
have been set in places
where hardly anyone lives.
What does that mean?
In the old plans,
that was supposed to become
a bustling shopping district.
What? Could that be…?
If you think about it putting together
various factors
such as the antique Paper Bombs,
the places where they were set
and such…
This is a trap that was
set thirty years ago.
Thirty years ago…
It’s just ridiculous.
Not one person noticed in thirty years.
It’s a blind spot.
Nobody would ever think
that this many Paper Bombs would
be set here in this village.
Once buried in a wall,
it couldn’t be found unless Byakugan
or something was used.
Then you mean
the Genno guy tried to use
the Paper Bombs someone
set thirty years ago?
But how did he find them?
Thirty years ago?
Could it be…?!
Shikamaru, where are you going?
Hey! Wait up.
We’re finished here, too
Let’s go to the next spot, Hinata.
Right.
Hinata!
What’s the matter?
I was using the Byakugan the whole time,
so I’m just a little tired…
I’m fine.
Are you sure?
Let me see.
Oh.
You’re kind of feverish.
Your face is red, too.
No, it’s not like that.
I’ll be okay if I just rest a little…
Really? Then I’ll deliver
the Paper Bombs
we’ve gathered thus far
to Grandma Tsunade,
so you wait here.
Okay.
I’ll be right back!
Ichiraku Ramen
The old man was standing here
the first time I met him.
I thought he was just
a ramen-loving old man, but…
Hm?
Could it be that what
he was looking at then was…?
Why in a place like this?
Well well…
So you found it, huh?
Old man?
I guess I cannot let you
go back now, can I?
Thirty years ago, huh?
That’s around the time when
my dad was still the master carpenter.
It was probably a time
when many outsiders were hired
just like now.
But I wonder if there are records
from back then.
Anything would be fine.
A blueprint or a ledger.
Hey, Shikamaru.
What’re you talking about? Explain.
Why did the referral vanish?
Referral? You mean the real referral
that became the catalyst for
Genno being suspected?
It was bugging me the whole time.
Perhaps the disappearance of
the referral was Genno’s doing.
But why was it necessary
to get rid of it?
It all makes sense
if we consider the referral
that disappeared was a fake, too.
What do you mean?
But that referral was always here.
So it was Genno himself
who came here to work with
that referral thirty years ago.
Oh!
That is to say…probably.
At that time, he used a referral
that couldn’t be distinguished
from the real thing.
And then he went to the trouble
of making one
that would be recognized as
a fake if compared with that one.
Why?
Even with old referrals,
he would be discovered
if reinvestigated again.
So he got rid of it right after
you blew the whistle on him.
In order to conceal the fact that
he worked here thirty years ago.
It’s because at that time in the village,
he set as many Paper Bombs
as were available.
Why?
Why’d you do such a thing?!
Long ago, there was a village
called Heat Devil Village in
the Land of Mountains.
This is the village where I was born.
Heat Devil Village?
You don’t know it?
No…
The only thing recorded in
the Bingo Book you brought
is that Genno’s homeland is
the Land of Mountains.
To be precise, Heat Devil Village
in the Land of Mountains.
The village itself vanished,
so it probably ended up
not being recorded.
Thirty years ago,
the Village Hidden in Leaves
and Heat Devil Village were at war.
Neither side didn’t give an inch
and the battle was in deadlock.
We launched a successful sneak attack
on Heat Devil Village,
taking advantage of the absence
of their main forces.
The tide of the war turned to
the Leaf’s advantage in one shot.
The only thing written
in the history books
is that an armistice was concluded
three months after that.
These three months are what’s peculiar.
Heat Devil Village should’ve been thinking
about a counterattack
before accepting a cease fire.
Here it is.
lt’s my dad’s diary from thirty years ago.
Really?
Yeah. It seems he left it faithfully.
Here.
Thanks.
"A middle-aged man from
the Hidden Sand came
"with a master carpentry referral."
"His skills aren’t great, but I decided
to hire him as I want manpower."
The date is one week after
the Heat Devil Village attack.
Then like you thought…
Checkmate. This is Genno.
It was my mission to infiltrate the Leaf
and to set Paper Bombs
throughout the village.
The operation was for the main forces
of Heat Devil Village
to invade the Village Hidden
in the Leaves at the same time
as the Paper Bomb explosions
and inflict a devastating blow.
I went out to various sites and
set Paper Bombs.
The Leaf village did not have substantial
Anbu Black Ops as they do now.
So I was able to move about with ease.
Right around the time when
two and a half months had passed,
I finished setting almost all
of the Paper Bombs…
and all that was left was to wait
for my comrades to attack.
But my comrades never came.
Why?
The leader of Heat Devil Village who
had insisted on “do-or-die” resistance;
lost his life in an accident.
And the man who assumed
the position of leader in his place
agreed to a ceasefire with the Leaf.
What?
"Genno doesn’t show up at the scene.
I wonder what the deal is."
He disappeared having left
behind the Paper Bombs.
As for me, my intention was to
immediately return to the Hidden Leaf.
I thought the ceasefire would just
be a temporary thing anyway.
But Heat Devil Village would never
give me another mission.
Two weeks after the ceasefire,
the Village Hidden in the Vale launched
a sneak attack on Heat Devil Village
and it was destroyed.
No way!
They were targeted at a moment
when they were weariest from
the battle with the Leaf.
Their defenses were probably
also down due to the ceasefire.
"Two months has passed since…
Where did Genno disappear off to…?"
Then why come back to the Leaf Village
now after all this time?
You set Paper Bombs because
it was your mission, right?
If Heat Devil Village is no more,
then there should be no reason
to go to the trouble of smashing the Leaf!
Could it be…someone asked you
to smash the Leaf?
Rest easy.
I haven’t been commissioned
or commanded by anyone.
Then why?
How can I put this? It felt like a waste.
A waste? What’s up with that?
I’m getting old and I could be taken
to heaven any time now.
If I were to die as is,
I’d be buried in darkness without
anyone learning of my traps.
If so, then I thought I’d put them
to good use before I die.
Are you serious?
You tried to kill people in the village
just for that reason?
I can’t believe that!
Then treating me to ramen was to…
It was to find out
about the present state
of affairs in the Leaf.
Damn you! You jerk!
You’ll understand when you get older!
I don’t understand!
As for me…
I won’t ever understand it!
I’ll show you my final big job
as a Trapper!
No way will I let you do that!
My friends are now in the middle
of removing all the Paper Bombs!
I won’t let the bombs blow up!
Sounds like quite a struggle.
But who said I was going to
blow up the Paper Bombs?
What’re you talking about?
You just said that before you die…
I said I would put them to good use.
You’re naïve, boy.
What?
I can put them to sufficiently good use
even without blowing them up.
Katsu!
A Shinobi reads two
or three moves ahead
and prepares several moves
in advance.
Remember that!
Shikamaru!
What is it?
The Academy students are saying
they’re tired.
What should we do?
The Academy students?
The Kunai Knife practice, right?
What? They were still doing that?
You idiot! You were the one
who had them do it.
Oh, oh yeah. Then have them
go ahead wrap things up.
Rather, it’d be trouble if they were
to get lucky and hit the center.
Oh!
What is it?
I get it. So that’s it!
It’s unnatural for a guy so prepared
to casually entrust the
final explosive device to pure luck.
What do you mean?
A Shinobi of Genno’s level should blow
it up with the most effective timing.
In other words,
it doesn’t matter whether
the Paper Bombs explode or not.
It’s just a diversion.
He’s really after something else!
On a checkerboard night
when the stardust’s are rapidly dancing
I just can’t come out and say,
“Ah, I don’t want to go home yet.”
Suggestively
Spat at that beloved face!!
Mister Cricket
The Trombone gradually going off-key
While on the sweaty center stage
does bug me.
But more importantly, the fuzziness I feel
in my undeveloped chest,
I wonder if it’s from
that coke I just drank?
Choji, things might get pretty ugly.
You’ve figured something out, huh?
We need to contact
the Fifth Hokage.
To not let the returning forces
enter the village.
Got it! But… Why?
If the Paper Bombs were
all a diversion,
then the moment he makes his move
is most likely when
the main forces return!
What?!
Shikamaru! Choji! We’ve got trouble!
What happened, Hinata?!
Naruto… Naruto’s in trouble!
Next time: “Multiple Traps!
Countdown to Destruction”