Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
The distance created between us
became too big,
because we were always together
Your honest reply, “See you…”
coming from that brash mouth
makes it sadder.
If you are in an unfamiliar town, crying
Then I want to deliver you a smile,
even if I’m not by your side
Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
I can feel it so close,
Our two hearts
Stop!
D-Don’t push my father around!
You idiot, Fuki. Get out of here!
What’re you hesitating for?
Take care of him quickly.
That’s your job, right?
Get out of my way.
Fuki!
You’ve got something nice there.
I’ll take that.
Please spare my daughter!
Like I care!
Father…
Father! Father!
Stop it!
Y-You jerk.
Here.
It’s okay.
Look out!
Just a little more…
Just a little more, believe it.
Rare menma pickled bamboo shoots?
Right. But only if I can get my hands
on it when it’s in rare bamboo state.
It seems the rare bamboo only grows
on some ungodly cliff…
Then I’ll get it, no matter what.
And then I’ll eat some Ichiraku ramen
with the rare pickled bamboo shoots on top…
No matter what, believe it!
Rare pickled bamboo shoots.
I did it!
I’m saved.
Huh?
What is that?
It’s a person!
Vanished Memories
To think there’d be thunder
even though it’s not raining…
It’s kind of eerie.
You shouldn’t shout like that…
This is a hospital.
You made me shout.
Huh? That white coat.
Could it be that you’re helping out
the Medical Team, Sakura?
Isn’t it lovely? I finally got the white coat.
I see. It’s great that you were here
just at the right time.
I’ve got someone I’d like you
to take a look at.
Someone you want me
to take a look at?
It’s him.
Wh-What? Could that be Dozaemon…?
His name’s Dozaemon, huh…?
I didn’t think he was
your acquaintance Sakura.
No. Dozaemon is a drowned body…
Oh, never mind…
I thought I knew him, but I was mistaken.
I see. Then I leave him to you.
Hey, this is a Leaf hospital.
So people outside of the village
can’t be admitted.
Come on, just do this for me.
I’ve got other business to attend to.
So I leave the rest to you.
Oh, hey, Naruto! Hold it!
This is indeed the rare bamboo
I’ve heard about.
Yeah, now I can eat the rare ramen!
What’re you talking about?
It takes three or four weeks to make
the pickled bamboo shoots
out of the rare bamboo.
What?!
First, I boil this
and then ferment it slowly.
What, I can’t eat it right away?!
You need a degree of determination
to eat delicious things.
Naruto, so this is where you were.
Hey, what’s up with you?
What’s up, nothing, you jerk…
Oww!
So you force a strange patient on me
and intend to eat ramen
by yourself at your leisure?
Ouch. That hurts.
Back to the Past Jutsu!
Oh, what’s he doing there?
He’s probing into his memory
from his subconscious.
That reverse hypnosis thing, huh?
Right.
Have you remembered anything?
I see.
It seems he’s lost his memory.
Lost his memory?
Let’s call it a day.
We’ll do more tomorrow.
It seems he doesn’t remember anything.
Not his name or address…
If none the doctor’s Jutsu don’t work,
then this is the real deal.
Then, doesn’t he have something
we could use to identify him?
Nope… This is all he had.
What’s this?
It’s a dove flute, also called an ocarina.
Ocarina?
It’s broken, though.
Oh, it looks like this will stick.
Not having memory could also
be a temporary state of shock…
Anyway, you sign this.
What’s this?
A letter of undertaking.
I told you earlier,
but this is a Leaf hospital.
Outsiders aren’t allowed.
If something were to happen,
you will take responsibility
for everything, Naruto.
What?!
You got a problem?
Fine, okay.
I sure picked up something troublesome.
What’s going on?!
That’s in the direction of the hospital!
Everyone, it’ll be okay.
Please evacuate calmly.
Help me!
Forgive me… Forgive me.
Is there anyone left?
Anyone here?
Sakura, did you evacuate everyone?
I’m checking right now.
Hey, Sakura!
Naruto.
Everything okay?
Somehow.
Hey, where is that guy?
What?
Come to think of it…
He’s not here.
Please help! My baby is…
My baby is still inside!
What did you say?!
No way. It doesn’t look like
we can get in with these flames…
What’re you doing?!
Hurry up and put out the fire!
I’ll go in!
That’s reckless.
The baby is in the deepest part
of the hospital.
What?
It’s the sound of a flute.
It's him!
He’s getting closer.
Here he comes!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
– This way! 					– To the right.
He did it! The baby is with him, too!
All right!
My boy!
That was a close shave.
Thank goodness!
Thank you very much…Thank you!
Sure.
Thank you so much.
An outsider with amnesia, huh?
Good grief. What a dilemma.
It’d be okay just to let
that one guy stay, right?
We can’t do that.
For the safety of the village,
we must not overlook even
the slightest thing.
But, we figured out that
he’s not a bad guy
after that incident, right?
Unfortunately, we must not let someone
whose identity we don’t know
stay in the village.
Then, if he were to do something,
I’ll take the responsibility
and figure something out.
Sakura, how’s he doing?
Has he remembered anything?
No, nothing yet.
I see.
I’m begging you.
I’ll let you guys have some of
the rare pickled bamboo
shoot ramen too, Grandma.
Rare…pickled bamboo shoots?
Yeah. I went to pick some on
the way back from a mission
and then found him--!
That’s news to me.
So you were loitering around like
that on your way back from a mission?
Ouch. Oww.
Naruto, so you’re serious about
looking after that boy, huh?
Yeah, it’s true.
All right, then I’ll let that boy
remain in the village.
Lady Tsunade!
I can’t run out the person
who saved a child from this village.
Excellent, Grandma.
Now you’re talking!
I’m Naruto Uzumaki…
Nice to know you.
I-I’m…
Oh, that’s right.
Your memory hasn’t come back yet.
Then, hmmm.
Menma, make it Menma.
Menma?
Yeah. I’d gone to pick some
and then I found you, so…
Menma…
Okay, got it. My name’s Menma.
It’s settled. Nice to meet you, Menma.
Good to meet you, Naruto.
Here you go.
Wow, it looks delicious.
The ramen here is the best
in the world, believe it.
Let’s eat.
Tasty.
But this isn’t the finished product.
Don’t you notice something lacking?
Huh?
Oh.
Come to think of it, there isn’t
any menma pickled bamboo shoots on top.
Right. Until the rare pickled
bamboo shoots are ready,
they’re sealed from your ramen.
Hey, old man, you’ll be
sure to make it, right?
Absolutely.
I can’t wait. Say, Menma.
Let’s definitely come here together
to have some at that time.
Right.
Okay, come on in.
Excuse me for barging in.
As of today, this is your home.
It’s a dirty place,
but make yourself comfortable.
Whoa.
It really is dirty.
Don’t get so hung up on the details.
Y-You’re right.
More importantly, let’s get to sleep and
starting tomorrow we’ll come up with
a way to get your memory back.
Right.
I can’t eat anymore…
Man, I slept well!
Morning, Naruto.
Menma?
Whoa.
Everything’s been cleaned up nicely!
Did you do this?
Yeah. I couldn’t sleep and
had time to kill.
Thanks for that…
Hey, Menma! What’re you doing?!
What do you mean?
I’m hanging up the laundry.
Don’t wash someone else’s underwear!
I’ll do that myself,
so don’t worry about it!
Really?
Now then…
How should we get your memory back?
Oh, I know!
Come with me, Menma.
This is a specialty from the Land of Wind,
Sand Dumplings.
This fine soy powder is used to
resemble sand and they taste really good.
Yeah?
And this one is a specialty from
the Land of Earth, Stone Rice Cakes.
The crunchy texture is irresistible.
Uh-huh.
And this is a specialty from
the Land of Water, Mist Mitsumame Beans.
So? Have you remembered anything?
No… Nothing at all.
Oh, I thought you might
remember something
if they had a specialty
from your home.
Sorry.
No need to apologize.
Naruto, forget about my memory.
What?
You see, we don’t know how
or when my memory will come back.
More importantly,
you’ve got your own work, right?
Well, you’ve got a point.
I’ve got to finish cleaning
the Great Stone Faces by today…
Then let’s do that.
But before that, wait just a minute.
Huh?
Hey, Menma.
Ma’am…
I’ll carry your things
to your house.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you very much.
No problem.
At any rate, you’ve sure got
a lot of weeds growing in your yard.
My lower back has been
bothering me lately…
The grass grows as much as it wants.
Then I’ll do it.
Oh, my.
I-I will, too!
Thanks so much!
Phew… Finally done!
Naruto.
What is it?
They want help too!
Huh?
It seems this area here
is all homes of the elderly.
Thanks.
I leave it to you.
F-For real?
What’s this?
Actually, thank-you gifts have
been sent to Naruto and that boy
from all over the village.
What’re those two doing?
But really, you’re sure an odd guy.
Am I?
You’ve got a strong
sense of righteousness,
I mean,
you’re the embodiment of kindness.
It’s not something easily done.
I just want to live right.
I don’t want to have any more regrets.
Hm? Menma,
have you remembered something?
Huh? No, not really.
I see.
What?! Is it bird poop?
It’s blood!
Give me a hand, Menma!
Right!
What’s the matter?!
Someone…in this village…
Let’s get out of here!
Menma, I leave this guy to you.
Got it.
Damn it!
Damn you. Come on out!
Damn it! Where’s he hiding?
Naruto…
Sound of a flute? Is it Menma?!
Huh? What’s this…?
Awesome power’s starting to
well up in my whole body.
All right.
Awesome!
Power’s flowing over me!
I see you.
Damn it.
I did it.
It’s a Substitution!
Damn it. He got away, huh…?
You okay, Naruto?
Menma…
That flute just now…
Who in the world are you?
The Key to the rusted heart’s door
Will always be smiling right near by
Even if rains of spears were to fall,
I will run through it
Because I want to find the joy
without a shape
This big dream of mine that
cannot be translated to words,
I will make it come true,
even if it were to deepen my wounds
We stand here today because of
what we believed through,
That is why I will continue running forward,
never looking away
Even if I’m told that
there is no bright future
I’ll change it right away,
lighting it with all my feeling
The wind is probably testing our hearts
In my heart, I gently grasped my hands
You are probably searching for
the answer to your tears
Your dream is always waiting near by,
with the answers in its hands
The Key to the rusted heart’s door
Will always be smiling right near by
As I thought, he’s no ordinary man.
He won’t be an easy opponent to fight.
Wait a minute.
You are talking about Menma
like his our enemy or something.
There is that possibility, you know.
He could be with the intruder
from the other day.
What are you talking about?
Weren't you two gonna help us
seek Menma's memory together?
Our mission is to find out
the guy's identity
and to catch the intruder.
Unlike you, we don't trust Menma just yet.
Next time: "Bringing Back Reality"