We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers
don't care what people think about them
follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh! Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
Down a difficult road
filled with endless struggles
Where do you think you are going
following someone else's map?
An insightful crow comes along
to tear up the map
Now open your eyes and
take a look at the truth (Yeah!)
There's nothing to lose,
so let's GO!!!
We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers
don't care what people think about them
follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh!
Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
We're gonna do it and do our best!
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
We're gonna do it and do our best! BANG!
This man Jiraiya does not fall victim
to any woman’s allurement,
but rather his forte is
winning women’s affections!
You were totally excited by a lame tactic
like a woman winking at you!
You shouldn’t be the one to try
acting all suave and cool, you Pervy Sage!
Like I said, don’t call me
that in front of people…
Be quiet…
More importantly these people
aren’t normal, Pervy Sage!
Didja hear me, Pervy Sage?!
Like I said, don’t call me “Pervy Sage”!
You are, after all, Master Jiraiya,
one of the legendary Sannin…
I didn’t believe that
I’d be able to stop you so easily
despite the fact that you are
a huge womanizer.
What?!
You know the true identity
of Pervy Sage?!
Well no, that’s not necessarily
who I really am…
Seems like you released the Genjutsu
that we had put on that woman.
You shouldn’t call yourself a man
for using such a cowardly tactic
like casting a Genjutsu on the woman
with your hypnotic eyes
to separate me and Naruto.
Separate us…
Why would they do that?
Your target is Naruto, after all.
You are after the Nine-Tailed Fox
in Naruto…
No wonder Kakashi knew that as well…
I see clearly now.
The information source was you.
To abduct Naruto is the No.1 priority
placed by our organization, Akatsuki!
What’s going on…?
I can’t let you have Naruto…
I wonder about that.
This is perfect…
I’ll get rid of you two right here!
Don’t butt in…
The one that’s going to kill him is …
Me!
Hate Among the Uchihas:
The Last of the Clan
Sasuke…
Revenge, I see…
Right now, I have no interest in you…
Don’t mess with me!
Sasuke!
Darn you!
Naruto! I told you not to butt in!
I told you before…
I’ve lived only for this very day…
for this very day!
Sasuke…
Not yet…
You can’t even make a hand sign
together at this point…
This is…my battle!
Fine.
Wha--?
You heard that didn’t you?
This is their battle.
Let’s not bother with it.
Fine then!
Wh-Why…?
Our power difference hasn’t changed
at all since that time…
Why is that?
He doesn’t show any mercy.
What have I…
been doing all this time?
Whatever have I…
You are weak.
And you are weak…
because you don’t have enough hate.
This place is…
Could it be?!
That's right.
This is our house.
Dad! Mom!
You are weak.
For the next 24 hours…
Stop it…
Relive that day.
Stop it!
Uncle! Auntie!
You’re not even worth killing.
Foolish younger brother…
If you want to kill me, begrudge me!
Hate me!
And keep on surviving in that
unsightly manner…
Just continue fleeing and fleeing
and hang onto your life!
Hasn’t changed at all…
Using Tsukiyomi: Nightmare Realm
on your own little brother.
Stop it already! You!
Wha--?!
Th-This…
Ninja Art: Toad Mouth Trap!
How unfortunate, Itachi, Kisame.
You guys are already inside
my stomach!
I summoned the esophagus of
the giant toad
of the Mt. Myomoku rock cave.
You guys are wanted criminals anyway.
I’ll turn you guys into fodder
for the stone toad.
What?!
Wh-What is this?
Naruto, you stay still!
Don’t worry, it’s my Jutsu!
Come here, Kisame!
Oh!
Darn it!
It’s useless!
There hasn’t been one person who
has been able to escape from this!
A wall of flesh is charging at us!
The wall is faster.
At this rate…
Hey…
Pervy Sage!
What’s the matter?!
Huh!
They’ve gone!
I cannot believe that this wall
has been torn through…
Why must we retreat?
You would be…
We have no reason to rush to
get Naruto in the current condition.
Besides, I have to rest
my body somewhere for a while.
Not just Tsukuyomi,
but he also made me
use Amaterasu as well…
What is this fire?
It’s black…
Don’t get so close!
How did those guys manage to get out?
Not only that…
What are these black flames?
The stone toad who has the ability
to blow fire had its intestine’s burned…
Huh…?
All right!
Sealing Jutsu: Fire Seal!
All right! It’ll be okay for now.
Now for Sasuke!
Sasuke!
Sasuke…
Dynamic…
Guy?!
Entry!
Well… Eh…
I’m sorry to have kicked you so directly.
I was in a rush and I forgot my mirror…
I used this headband instead,
but it was hard to see.
And I assumed this rough-hewn face
was the enemy…
I just let the flames of
the burning juvenescence take over me…
I’m sorry!
Is that … supposed to be an apology?
I’m a simple-minded guy
just like how my face looks.
It doesn’t really matter.
More importantly, we have to get Sasuke
to the Medical Team!
Yes!
He’s broken his arm and ribs.
Not only that, he’s lost consciousness
from some kind of mental blow
he received from the Visual Jutsu!
This boy also experienced that Jutsu…
Hey Pervy Sage!
ls Sasuke going to be all right?
Seems like he’s received
a significant amount of mental damage.
I’m going to kill you!
Die!
You jerk!
You’re in the way!
Darn… Why?!
What did that guy do to Sasuke?!
Hey, Pervy Sage!
We’ve gotta change our plan!
I got scared earlier,
but this time I’m going to chase
those black-capes and get them!
It’s me that they want, right?!
Then, I’ll be the one to
make my way over!
Humph, you’re only going to be killed
if you go now.
They’re at a totally different level
from you.
I just managed to get you
away from them…
Then, are we just going
to keep running away?!
Are we supposed to keep living in fear?!
Shut your mouth for a second!
You are weak.
I’m sorry, Guy.
I thought that I had spared
the boy’s feeling, but…
I should have saved him much sooner.
Kakashi has also come down
with the same Jutsu…
We don’t know when
he will regain consciousness.
Kakashi Sensei?!
When my students are hurt…
I always wish,
from the bottom of my heart…
If that person,
who is a medical specialist, were here…
That’s why we’re going to
go find her now.
What?
You mean, her?
Could it be…?
W-Wait…!
C-Could this money be…?!
Yup, that’s right…
The one who uses the slug
and drives illness away,
and who is also
one of the Sannin like me…
All right! We’re going to turn around
our luck with this!
Princess Tsunade with
the letter “Gamble” on her back!
A cycle of hardship, right?
Inside, we were crying, right?
But the one thing we won't give up
is the dream we've chosen, right?
It's a secondary role,
a role in the shadows
But in reaching for that dream,
let us stay centered,
let us stay true
Over and over,
we hung on without giving up
we kept coming back up
Over and over,
we believed and dreamed
we've seen fools
It’s festival, festival, festival!
I’m going to spend like
there’s no tomorrow!
Wait a minute, Naruto!
I will keep your wallet for you.
Huh?!
It’s been said since ages past
that three forbidden factors:
money, alcohol, and women,
are believed to cause Ninja failures.
I am not like you, Pervy Sage!
All right! I am going to
enjoy the festival!
Next time: “A New Training Begins:
I Will Be Strong!”
Wait. What are we gonna
do about my training?