C'mon!
Running like a fugitive,
Being chased by something
Inside my heart is pounding
My throat dry like it's withering
For no single one,
To none does belong,
This time is ours, right now...
Unraveling the pain,
Unraveling our hearts,
Unraveling shadows
Stifling our breath,
Reaching for beyond,
Tearing through the dark
In fighting and in love
To the distant light above,
Yes, we are on the way
I wanna rock...
Rockin' my heart
Today's…a special day, so…
Time to eat!
Sasuke and Sakura: Friends or Foes?
Fight me, here!
What're you doing, Konohamaru?
Very good, Naruto…
You're the man I expected you to be.
I didn't do anything, you know…
Let's fight fair!
Sorry! I've got
an orientation meeting to go to.
An orientation meeting…?
Cause… As of today, I'm a Ninja!
Oh…
Sakura!
Shouldn't you be heading out soon?
I was thinking of leaving now!
Cha! How long are you planning
to treat me like a child?!
That's right… I'm not a student
of the academy anymore…
I'm a Kunoichi of the Leaf Village,
Sakura Haruno!
I'm off!
Morning, Sakura.
Morning... Ino.
Who would've thought you'd
be able to graduate.
Ancient history has nothing to do with it.
As of today,
we're both full-fledged Ninjas...
I won't lose to you anymore, Ino!
What the--? Why are you here?
Today's meeting is for graduates only.
Hey, don't you see this headband?
As of today, I'm a Ninja, too!
How can I put it, it really suits me.
So Naruto…was able to graduate.
Goal!
I won again, Sakura!
What're you saying…?
The tip of my foot got in
one centimeter faster!
You must be blind.
It's Sakura.
Oh…
Sakura's looking at me…
Hey, Sakura!
Mor... morning, Sakur--
Get outta' the way!
M-Morning, Sasuke…
Mind if I sit next to you?
Hey! I'm going to sit
next to Sasuke!
First come, first served!
I got in the classroom sooner!
I did!
If that's the case,
then I did!
I was first!
I'm sitting next to Sasuke!
How annoying...
Is that this year's top rookie,
Sasuke Uchiha?
Yes.
The sole survivor of the Uchiha clan?
Naruto Uzumaki, eh…
Naruto! Don't glare at Sasuke!
Sakura…
Everyone's all Sasuke Sasuke.
What's so great about this guy?!
Just beat him up, Sasuke!
Yeah! Yeah!
What? Really?
Oh! Sorry!
Wha--?
Whoa!
Cha! I was planning on
seizing Sasuke's first kiss!
You jerk…
Naruto! I'll kill you!
– My mouth is rotting.
– Huh? Was that my fault?
What? I feel rage…
Naruto…
You…
An accident…
lt was an accident
You are annoying!
Yikes!
Naruto…He's at
the center of trouble as usual.
As of today, you all have become
full-fledged Ninjas…
However, you're still Genin.
The tough part's still to come!
From here on, you'll be in a squad of three
and carry out your missions
under your Jonin teachers.
A squad of three?!
I wonder who's going to be
grouped with Sasuke.
I don't know…
Cha! I'll be the one grouped
with Sasuke, naturally!
Squads of three, eh.
lt'll just slow me down…
First will be Sakura.
And the other person…
can be anyone other than Sasuke!
The groups have been determined
so that the strength of
the groups will be balanced.
Now for the assignments!
Now then, next is Group Seven…
Naruto Uzumaki!
Sakura Haruno.
Hooray!
I'm with…Naruto…?
And…Sasuke Uchiha!
Hooray!
I'm with…Sasuke…?
So I'll be in a different group
from Naruto, huh…
Next is Group Eight. Hinata Hyuga!
Y-Yes…
Kiba Inuzuka!
Shino Aburame!
Why is this happening…?
Group Nine.
Cha! Love will be victorious!
Man…
Why do women think that
kind of guy's so great…?
Don't you understand, Shikamaru?
Well, I'm not a woman…
That's why you are
not popular among girls.
I wouldn't want to be grouped with you.
Group Ten. Ino Yamanaka.
Shikamaru Nara.
It appears we've been
grouped together.
And Choji Akimichi.
And Fatty on top of that...
That's all for the group division.
Iruka Sensei!
Why does an exceptional student
like me have to be
in the same group with this guy?!
Sasuke has the best grades
of the graduates.
Naruto, you're at the bottom!
Of course, this is how it is when trying
to balance the strength within groups.
Just don't get in my way, loser!
Hey, what did you say?!
You want to fight, loser?
Knock it off, Naruto!!
In the afternoon,
I'll introduce you to your Jonin teachers.
You're dismissed until then!
Sasuke!
Where'd you go, Sasuke?
I thought since we're in the same group
and all, we'd eat together.
Sakuraaaa!
Since we're in the same group and all,
let's eat together!
Why should I have to eat with you?!
Well... we're in the same group, so…
You're…annoying.
Sasuke! Where are you?
Darn! This is no fun.
I 'm finally in the same group as Sakura…
and then it's like this…
I wonder if something good will happen…
That's it!
Listen up!
As long as we're in the same group,
you will follow my instructions.
Yeah-yeah…
She becomes a real pain in the neck
when people try to argue with to her, so…
Let's all go out for
some BBQ sometime.
Oh, man…
Hmm?
Naruto…?
Huh?
Oh!
Jerk, it's Naruto, isn't it!
Darn! Just be quiet.
Naruto! I won't forgive you
if you hurt Sasuke!
What happened?
Heh! Idiot…
So Naruto got beaten by
the one he challenged…
Of course! Naruto's no match
for Sasuke!
No need for me to feel rushed…
From here on out,
I'll be in the same group as
Sasuke for the long haul…
But…
Even if I were to use
my feminine charms…
my proportions are below average…
All that's above average is
the width of my forehead…
What should I do…?
Huh? No way!
Sasuke…is looking...
this way!
And with such a passionate look!
You…have a charmingly wide forehead.
It makes me want to kiss it.
That's what its surface area is for.
Yeah, right…
I'm not just some kid
who believes in fairy tales…
There's no way.
You…have a charmingly wide forehead.
What?!
It makes me want to kiss it.
Cha! This fairy tale is for real!!
Or that's what Naruto would say.
I've got something to ask you.
What?
What do you think…of Naruto?
He's quite at home interfering and
enjoys it when I make mistakes.
Naruto doesn't understand
one thing about me…
He just annoys me!
All I want…is for you to
accept me, Sasuke.…
For me to accept you…?
I'll do anything for the sake of that.
I was careless!
W-Wha--?!
Gotcha!
I didn't think someone who couldn't
perform the Clone Jutsu properly
could do the Shadow Clone Jutsu.
I'm…desperate, so…
I finally know why I…
I like Sakura so much.
Diarrhea at a time like this?!
What's wrong?
I-I'll be right back…
225	01:41:53:26	01:41:56:04
Sasuke's so shy!
I guess he needs to
prepare himself mentally…
That was close!
My stomach hurt so much that
the Jutsu was about to wear off!
Why does my stomach have
to hurt at such a good time?!
I'm annoying... huh…
She said so again…
And I transformed into Sasuke and
had got a little closer to Sakura…
In that case…
I'll play an obnoxious Sasuke …
and make her hate him!
Oh Sasuke,
you're such a shy bad boy!
Are you prepared? I'm raring to go!
H-Hey, Sasuke!
Where's Naruto?
Oh, there you go changing
the subject again…
Just leave Naruto alone!
All he does is pick fights with you!
It's because he wasn't raised right!
You know!
He doesn't have any parents, right?
He always selfishly does
whatever he wants!
My parents would get mad at me
if I did something like that!
There are no parents to nag you
if it's just you alone!
So his selfishness comes
out at various times!
The loneliness.
Huh?
It's something worse than getting
scolded by parents and...
W-What's gotten into you…?
You…
annoy me.
Darn! It finally stopped!
I wonder if Sakura's still waiting.
W-What are you doing here?!
I used the Escape Jutsu,
the very basic of techniques.
Oh...
What were you planning to do…
by transforming into me?!
I thought it'd be fun, so I gave it a try!
The Shadow Clone Jutsu again?!
I'll show you that I'm really amazing!
I'll defeat you…
and make you accept me!
Prepare yourself, Sasuke!
Just like that, my stomach again…
B-Bathroom!
I'm first, I say!
I'm first, I say.
I'm about to go in my pants, I say!
How stupid!
"You annoy me" …huh?
I see. So this is how
Naruto must've felt…
I wonder if I can…
be a bit more nice next time…
Darn.
Did I eat something bad?
Naruto…
Smile…Smile…
Let's go back to the classroom, Naruto.
Sakura…
Payback for earlier, huh?
Sasuke's turned himself into Sakura…
You're trying to trick me, right, Sasuke?!
I don't think so!
Ow-ow-ow…
What the heck is going on?!
Oh…
You idiot, Naruto!
So, this is Naruto's room…
And Sasuke of the Uchiha clan is
also in the group you'll be in charge of.
I wish you good luck!
The expiration date…
of this milk has passed quite awhile ago…
He'll get sick if he drink this.
It seems like that things are
going to get disastrous.
What the heck is going on?!
What is going on?!
This isn't the same Kakashi Sensei
from yesterday.
Is this really the same Kakashi Sensei
who got caught in my trap
and breezily came late?
Darn it! Darn it!
No way am I giving up!
I'll defeat him and clear
this super difficult testl!
No way am I going back now!
Next episode:
"Pass or Fail: Survival Test"
Don't miss my outstanding performance!