Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
The distance created between us
became too big,
because we were always together
Your honest reply, “See you…”
coming from that brash mouth
makes it sadder.
If you are in an unfamiliar town, crying
Then I want to deliver you a smile,
even if I’m not by your side
Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
I can feel it so close,
Our two hearts
This is my chance to show my master
the fruits of my training!
They're both caught in a Genjutsu…
Yakumo?
Is that you, Yakumo?
So you were safe!
Help me!
It’s okay now, Yakumo.
I’ll protect you, no matter what!
Kurenai Sensei!
Kurenai's Top-Secret Mission:
The Promise with the Third Hokage
The two who went in first
haven’t come back, huh?
Sure enough, is Yakumo in
a state of awakening?
You two handle
Yakumo and Kurenai…
– Yes, sir! 					– Yes, sir!
You handle the nuisance
that’s heading this way.
Yes, sir!
What?!
Leave it to me…
That emblem…!
You’re with the Kurama Clan…?!
Yuhi Kurenai…
Hand over Yakumo quietly.
What does the Kurama Clan
plan to do with Yakumo?!
This is a clan issue.
It doesn’t concern you.
Yakumo is the child I’ve
taken custody of,
from the Third Hokage.
Then, by force…
No!
You can’t escape now!
What’s this?!
To think she’d make it look like
she got caught in a Genjutsu
and then trap us in
a Genjutsu…!
Damn it! Where’d she go…?
It hurts…
You okay…?!
Wha--?!
You jerk!
Oh, Naruto!
– Hey! Hold it. 					– H-Hey!
Take this!
What?!
Ow-ow… Hm?!
This bean stalk is too damn big!
I-I can’t move…!
This is not good!
Naruto!
Die!
Shino!
What?!
Genjutsu doesn’t work
on the insects…
Damn it.
Wh-What…?!
He vanished?!
There!
No matter where you hide,
you can’t cover up your scent!
Man-Beast Clone!
Fang Over Fang!
Yes!
Severe Leaf Hurricane!
No chance a half-baked Genjutsu would
work on us fully trained Ninja!
Stop!
– Huh?
– Let go, let go! Let me go!
Jeez!
– Naruto! 					– Let go!
Release!
What?! Sakura…
Morning…
It’s because you charge right
into an enemy’s Jutsu on your own.
Oh! Kurenai Sensei and Yakumo?!
Kurenai Sensei!
Who’re these people?!
All four of them have been caught in
a Genjutsu and are unconscious.
Kurenai Sensei!
S-Sensei… Kurenai Sensei!
She’s nowhere to be found!
Byakugan!
What is it?!
K-Kurenai Sensei has…
There's one left…
Just like that…
To think they’d cast a Genjutsu on me.
Release!
What?! It won’t wear off?!
It’s Unkai who served as
the replacement leader
of the Kurama Clan
after my father died.
Unkai from the Kurama Clan…
I see.
Things won’t go as they did
with the others, eh?
Kurenai Yuhi, Genjutsu user.
I’m embarrassed to be praised by you…
I’d like to avoid needless battle.
Hand over Yakumo.
Hang on tight.
You may very well be
Kurenai Yuhi,
but how do you intent
to fight within my Jutsu?!
Oh, no!
Damn you!
I smell blood!
Heh. I won’t let you escape…
There!
Next, I’ll pierce your heart…
Hand over Yakumo.
Why do you protect her?!
Kurenai Sensei!
I won’t let you touch Kurenai Sensei!
Look out!
Wha--?! Not again!
Geez, when will you
ever learn, Naruto?!
Byakugan!
Naruto! The enemy’s above you!
Huh?!
Byakugan, huh?!
If you’re coming at me
with Genjutsu, then…
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Go!
Clones, huh?!
Heh! Mine aren’t just illusions.
Let’s go!
– Yeah! 					– Yeah!
U-zu-ma-ki!
Naruto Barrage!
I’ll definitely get Yakumo…
Byakugan!
Yakumo has been sedated to calm
her nerves and is asleep now.
But it would be best for her
to have a complete examination
back at the village hospital.
It was a big help having
you here, Sakura.
You should also get
some first-aid treatment, Sensei.
Right… Thanks.
Okay, please show me.
They’ve been like this the whole time.
It doesn’t look like they’ll wake up
from the Genjutsu
for quite a while…
Well, I guess that serves
our interests better. Hm?
It’s…!
Kurenai Sensei!
Oh! Thank goodness you look okay!
Y-Yes…
She’s not okay!
Wha--?!
I gave her some first-aid treatment,
but she has a deep wound.
We must get back to the village quickly…
Don’t worry about me.
I’m more concerned about
Yakumo’s instability.
Yeah, their comrades could
very well return.
I’m also concerned about
how we haven’t seen the three people
who were assigned to guard Yakumo.
All right!
Leave this to me and all of you
head back to the village
with Kurenai and Yakumo!
Organize a back-up unit.
Your opponents are practitioners
of Genjutsu.
Will you be okay alone?
What?
This fully…
…trained body!
I would cram by the likes
of the Kurama Clan’s Genjutsu!
A pun?
Oh?
Are you awake?
Hey, do you resent Kurenai Sensei
for sealing your Genjutsu?!
That person hates me…
She didn’t want to make me into
a practitioner of Genjutsu.
It’s not like that!
Then…why?!
I’m sure she had some kind
of reason!
You would’ve been in trouble
had Kurenai Sensei
not risked her life to save you before!
That was the Kurama Clan…
People from the same clan as me.
What?
Why would people
from the same clan as you…?
Kiba, could you take Kurenai Sensei
back to the village?
I’m fine…
I can at least do that myself.
Kiba?!
Hey, Kurenai Sensei?!
Tell us the truth!
Isn’t this incident and you
quitting our squad…
somehow related?
The Kurama Clan into
which Yakumo was born…
was once a force in
the Village Hidden in the Leaves
as a family of Genjutsu users.
However, they had been brought
to ruin in recent years,
unable to turn out Chunin and Jonin.
Then a rising star brimming with
talent appeared in the clan.
And that was Yakumo.
My parents and relatives placed
their hopes in me,
the only daughter of
the head family.
But I was in poor health and
my official entrance into the Academy
was not acknowledged.
I had wanted to live up
to the expectations
of my parents and the clan…
and I got really depressed.
My father saw me like that
and negotiated directly with
the Third Hokage for me.
The Third Hokage whom
Murakumo consulted
realized the high level of
Yakumo’s latent power
and decided to leave her
in my custody.
By the order of the Third Hokage,
Kurenai Sensei became
my personal teacher.
But…
Y-Yakumo?!
Kurenai Sensei… She…!
Why?!
I don't know.
Maybe since I’m a Genjutsu user too,
I got jealous of the high level
of Yakumo’s latent powers.
Jealous…?!
Genjutsu practitioners with
higher powers than mine
are not necessary in this village.
No way. You’d do that for
a reason like that…?
You understand, don’t you?
A selfish person like me can’t continue
to go on missions
with your lives entrusted to me.
I can’t believe that!
It’s not just her…
I’m a hindrance to the Leaf Village.
Wh-What do you mean?
I just can’t believe it.
Isn’t Kurenai Sensei still hiding
something from us…?
I also…get that feeling.
Exactly.
It’s because…
Kurenai Sensei’s hand shook
with heartache
when she talked about events
in the past.
But the shaking stopped…
when she talked about her motive.
What do you mean?
That motive is a lie.
The heart is not affected by
a made-up story.
Then her being jealous of Yakumo…
Perhaps she’s protecting someone.
Someone so important
Kurenai Sensei would protect?
That would be, for example…
I overheard Kurenai Sensei
and the Third Hokage talking.
Yakumo’s powers probably
will not awaken for a long while.
I see. But the time will eventually come
when the dam bursts and
her powers will pour out.
That power of the Kurama Clan
will eventually threaten
the Village Hidden in the Leaves.
At that time,
we’ll have to eliminate it.
Even the Third Hokage was
involved with the sealing of my powers.
The Third Hokage would
never order something like that!
My parents died just before
I started training under
Kurenai Sensei.
There was a sudden fire.
It seems the fire spread quickly
and they couldn’t be saved…
But my parents were even Jonin!
To think they would die
just in a fire.
And a fire in broad daylight
on top of that…
And after that, although I was told
there was no foul play…
the autopsy reports were
classified and sealed.
No way?!
lt wasn’t just an ordinary fire?
My parents were killed on
order of the Third Hokage…!
No way…!
No way could that ever be true!
The Key to the rusted heart’s door
Will always be smiling right near by
Even if rains of spears were to fall,
I will run through it
Because I want to find the joy
without a shape
This big dream of mine that
cannot be translated to words,
I will make it come true,
even if it were to deepen my wounds
We stand here today because of
what we believed through,
That is why I will continue running forward,
never looking away
Even if I’m told that
there is no bright future
I’ll change it right away,
lighting it with all my feeling
The wind is probably testing our hearts
In my heart, I gently grasped my hands
You are probably searching for
the answer to your tears
Your dream is always waiting near by,
with the answers in its hands
The Key to the rusted heart’s door
Will always be smiling right near by
The story I heard from the girl.
The story I heard from
Kurenai Sensei.
Which one is true?
lt’s unlikely that they’re all lying.
But I can say this.
There’s no way the Third Hokage
would think about eliminating the girl.
For the time being,
I’ve got to get Sensei and
the others to the hospital quick--!
What’s this?!
Next time: “Genjutsu or Reality?”