I want to try and gather
the unrestrained winds
I’ll run toward the horizon,
alongside the wave crests
I’ve made my decision,
even if there’s a long way to go
on that road.
I’ll continue towards the future I’ve planned
Time rushes us
The heartbeat speeds up
When I woke in the middle of a dream
I kept searching for that same light
Under the shining star-lit sky with
countless constellations and shadows
There was something beyond that…
What were you gazing at?
Ah, which way is it?!
There’s a faint scent of salt water…
We were almost there…
Then I’ll use
my Rasengan to…
Wait! If it doesn’t go well,
we’ll be crushed under the ceiling.
If so, what should we do?!
Everyone, step backward.
What?!
Phew, we’re safe…!
Anko Sensei!
Let’s get moving…
lt’s already morning.
Oh no!
The ships collecting funds
are in danger…!
We’ve got to follow them
right away!
With that ship!
Okay, let’s go!
You’ve had no contact
from the Ninja of the Leaf Village?
They were told to
accompany the ship.
What in the world happened?
Captain, we just received
communication.
I see!
That’s what I expect
from elite Ninja!
It seems they finished
the suppression of
the Demon of the Ocean last night.
– Oh… 					– Oh!
Excellent…
So now the ships are safe.
Of course.
Men, take your positions!
We’ll depart.
Despair: A Fractured Heart
Be careful of the reef!
I don’t see any ships that look like
those that collect funds in the port.
How could they depart without us?
Have they already fallen
into Amachi’s scheme…?
C-Captain Hitode…
What happened?!
There’s something there!
The bottom of the ship…!
Confirm the enemy!
R-Roger!
Huh? What?
Full toward port!
I can’t steer!
What?
It’s no good. It won’t move.
We’re going to hit, everyone.
Grab onto something!
This must be the attack from
the Demon of the Ocean?
Thank you for working hard
for transporting the funds.
I saw you while ago!
Identify yourself!
If you hand this ship over
without resistance,
I will save your life.
Don’t mess with me!
– It’s the Demon of the Ocean…
– A monster!
Demon Illusion: Fire Jutsu.
Wh-What…?
Th-That’s…
It’s fire torture…!
Yoroi, take care of the rest.
What?!
I’m your opponent!
Everyone, hang in there!
Don’t be so nasty!
We meet again, weirdo!
Excuse me, but I still have
something to ask you.
What are you doing, Isaribi!
Cut it out already!
Keep this up and you’ll really turn
into the Demon of the Ocean!
Do it, Isaribi.
Your opponent is right here.
You said that Orochimaru left
that research facility
half a month ago…
Where did he go?
I don’t know…
Now that you mention it,
Orochimaru had a kid in tow.
I heard that the kid is
really excellent, unlike you.
Sasuke Uchiha.
Something about you
just wasn’t enough.
That’s why you were abandoned,
I guess.
Isarirbi?!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Isaribi…
I bet you still understand
what I’ve been saying to you, Isaribi!
Don’t you care a bit after
tormenting everyone this much?
No.
I think nothing of…
even bringing you down…
That’s a lie!
It doesn’t matter to me
who gets injured…
or who drowns…
I’m satisfied as long as
I can return to being a human!
It’s about time to come
to yourself!
I understand painfully
enough how you feel…
But…doing that…
lt’s not good!
Isaribi, you saved me.
You have a kind heart!
Pretty good for a Medical Ninja.
Shut up!
I’m a little surprised that
you had enough time
to take your eyes off…
D-Damn it!
You’re too confident…
You’re useless.
How long you think
you’ll be doing this?
Amachi…
He’s just a kid.
Why can’t you finish him off
right away?
Sorry. But…
I can’t take it anymore.
Get out of my way!
Bring it on.
I’ll kill a damn monster like you!
Monster? Me?
That’s right!
You so easily injure
and kill people.
You’re a monster wearing
human skin!
Hey! What’s so funny!
If so, what then?
I’m not some half-monster
like Isaribi…
I’m…
further refined than her and
fully integrated for combat use!
You…!
Amachi…!
Get out of my way!
You’re an almost-dead guinea pig…
What are you doing?!
Even though we were supposed to dissect
and use her as material for experiments,
we took pity on her and
kept her alive.
But after all,
she’s terribly ungrateful and useless.
What’s wrong…kid?
You! You’re not only
a monster in body and soul!
In truth, you’re scum!
C’mere… I’ll play with you.
Bastard!
Idiot!
Hah, amateurish…
Not over yet!
Shadow Clone Jutsu
No matter how many times
you come at me,
you’ll get the same thing!
Well, what’s wrong, little guy?
You’re going to come again, huh?
Yeah, of course!
Until you change Isaribi back…
I’ll come at you again and again.
Water Style:
Great Cannonball Jutsu!
What’s wrong,
you’re done already?
Give it up already, kid!
I told you!
Until I take Isaribi back…
I absolutely will not…quit!
Why…
would you go that
far to save me?
I can’t keep up with the farce.
Come on! Sea Monster!
Do it…Sea Monster!
Hey! Let go of me, you!
Let me tell you that almost all of
Sea Monster’s body is made of water.
You can say it's like
a moving Water Prison Jutsu.
Naruto!
Damn…
You’re stupid.
Do you think something
like that will affect it at all?
Do you understand, Isaribi?
I am the only one
who can save you.
Now, finish them off!
What’s wrong?
You want to turn back into
a human, don’t you?
Then do as I say!
It’s no good…
I can’t let Isaribi…
go to…that world…
This feeling…
SEAL
What?! What are these
extraordinary Chakras?
S-Sea Monster!
Isaribi…
I will never let Isaribi
go over there!
What are you…?!
Naruto…?!
He’s the same as you.
Same as me…?!
Yes…
The Nine-Tailed Fox Spirit,
who long ago attacked our village,
is sealed inside Naruto.
And there was a time
when everyone in the village
treated him like a monster.
And…
And even so, he works so hard,
everybody approves of him.
I understand painfully enough
how you feel…
But…doing that…
lt's not good.
Those words…were true…
Naruto!
You bastard!
The wind blows, Ah…
The pain,
The memories won’t disappear
What should be brought along?
Assemble them into a piece.
There is no second chance, never
How foolish it is to throw away
Acting so innocently, Ah…
The images.
It probably will not end
Burn that love-filled heart,
Sail across a thousand dreams
Running freely
To take hold of the world in hand
The clouds scatter
The sun sets yet again
The solo parade begins to move.
Adventure, Lucky Day, Heart Beat, Rising,
Decisive, Encounter, Life, Mutual Love
Oh, I was able to do
the Chief Toad summoning
for the first time in a while!
Now, prepare yourself,
you flabby jerk!
Tomorrow will never come
for you again!
This itches!
What? It’s not a good time
to be getting scared now!
It really itches.
Now, Chief Toad,
take him out good.
Naruto, summoning me in
salt water like this!
I could take your life for this!
What…?!
Next time: “Battle at Sea:
The Power Unleashed!”