I want to try and gather
the unrestrained winds
I’ll run toward the horizon,
alongside the wave crests
I’ve made my decision,
even if there’s a long way to go
on that road.
I’ll continue towards the future I’ve planned
Time rushes us
The heartbeat speeds up
When I woke in the middle of a dream
I kept searching for that same light
Under the shining star-lit sky with
countless constellations and shadows
There was something beyond that…
What were you gazing at?
Look, Papa!
What is it, Kunihisa?
Look, it’s sparkly and pretty.
That’s right, Kunihisa.
Even though it’s so pretty,
how can it have no value…
That’s horrible, isn’t it, Papa?
Impossible!
Celebirty Ninja Art: Money Style Jutsu!
A-Are you serious, Grandma Tsunade!
Calm down!
Sorry, I’ll calm down.
Since he is an important person,
I believe there is no one appropriate
for the job other than you.
Finally… Finally a mission
appropriate for my abilities.
Guarding an important person…
lt has such a nice ring to it!
Listen seriously!
Gotcha.
Okay, about this mission…
Shizune.
Yes!
The details are written in
those documents.
His name’s Kunihisa,
he lives in the capital.
He’s the heir of
an old acquaintance of mine.
Your acquaintance, Grandma Tsunade?
Yes, his father’s name is Kunijiro.
He made his fortune in one generation.
He’s a successful jeweler.
The heir of a jeweler…
Hey, Papa?
Is this real, too?
Of course it’s real, little Kuni.
So, is that and that and this
and the one over there too?!
Of course, little Kuni!
Ninja! Ninja! Ninja!
Suddenly my motivation is boosted!
I’ll do it! I’ll do that mission!
So where is this Kunihisa at,
Grandma Tsunade?!
Come in!
– Ninja! Ninja! Ninja!
– Wow! What’s this brat?
Ninja! Ninja! Ninja! Ninja!
Ninja?
Don’t add that question mark at
the end of your sentence, don’t!
So it must be you!
You are the kid who’s going with Kunihisa
to play be a-Ninja-for-a-day…
I’ll leave him to you, then.
What? Be a Ninja for a day…?
My little Kuni really admires Ninja,
and he aggravates me by saying
nothing but Ninja everyday.
Grandma Tsunade!
Wasn’t this
the guarding-important-person mission?!
What are you talking about?
I did say he’s an important person,
but didn’t say a word about
guarding him.
I was fooled! Grandma!
Naruto Uzumaki!
I order you to play be
a-Ninja-for-a-day with Kunihisa!
Damn… That’s a dirty trick, Grandma!
Oh, there’s one more thing.
I added your regular missions
as a service.
Oh, that’s cruel, Grandma Tsunade!
Clean the pond, repair the bridge,
get rid of the savage pig,
and…
It turns out that babysitting is just added
to the regular D-rank missions!
Ninja, Ninja.
Watch this, Kunihisa!
I’ll teach you the awesomeness
of a Ninja.
Hey, awesome Naruto! Awesome!
It’s “be-a-Ninja-for-a-day,” isn’t it?
So Kunihisa, you gather garbage
from over there, too.
Okay!
Oh, that’s right.
Don’t go into the marsh.
This marsh is bottomless,
so once you’re caught,
you can’t get out.
Huh, what?
– Oh, no, Young Master is in trouble!
– Naruto!
What are you doing?!
You fool! I’ll save you,
so you stay right there!
Fool! I’ll be fine.
You’ll be fine?
I can handle this kind of simple task
with my Ninjutsu.
Ninjutsu?
– Oh no! Young Master!
– Oh, no!
Alligator snapping turtle, Piranha, Toad!
Money Style:
Help Me Jutsu!
What?!
– Yay! 					– Mine!
Wha--?! Wh-Wh-Wha--?!
I’m fine!
What are you guys doing?!
If you want money hurry up
and rescue me.
What good would increasing
the victims do?
Hey, Kunihisa.
Huh?
Who are they?
Oh, them…
Papa employs them and
they protect me if I get into trouble.
Really.
That’s right, for example…
There!
See!
What do you mean “see”?!
Is it okay?
I said it’s okay!
Really, really okay?
What are you so freaked out about?
lt’s okay!
But still, it’s scary!
Cut the bull and come here now!
R-Right!
But just before that…
Ninja Art: Scapegoat Jutsu!
See? It’s fine.
C’mere, quick!
If I get on it next,
I think it might break…
Let’s check out a bunch more.
I’m not finished yet! More of you!
Go!
What the--?!
Just as I thought.
I thought I was gonna die.
What were you doing, Kunihisa?!
What would have happened if
I’d got on the bridge like that?
C’mon you!
Okay everyone, your compensation!
Here!
I’m telling you, stop that!
That kid…
He’s got money, huh, Big Brother.
Yeah… And his main guard
is a single Genin.
Big Brother, it’s decided.
Yeah.
What’s next?
Get rid of the savage pig
who appears in the field ahead.
Okay! I’ll do my best!
What the--?!
A savage pig…?
More like a monster!
Crap!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
That’s cool!
Naruto!
Okay! It’s my turn this time!
F-Fool! What are you doing?
Hurry up and escape!
Here I go!
Ninja Art: Money Clone Jutsu!
Money Clone?!
Huh?!
Hey, you ugly savage pig!
Starting now,
I, Kunihisa, will punish you!
Go!
Go! Get him! There!
What, nobody wants to eat your meat!
You dummy!
He ordered all of this!
What?!
I didn’t want to,
but he forced me to…
Huh? W-Wait…
That’s a lie. It’s a misunderstanding!
Those are false charges!
Forgive me! Naruto…
I… How should I put this…?
really hate guys like you!
Why are you getting so testy?
Geez, poor people just can’t help
that they have short tempers…
This’ll put you back in a good mood.
Take as much as you want!
Enough already!
I’m telling you to stop
doing stuff like that!
Why?
It’s a big mistake to think that
anything can be resolved with money!
There are times when you have
to use your own power!
There hasn’t been anything that
I couldn’t do with money so far!
You… Are you always like this?
With that personality,
you can’t make friends!
It’s okay ‘cause
I can buy friends with money!
What…?
You… Buy friends? You mean…
If I give ‘em money,
everybody will be my friend!
Kunihisa…
That’s why I hate country Ninjas.
They’re cheap and stink of poverty…
Stupid!
Oh, please wait, Master Kunihisa!
Running made me hungry.
Take this and buy a boxed lunch!
There’s nothing like a store
to buy lunch around here.
Well, snacks will be fine!
There’s no convenient store
or candy shop…
You’re useless!
This is why I hate the country!
Stupid Naruto.
What’s that?
Oh, Young Master!
Oh!
Little fish, little fish!
Let’s eat!
The kid must be stupid to get
caught in this cheap trick.
Don’t you agree, Bro?
Yeah!
Huh? Naruto?!
Aw man,
you’re really high maintenance.
Those two guys just now…
They were going to catch you!
They were plotting a kidnapping, whatever…
Whatever…?
I’m often a target,
because I have money.
Often a target…? You…
More importantly,
I want to eat more fish!
Go find a shop and buy some.
You… Still think you can do
anything with money?
All right, watch this!
Yay! Awesome! Awesome Naruto!
How’s that?!
You can just get things using
your own power without using money.
Even… without using money?
Damn!
He attacked us by surprise,
that cowardly bastard.
I’ll give it back to him doubled!
Well, wait…
If we do it thoughtlessly,
we’ll just get creamed again.
So what do we do?
We’ll use that thing.
That thing…?
Look close at the movement
of the fish…
Aim for the instant when
they fall after jumping up.
Don’t get hasty.
Now!
Oh!
That was close!
O-One more time, Naruto!
I’ll get the Kunai knife,
so one more time!
Master Kunihisa!
– It’s deep over there!
– Please be careful!
I know, I know…
Where did it go?
I think it’s in this area, but…
I won’t let you get away this time!
You guys…
We hired these guys with
the money you threw away.
It means that now,
they’re on our side…
Hey, you guys! I’ll pay you double
what those guys did!
So be on my side…
Wh-What the…?
Looks like you’ve run out of money.
How about you guys over there?
Wanna join us?
We’ll pay up stacks of money.
Humph! These guys have been
with me for a long time.
That paltry sum won’t…
We’re not going along with
your selfish acts any longer!
Y-You guys?!
No! I don’t like it!
Annoying brat. I’ll have to tie you up
so you won’t move.
What are you doing, Kunihisa?!
Naruto, I… I…
It’s fine already!
Hey you… I’ll pay you double what
you get for your mission.
Won’t you hand that brat over to us?
We’re just going to demand
ransom money from his parents is all.
We won’t kill him.
Relax and hand him over.
I-It’s not enough?
Here, how about this?
Naruto…
Kunihisa! Ride on my back!
O-Okay.
S-Still not enough, huh? Here!
That’s all of it! Take it!
Like I said…
It’s a big mistake to think
you can obtain anything with money!
Crap!
After them!
Listen! Hold on tightly Kunihisa.
Okay!
Damn! I can’t move
with him on my back!
I can’t see the bottom, Naruto…
Go!
Okay! You go on ahead.
What?! Go on ahead?!
There he is! Let’s get him!
– Yeah! 					– Yeah!
Wh-What are you doing?!
It’s okay! Hurry up and jump!
I-I can’t… I’m scared, Naruto!
It’s not scary, c’mon!
I can’t… I’m scared…!
Damn it!
Do it!
Naruto!
Well, you’re coming with me!
Hurry! Kunihisa!
B-But……
It’s okay… You can definitely do this!
Believe it!
Prepare yourself!
No way!
Go Kunihisa!
Oh, Big Brother!
Huh?! Kunihisa?!
It hurts!
I’m going to clean those guys out
and then I’ll be right over!
So wait a second!
D-Daruto…
D-Darudo!
The wall’s collapsing… Escape!
How long are you guys gonna be
on top of me!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Wh-Wh-What’s going on?!
I have to go to him!
There are times when you have
to use your own power!
Use my own…power!
You can just get things using
your own power with out using money.
Even without money…
with my own power!
I can…do this!
Just one step short!
Naruto!
Kunihisa!
No! A little bit more!
– We did it! 					– We did it!
All right!
I-It hurts but…
I’m scared but…
I…!
You… What a face?!
Kunihisa…
You did a good job!
Darudo!
Wha--?!
Hold on, don’t drip snot!
But Naruto!
Stop it!
Well… See ya!
Yeah! Next time you come play
at my house, Naruto!
Okay!
Really… You took great care of him.
Thank you!
Yeah, well…
Well then…
Yes…
Papa, Papa!
What is it, little Kuni?
Look, it’s sparkly and pretty…
But it has no value,
it’s just a marble, little Kuni.
That’s true, Papa…
But…
As long as it's pretty, it doesn't matter
whether it's valueless, right?
The wind blows, Ah…
The pain,
The memories won’t disappear
What should be brought along?
Assemble them into a piece.
There is no second chance, never
How foolish it is to throw away
Acting so innocently, Ah…
The images.
It probably will not end
Burn that love-filled heart,
Sail across a thousand dreams
Running freely
To take hold of the world in hand
The clouds scatter
The sun sets yet again
The solo parade begins to move.
Adventure, Lucky Day, Heart Beat, Rising,
Decisive, Encounter, Life, Mutual Love
All right, I’m fired up!
Our mission this time is a treasure hunt!
But your recent low mission
success rate concerns me.
No need to worry.
We’ve got a map, so it’ll be a cinch!
I’ve thought about it, you see…
No need to think, believe it!
If you fail this mission…
It’ll be okay, I tell you!
You’ll all start over again
from the Academy!
What?!
Next time: "The Treasure Hunt is On!"