Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost, let’s start walking
One more time
Are you really happy
when you're always meeting
to someone's expectations?
Even if you change to
who you really wanna be
Will you always have a great smile?
Dreaming of only “the beginning,”
I wake up
and someday, I'll live on my own.
Yes, precious things are never in shape
You never know what it is
when you get it or lose it
Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost,
let's start walking
One more time
So what’s up, Temari?
He’s close. He’s just right there.
Dang it! What should we do?
Leave it to me.
That was close.
What was that noise?
An explosion…
Perhaps it was a trap set for Sasuke.
I wonder if he’s okay.
Don’t worry…
He wouldn’t get bumped off so easily.
I sure hope so.
Now then, shall we get started?
Before that, I must have you both
return to your original forms.
Please prepare yourself,
Sarutobi Sensei.
An Unrivaled Match:
Hokage Battle Royale!
With every moment,
they are looking more lively…
What is that…Jutsu?
Reanimation.
It’s a Forbidden Summoning Jutsu
that can bring the dead back to this world.
The cost of a regular Summoning Jutsu
is that it uses the blood of the caster.
But I’ve heard that with this Jutsu,
in order to summon
a dead soul to this world…
the body of a living person is sacrificed
as a container for the soul.
Then, the bodies of those two
are of the sacrificed…
Right…
Perhaps dust and dirt cover
the sacrificial body
and take on the original form
of the summoned soul.
And by way of the charm
embedded in the head,
the personality of the soul is killed
and it morphs into no more
than a killing puppet.
They’re complete.
They look like how they used
to look more than ever.
Do you know the joy and sense
of accomplishment
of hurting one whom
you once called Sensei?
I prepared this scenario
so that you might know that joy.
So please enjoy it.
Lord Hokage!
Even if the shape and form
are the same…
they’re neither the First Hokage
nor the Second!
I…know!
Here I go!
Fire Style: Fire Dragon Flame Bombs.
Water Style: Water Wall.
No way!
To be able to set into motion that level
of Water Style in a place with no water.
I can’t believe it.
True to the title of the previous Hokage.
Water Style: Water Shock Wave!
Earth Style: Mud Wall.
Same mighty strength as always.
Having two of you is quite a challenge,
as might be expected…
This is bad.
This is a Hidden Jutsu of the First Hokage.
Hidden Wood Style Jutsu:
Deep Forest Emergence.
His Chakra became a source for life.
Wow… So this is the legendary
Wood Style Ninjutsu of the First Hokage
who brought turbulent times under control
and built the Leaf Village.
You’re finally caught…eh, Sensei.
Okay. Everyone’s here, right?
Okay everyone, let’s evacuate quickly.
Don’t rush and don’t panic!
What’s the matter, Konohamaru?
Does your stomach hurt or something?
No…it’s not that.
Ninja Art: Summoning Jutsu.
Appear!
Monkey King Enma.
Humph…
Something pesky has appeared, eh?
Old Monkey Enma.
Orochimaru…
I knew this would happen.
You’re pathetic, Sarutobi…
lt’s because you didn’t kill him back then.
I’m going to do it now!
It’s too late.
Please…Enma!
The Adamantine Nyoi.
Take care of him.
Don’t let him transform into that!
Okay… Got it!
Transform!
All right.
Wow… What level of Ninjutsu battle!
This is Hokage level!
Oh well…
Things have finally gotten interesting.
That's one of his Snake Swords.
Let’s do it, Enma!
No matter how strong the body,
the Snake Sword still hurts.
You’re mine!
Lord Hokage!
So foolish…
To think you’d strike without even
using the Shadow Clone Jutsu.
No, that’s not it.
It's not that he didn't use it.
He can’t use it.
The amount of Chakra the Third Hokage
has differs from the past.
The Shadow Clone Jutsu that
evenly disperses Chakra,
if things go wrong,
would be like throwing away Chakra.
Sure enough, is it age?!
Are you okay, Sensei?
Please hang in there.
You are called…
“the Professor who knows and uses all
of the Jutsu existent in Leaf Village,” right?
Please don’t disappoint me too much.
Please get up, Lord Hokage…!
And please save the Leaf Village!
Lord Hokage!
Fool… It is too late.
Sarutobi, what’s wrong?
You’re not your usual self.
It’s as if you’re good for nothing…
What are you hesitating for?
Now’s the time to draw the line.
Orochimaru…
You…fool!
This is the end.
I’ll snap your neck.
As I thought…
It looks like there’s no point if
I don’t do something about the soul itself
that is bound by the Reanimation.
If so, all I can do is to use…
the Fourth Hokage’s Jutsu.
Lord First Hokage, Lord Second Hokage,
please forgive me for using that Jutsu!
Sensei…it seems you’re out of breath.
You’ve gotten old, haven’t you?
I’ve never seen such a pained look.
What’s so funny?
It’s quite sad…
Old age beats even you,
once renowned as the god of Shinobi.
What’s that…?!
What the heck is going on?
Who the heck is that youth?
Who the heck are you?!
Is it so sudden you can’t tell?
It’s me. Orochimaru.
It can’t be…
Have you completed that
Forbidden Jutsu?!
You’re a truly frightening,
inhuman monster!
I finally caught up.
This is as far as you guys go.
Dang it!
Sasuke Uchiha.
I won’t let you get away now.
Everyone makes mistakes
lt’s nothing to be ashamed about
Don’t let this scar be for naught
Walk with a smile
Yes, breathe in the air
Lift your face to the sky and jump
If it rains, take a break
Go where the wind takes you
So many regrets
Don’t let this scar be for naught
Let’s go carve the badges in our chest
Yes, it’s Show Time, life begins now.
Everyone makes mistakes
It’s nothing to be ashamed about
Don’t let this scar be for naught
Walk with a smile
Transform sadness into the wind
and continue to forge on
Forge on strong
Orochimaru…
a genius Ninja who appeared
during the war-torn era
and one of a kind in decades.
I wanted to believe that this individual
would succeed my strength and will.
But my naiveté created this situation.
I will bury you now and
correct my old mistake.
Next time, “A Mistake from the Past:
A Face Revealed!”