Hey boys, listen up!
Humans aren’t such a big deal
Who needs tomorrow anyway,
so don’t hide your fists
You’re not old enough
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
Hey boys, you’re the only ones
who can pull the trigger in your heart
All the kids said
We’re living in this senseless, ridiculous,
awesome world right at this moment,
All the kids said
Don’t forget every truth or lie
We’re way too young to die
In this empty town lined with empty faces
All the kids took off
into this windless night
Because they want to change something
A Town of Outlaws!
The Shadow of the Fuma Clan
It seems that the most bustling traveler’s
town in the Land of Rice Paddies
is at the bottom of these mountains.
You’re going to weird places again
in the name of investigation,
aren’t you, Pervy Sage?!
Please stop it already!
We had a rough time shaking
off the bodyguards from the rip-off bar.
I understand your point,
but there’s no other way to find
Village Hidden in the Sound.
Gee, I don’t like it either, but…
This is truly a problem…
But we have to do things
we don’t like… Right?!
Okay, let’s go!
Naruto, Sakura,
don’t drag your feet!
Investigation, investigation!
What a pain.
He looks like he’s having fun.
He hasn’t learned at all.
Fuma Alley
– Oww! 					– That's my line!
This is even rougher than
the traveler’s town before.
Let’s just take a pass on this place
and find Village Hidden in the Sound.
Say…
I don’t have any more money.
I don’t have any more money either!
Here!
You guys go get some food with that
and wait in the temple
on the outskirts of town.
Information accumulates
in this kind of place,
but it’s not good for you guys to see.
I’ll sacrifice myself and check it out.
He’s a surprisingly nice person…
Sakura… You’re still so naïve.
Where should I investigate first?
Gee, how rough…
lnvestigations are painful.
Let’s leave the Pervy Sage be
and check somewhere else.
What’s the matter, Sakura?
I don’t think…
Sasuke’s in this land anymore.
What’s the matter?!
We won’t know that if
we don’t investigate!
Yeah, but…
Our opponent is Orochimaru.
Of course, things might not go easily.
But you know…
But I’m sure we’ll find him!
Right.
Naruto!
You’re…the one from before?!
This kid’s…hurt…
You…?
Naruto!
Substitution, huh…?
We let them get away.
Don’t worry…
My cute children
are making a silver trail for us.
They can’t escape from us now…
It seems those two are
petty Ninja from somewhere.
But getting involved with us
has sealed their fate.
It’s unfortunate for them…
The objective of those who sneak into
this land is Lord Orochimaru, anyway.
Sure enough, the skin of
a young woman is supple.
You’re mean!
Eh? Oh, sorry sorry.
By the way, have you guys heard
rumors about the Sound Village?
The Sound Village?
I’ve never heard the name
of such a village.
I’ll tip you handsomely if you tell me.
But I really don’t know.
I’ve never heard of it.
I’ve heard of it!
One of my regulars knows
a lot about it.
Wanna come?
Yeah.
His home is in the back of this alley.
Trapped like a rat.
What, it’s a seedy old man!
Hey! He’s got money, right?
Yeah. I saw it with my own eyes.
You punks! Stop the idle chatter
and take care of him now!
Right, boss!
Getting infatuated with girls has sealed
your fate! Rest in peace!
Ninja Art: 					Needle Jizo.
You punk…
I’m in a hurry…
I think it’d be best if you
answer compliantly
whether or not you know
about Hidden Sound Village.
You’re a fool if I look like
a compliant person to you!
You a Ninja?
If so?
Interesting!
We’ve reduced ourselves to
being thieves,
but we’re a somewhat
famous Shinobi clan around here!
Instead of taking your life,
I could hire you if you want!
A Ninja, huh…
Then I don’t need to go easy on you.
Don’t be acting like a big shot, old man!
Shut up, you squirt!
A Ninja refers to one who endures.
Those who couldn’t endure
their hunger pangs
and resort to use their diligently
studied Jutsu for stealing
are not called Ninja!
I won’t let that pass!
Thinking we’re fellow Shinobi,
we took pity on you.
Acting all conceited!
Regret after being sliced in two!
Fuma Ninja Blade Zanbato!
Rasengan!
You punk! How dare you
do that to the boss!
We won’t let you do
any more than that!
Oh?
Hold it, you guys!
I didn’t know you were so good!
That Jutsu just now…
I sense you must be
a person of stature!
If it’s all right,
may I ask you your name?
If you don’t know, then I shall tell you!
Women become infatuated
with his sex appeal.
He’s strong against Shinobi,
but has a soft spot for women!
He exists in Village Hidden in the Leaves…
And made his name known…
Master Jiraiya, that’s me!
What?!
You guys bow your heads
and beg for your lives!
We’ll all be killed!
– Yes, sir! 					– Yes, sir!
Although we didn’t know,
being so rude to Master Jiraiya,
reputed as one of the Legendary
Sannin of the Leaf Village!
We beg for your forgiveness!
So my name’s known in this land, too…
Well, it’s okay.
So is it true that you know about
Village Hidden in the Sound?
Yes! There were many Ninja clans
in the Land of Rice Paddies,
including us Fuma.
We divided up the roles
amongst ourselves
and the Ninja of this land
were doing well in their own way.
Until that man appeared…
Who was that man?
It’s regrettable to even speak
of that name…
It was Orochimaru!
It’s okay! Rest easy!
If germs get into the wound
and you get tetanus,
you won’t be saved.
But fortunately, I have medicine,
so let me treat you.
They’re not coming.
Just show us your wound.
Well, huh?
Naruto, go wait outside
till my treatment is done.
164.01	01:37:53:04	01:37:53:24	Huh?
Why do I have to be
the only one chased out?!
Jeez!
I guess it can’t be helped.
Don’t peek!
I know.
Okay, show me your wound.
How mean…
To hit me out of the blue…?
Whoa, interesting.
Naruto! You can come in!
What?!
A cute girl?
Sakura! This girl!
Who the heck is this girl?!
How dense. It’s the Ninja
from a moment ago.
Come to think of it…
Why…?
I am Sasame Fuma.
Sasame… Why were you being
chased by those guys?
If you like, try talking about it.
We might be able to help.
They were the Sound Ninja protecting
Orochimaru’s residence.
What?!
I’m sorry for mistaking you guys as
one of them the other day.
That doesn’t matter!
We’re also looking for Orochimaru!
Would you please give us the details?
Okay…
It all started with the Feudal Lord
of the Land of Rice Paddies
launching an attack on
a neighboring land
in an attempt to expand the territory.
The Land of Rice Paddies is a small land…
And there aren’t that many Shinobi.
It was a foolhardy attack.
Losing was expected…
And the Shinobi clans of this land
who participated in
the losing battle went to ruin…
We the Fuma Clan as well.
I hear that among
the surviving Shinobi,
there are those who have left the land
and those who have
stooped to become thieves.
Even so, we’ve lived believing
in a restoration of the clan
and continued to live hiding
in the shadows.
At that time, an emissary of Village Hidden
in the Sound appeared before us
attempting to create the first full-scale
Shinobi village in the Land of Rice Paddies.
The emissary of
the Sound Village said…
My master Orochimaru is
gathering all sorts of Jutsu!
He has taken an interest
in your Jutsu well.
Depending on your work,
you might be given the chance
to serve the Feudal Lord!
My cousin Arashi…
was an up-and-coming star
for the restoration of the clan…
Arashi as a representative of the clan
headed for Village Hidden in
the Sound together with the emissary.
But…
And then…?
We waited for a notice from Arashi, but…
There is no word from him, huh?
Damn it!
He was tricked by that Orochimaru!
Naruto!
Oh…!
Uh, even so, your cousin Arashi
might be safe…
We don’t know, right?
And so…and so…
Idiot…!
I’m going to save Arashi!
I have a small body and
my power is weak.
So no matter what I did…
I did nothing but become a hindrance
even in Ninjutsu training…
But Arashi always saved me!
Everyone in the village has
already given up, but…
So I’ll find Village Hidden
in the Sound alone…
And so you were chased by
the Sound Ninja, right?
This time, it’s my turn to save Arashi!
Sasame!
I…I want to be of help to Arashi!
Naruto!
Yeah…I know!
We have to go to Village of the Sound
to bring back Sasuke anyway, so!
Now instead of one,
it’s just that there are two guys
for us to bring back.
I’ll save your cousin, Sasame!
Right!
Eew! A spider…
What’s this?!
Naruto!
Wha--! What’s this?!
Ninja Art: Wind Spiders!
My cute children made a path
for me out of silver thread
and told me where you guys
were going.
All three of you together will descend
into hell while bearing the secret!
Naruto! It’s the Ventriloquism Jutsu!
He’s scattering his voice
to multiple directions
and covering up location and number!
I get it! I leave this girl to you, Sakura!
Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Okay! Bring it on from anywhere!
It’s a large number,
but it’s just Clone Jutsu.
No. Look closely, Jigumo!
The threads are getting tangled.
All of the clones are tangible?!
Shadow clones?!
If so… Kagero!
Understood…
Come out!
Borne to be born, lived to live,
one sunrise and one sunset…
The life of a mayfly lasts but one day.
Thinking that such a fleeting life
is pitiable is, in fact, pitiable…
Know that I’m at my best
when living in the dark and
deep in the ground!
Ninja Art:
Ant Lion Jutsu!
When I recalled the parts one by one,
I felt as though
I had understood everything
Faded words which I kept so close to me
Speechless nights, a hint of warmth,
and this distant yearning for you
I live, simply repeating this cycle
Held in my two hands
A droplet of time
Softly clutching forgotten memories
Lost words
I’ll keep these thoughts…
Darn it! What a pesky bunch!
But I won’t be done in so easily!
I have to kick that Orochimaru jerk’s butt
and bring back Sasuke and
Sasame’s cousin!
It doesn’t matter if you guys
are powerhouses!
I’ll kick all of your butts,
so bring it on from anywhere!
Next episode, “Pure Betrayal,
and a Fleeting Plea!”