Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
The distance created between us
became too big,
because we were always together
Your honest reply, “See you…”
coming from that brash mouth
makes it sadder.
If you are in an unfamiliar town, crying
Then I want to deliver you a smile,
even if I’m not by your side
Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
I can feel it so close,
Our two hearts
Please, Sensei!
– What?! 					– What?!
Whoa, my heart, my heart!
Huh? There's nothing wrong.
Hey, it's you again.
To think you'd transform into Kurenai
with a Transformation Jutsu.
Hey, what the heck was that earlier?
Shut up! For your sake,
don't be nosing around needlessly.
Hey!
You're Yakumo. Right?
I want to ask you something
about Kurenai Sensei!
D-Damn it!
This is…the Academy's hallway.
Sensei, please!
Yakumo's Sealed Power
Why am I no good?!
Kurenai Sensei?
I want to become a Ninja,
no matter what!
I must become one!
I told you to give up.
No!
Then I’ll just have to perform
a Sealing Jutsu
and seal your power.
Huh?
Huh?!
Kurenai Sensei!
Why?!
S-Sakura. Umm, where am I?!
As for me,
what am I doing lying here?!
Oh yeah! Kurenai Sensei
got stabbed
and my heart leapt out
of my chest and…
No, that’s not it.
Where’s that girl?
Where’s Yakumo?
It seems you don’t remember at all.
You got caught breaking
into a mountain cottage
under special security!
Huh…?!
The Anbu Black Ops are in action,
so you should be thankful
you’re alive!
Oh yeah!
The dream I just had…
lt was strangely real.
No doubt it was the girl
in the mountain cottage!
What’re you blabbing about?!
I’ll inject you with a stimulant
if you don’t knock it off.
I can’t be doing stuff like this!
Hold it!
The medicine hasn’t worn off, yet!
Sensei! Kurenai Sensei!
Kurenai’s already gone out.
What?!
You’ve gone to the trouble
of getting up early.
So how about joining me for
an early-morning marathon?
This isn’t the time for that!
Morning marathons are great!
Marathons purge the sweat
and impurities built up
in your body from a night of sleep.
More importantly,
where did Kurenai Sensei go?!
Come to think of it,
she said something about going
to visit someone…
Something about a student
she took care of in the past
being in poor health…
Huh? She went to see Yakumo!
Then at least join me for
some morning exercise!
Morning exercise purges the sweat
and impurities built up
in your body from a night of sleep…
Kurenai Sensei!
Whoa?!
I have something I want to ask you,
Kurenai Sensei.
Naruto, don’t stick your nose
into my business any further.
Yesterday I went to see Yakumo!
I don’t know if it was
on account of that,
but I just had a strangely real dream!
A dream…?
Yeah.
You said to Yakumo that you were
going to use a Sealing Jutsu
if she wouldn’t give up
becoming a Ninja…
Sorry, but I’m in a hurry…
H-Hey. Wait!
It doesn’t concern you…
Yes, it does!
Hinata, Kiba and Shino are
all troubled
because you said you were
going to quit!
Doesn’t the fact that
you’re quitting Squad Eight
have something to do with
that girl Yakumo?!
What you saw wasn’t just a dream…
What…?!
I used a Sealing Jutsu and
took away a student’s power!
No way. That couldn’t be!
It happened over a year ago…
By my own hand,
I crushed the dream of a girl…
I tutored individually named Yakumo…
who was trying to become
a practitioner of Genjutsu.
No way!
I don’t deserve to have
the lives of the Genin
in Squad Eight entrusted to me.
But why…?
Now, get out of my way!
That’s the end of this conversation.
No way…
But I still have stuff I want to ask you…!
I have no choice.
What's happening?!
They won’t come off!
Kurenai Sensei, that’s just cruel!
We’re already surrounded…
Make emergency contact
with the village…
Yes, sir.
There!
What?!
We’re counting on you!
Hurry…to the Hokage!
Yakumo… Come with us.
Geez, that Naruto.
The least he could do is thank me
for attending to him all night.
What?!
Isn’t it about tea time?
After you’ve taken care of
these documents!
Why’s there so much work?
It’s because you didn’t take care
of it lickety-split, Lady Tsunade.
It’s a carrier pigeon for
emergency contacts!
What?!
It’s from the mountain cottage
in Satomi Hill…
Something’s happened to Yakumo!
There’s a possibility that
a person being protected
by the Village Hidden in Leaves,
Yakumo Kurama, has been kidnapped.
Head for the mountain cottage in
Satomi Hill and secure Yakumo.
Yakumo Kurama…
As I recall, that’s the girl Kurenai
took custody of, right?
Yes, the only daughter of Murakumo
of the Kurama Clan head family.
Umm, what’s the Kurama Clan?
It’s natural that you guys wouldn’t know.
They were a distinguished family
that wielded considerable power
in the village,
but they’re just a shadow
of what they used to be.
The death of Murakumo
and his wife about a year ago
became the catalyst for that.
I hear that the clan fell apart
after that.
Does the kidnapping of the only
daughter of the head family mean
that the Kurama Clan’s
Secret Jutsu is being targeted?
Well…
According to the documents
handed down from
the Third Hokage,
it seems her latent powers as
a Genjutsu Ninja
are extremely dangerous…
In other words, she would make
for a powerful asset
if those powers can be awakened.
That means it wouldn’t
be surprising
if there were guys seeking
that power, huh?
After her parents died,
she was kept under
protective custody in the village.
All right. Leave it to me!
I won’t allow a girl to cry!
Might Guy,
the Leaf Village's Handsome Devil
will rescue her,
no matter what!
Sakura, you go with them as well.
– What?! 					– Huh?
Once we have her in custody,
we’ll need someone to look
after her condition.
Only one with experience as
a Medical Ninja can do this.
Y-Yes ma’am!
This mission is a chance
to show my master
the fruits of my training!
Ouch!
Ouch? Did you trip on a tree root
or something?
What’s this?!
N-Naruto…!
He fell asleep in a place like this?!
Nice, Akamaru!
Naruto…
He’s…caught in a Genjutsu!
– Huh? 					– Huh?
Release!
What…? Sakura…
Salty!
What the hell is this?!
I mean, was I asleep again?
What’re you babbling about?!
You were caught in a Genjutsu.
Genjutsu…
I was chasing after Kurenai Sensei
who was heading for
the Satomi mountain cottage
and I tried to get her to listen to me.
Satomi mountain cottage,
you say?
Then Kurenai went alone?
Yeah, probably.
Kurenai’s in danger
if she went without being aware
what’s happening!
Huh?
Something’s strange…
Someone’s here!
Damn it. Was it a mistake
to come alone…?
But I don’t have the time
to return to the village…
They’re most likely after…Yakumo.
What?!
Oh no!
Sorry, but I mustn’t allow you
to interfere with our work.
Wha--?!
You think you caught me with that?
What?!
You’re the one who’s caught!
The enemies are also practitioners
of Genjutsu.
I must not lose…
What’s this presence?!
They’re both caught in a Genjutsu.
Yakumo… Is that you, Yakumo?
So you were safe!
Help me!
It’s okay now, Yakumo.
I’ll protect you, no matter what.
Kurenai Sensei!
Release!
You were hit with
a reverse Genjutsu, eh?
I-I’m sorry.
Just what I’d expect from
a Jonin…
No, I should probably say Kurenai Yuhi…
Stay alert!
We should consider ourselves
as being under suspicion
by the Leaf Village.
– Yes, sir! 					– Yes, sir!
The two who took Yakumo
haven’t returned…
I guess somewhat violent action
can’t be avoided.
Although we come from
the same village…
we will get Yakumo,
no matter what the cost.
Understood?
– Yes, sir! 					– Yes, sir!
Oh!
What is it, Hinata?!
Did you see something?
The mountain cottage is
being attacked by someone.
There are four out front and four inside
the mountain cottage.
Are two of the people inside
the mountain cottage
Kurenai and Yakumo?
I bet that’s it!
Kurenai Sensei,
what the hell happened?!
Tell us!
The Key to the rusted heart’s door
Will always be smiling right near by
Even if rains of spears were to fall,
I will run through it
Because I want to find the joy
without a shape
This big dream of mine that
cannot be translated to words,
I will make it come true,
even if it were to deepen my wounds
We stand here today because of
what we believed through,
That is why I will continue running forward,
never looking away
Even if I’m told that
there is no bright future
I’ll change it right away,
lighting it with all my feeling
The wind is probably testing our hearts
In my heart, I gently grasped my hands
You are probably searching for
the answer to your tears
Your dream is always waiting near by,
with the answers in its hands
The Key to the rusted heart’s door
Will always be smiling right near by
I’m surprised…
Who would’ve thought that
the intruders would turn out
to be you people.
But whatever reasons you may have,
I won’t let you take Yakumo!
The Third Hokage entrusted
this child to me.
Even if you are experts in Genjutsu,
I will protect this child with
every ounce of strength I have in my body.
Next time: “Kurenai's Top-Secret Mission:
The Promise with the Third Hokage”