Connecting old words
that have been used up
I just want to convey
my simple thoughts
That day's faint wind blows away
at the castle ruins of yesterday
I'll laugh with you
and live for the moment
Still that incident
will continue to trouble you, right?
That's why it must be good-bye
Leaving nothing behind,
let us share what is left
In time, we'll realize
that it was everything
And sadness will touch our cheeks,
creating a river of tears
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex
and melting away
Heh! It’s over…
Losing is not an Option
What?!
Just barely…
That was a close one.
But…I was able to throw it off
just a little.
There’s no mistake.
He’s now realized the secret
of the Byakugan.
What’s the meaning of this?
How?!
How was he able to throw it
a whole six inches
from his vital point?!
I see… That Chakra!
He was emitting Chakra
the whole time
and covered the area surrounding him!
And in a wide range to that extent.
No wonder he was able
to detect the arrow and
throw off the trajectory of it.
But constantly emitting that
much Chakra is a death throe…
If he doesn’t go that far,
he can’t dodge.
In other words, there’s no mistake.
It’s as I hypothesized…
The arrow earlier was
totally invisible to him!
He doesn’t carry out useless attacks…
And from the results,
he accurately examines the information.
And…he’s also discovered
the weakness of my eyes…
Impressive.
Of all the enemies
I’ve fought until now,
this guy’s the strongest!
He has 360-degree sight.
And he unfailingly detects attacks
that penetrate the roughly
150-feeot circumference around him.
But for some reason,
there were Kunai Knives
he couldn’t evade completely.
Why couldn’t he evade them?
Because he couldn’t see them!
In other words, even his Visual Jutsu
has a slight blind spot!
Being unable to see Kunai Knives
entering that blind spot,
he’s unable to react.
So he was dealing with attacks
from the blind spot
with that defense technique.
And I analyzed all the attacks
I carried out
and grasped them perfectly.
Right behind his first thoracic vertebra…
there exists a blind spot expanding
from a very small point.
Indeed, if he moves and
doesn’t stabilize the blind spot,
it becomes difficult to aim there
with an arrow.
But such a trick…doesn’t fool me!
Gentle Fist is pointless if
you don’t come close to your enemy.
And you can’t afford to think about
approaching me at this point.
It’s about how to escape now…
Though whether you struggle or not,
you’re going to die anyway.
Heh… It seems you only
have a little Chakra left.
The fate of the small fry character
in an easy game
is to be destroyed right away!
It’s useless!
A thread?!
I see, with this thread…
This time, the trajectory was thrown off
slightly by the trees, huh?
If that’s the case…
I’ll add some rotation this time.
So even if it hits a tree,
it’ll just cut through and the trajectory
won’t be thrown off.
And as before…
I’ll control the arrow up until
150 feet away from him
using a thread with Chakra
flowing through.
I’ll take aim at the moving target…
and plunge the arrow into
the blind spot with a pinpoint attack!
He’s still standing up?
He’s strong…
He’s much stronger than me.
I hardly have any Chakra left now.
I probably won’t be able to evade
his next attack completely.
Is this it?
I’ll win no matter what!
Naruto… I wonder what you’d do.
I’ve had enough.
I can’t dodge it anyway.
He’s stopped moving…
Has he given up?
But just to make doubly sure…
Maximum destructive power
with 120% accuracy.
I’ve got him!
This is it.
Gentle Fist!
Wh-What? He still…?!
No! My attack just now
should’ve made the kill.
Substance with Chakra base…
It’s meaningless against Gentle Fist.
Gentle Fist…
I see, in his final moments,
he funneled the last Chakra
through the thread!
Eight crows…
Again I couldn’t see one of them.
What happened to him?
He damaged several of
my internal organs.
But…I can still move.
You failure…
I told you… I don’t know when to quit!
Why do you try to go against
your destiny that much?
Because I was called…a failure!
But if you’re going to say it’s futile,
you don’t have to do anything!
After I become the Hokage,
I’ll change Hyuga!
The Ninjutsu that you’re good at, huh?
I was careless…
Clone Jutsu was the Ninjutsu
I stunk at.
Don’t be whining about boring stuff
like destiny and what not,
and how it can’t be changed!
Unlike me,
you're not a failure.
Naruto…
Now it’s become the three of us…
Don’t worry about such things.
Both Choji and Neji will
catch up right away.
Choji had the trump card.
And I’ve fought Neji
in the Chunin exam, so I know…
Know what?
That he’s…a true genius. Believe it!
I cannot lose…
Whether he’s an enemy
much stronger than me…
or even if this body should fail me…
I cannot lose!
I have a reason why I cannot lose!
I’ve had a hard time of it this time.
I played too long…
Huh?
I can’t build up Chakra…
How? You should’ve
been instantly killed!
How come you’re alive?!
I couldn’t completely
evade it anyway.
So I was prepared to deliberately
take the hit.
And I knew of my own weakness
much more than you do…
There were eight crows, huh?
This Byakugan has a blind spot.
However, if I knew that your attack
would only come from there…
I could release my Chakra just
to that blind spot and detect the attack.
It’s not so difficult to make
a move of just a few inches
to throw off the aim.
I’d suffer a serious injury,
but instant death can be avoided.
So you took the hit deliberately…?
It doesn’t change the fact
that you’re going to die here.
How can you go that far?!
“Of all the enemies,”
you’re the strongest I’ve ever fought…
But, there’s a reason why I cannot lose.
Of all those I’ve ever fought,
the strongest one said this to me…
– Unlike me…you are not a failure!
He said that.
I’ve been called a genius all along.
So I cannot lose.
And for the sake of those guys
who believe
that this humdrum and small me
is a genius!
“The fate of the small fry character
in a game is to be destroyed right away.”
You said that, didn’t you?
Look at this situation!
Things like fate,
isn’t determined by someone!
I wonder…
You also look like
you’re going to die!
Neji, live.
More than anyone in the clan,
you’re the man loved most
by the Hyuga ability…
I cannot die so easily.
Even if you act tough,
you can’t stem the current now…
Master Sasuke ran to
the Sound Village by his own wish.
Sasuke is now in the darkness…
No…
Naruto… You’ve got better eyes than me.
There’s a person who can find him
in the darkness and save him.
Master Sasuke belongs
to Lord Orochimaru.
No matter who it may be,
they can’t save…
He can save him!
Because…Naruto…you…
You saved me from the darkness!
Talking rubbish until the end…
But…
I haven’t been pushed this far
since Kimimaro.
Damn it…
Everyone…
I'll leave the rest…
to you.
For the first time, I spoke to you
And you smiled
For the first time, I was able to speak
In my own words
Would you think it was
a bother if I approached you?
Despite my doubts,
I worked up my courage
My clumsy attempts with words
You listened without turning away
No wonder I get carried away by you
But you don’t feel anything for me, do you?
I feel so sad
But…
For the first time, I spoke to you
And you smiled
For the first time, I was able to speak
In my own words
For the first time, I spoke to you
And you smiled
For the first time, I was able to speak
In my own words
For the first time, I spoke to you
Yahoo! The enemies are quite close!
All right! We’ll catch up in a burst!
Speaking in terms of number,
we’ve got more!
If things go well,
we can get him back next!
Yeah! I don’t feel like losing
with four against two!
Four against two?
That’s twice the opponents’ number!
Say-say. Were there four of us?
Are you an idiot?!
Me, Akamaru, Shikamaru, and you!
No matter how you count,
there are four!
Next episode:
“The Vessel Arrives Too Late”