Connecting old words
that have been used up
I just want to convey
my simple thoughts
That day's faint wind blows away
at the castle ruins of yesterday
I'll laugh with you
and live for the moment
Still that incident
will continue to trouble you, right?
That's why it must be good-bye
Leaving nothing behind,
let us share what is left
In time, we'll realize
that it was everything
And sadness will touch our cheeks,
creating a river of tears
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex
and melting away
Where’s the other one?
Hey…
Who are you looking for?
I’ll take care of the rest.
Go wash your eyes in that river.
This is my ability…
specializing in assassination, of course.
You can’t beat me by just having
a good nose and nails…
You can’t beat my ability!
Akamaru… I’m sorry…
Akamaru…
We’ve always done things together.
We were together
whenever and wherever.
However this one time, I’m sunk.
My cells can swim inside
your body as I wish,
and I can even create parts
that are only you.
In other words,
a little bit of a fusion condition…
a sharing of the flesh is what it’ll be.
A sharing…?
That’s right!
And a cruel way of killing
that only I can accomplish…
the gradual scraping off
of just your cells!
I see…
If that’s the case…!
If I do this…
what’s gonna happen?
Suicide?! That’s ridiculous!
Die with me…
To Each His Own Battle
What are you thinking?!
It’s just as I thought…
We are sharing one body, right?
Damn it!
Entering my opponent’s body
to avoid any attacks…
that is my Jutsu’s greatest advantage.
There hasn’t been
a single one before now
who’s done this sort of thing.
Are you in pain?
All right then, let’s get comfortable now.
Yikes, you idiot! 					Stop it!
It’s too late!
There’s not enough blood…
Damn!
Damn…
Where’d he go?
So he left his little dog behind
and fled.
It’s the right decision,
but he’s more cold-hearted than me.
What?!
It couldn’t be!
What a relief…
He’s still breathing.
What a relief!
Akamaru… You really gave it your best.
Because of you, I was able to hold up
the enemy for a while.
We’ve caused injuries
upon the enemy too.
It’s enough… You’ve done enough.
His name is Akamaru.
Huh?
Mom… Sis…
From today, you’ll take care of him…
Okay?
I will?
I’m Kiba. Nice to meet you, Akamaru.
You!
We’ve been together forever.
Nice catch, Akamaru!
All right, you did well!
Here we go!
Be more serious about it!
Stop being such a baby!
Mom…
Listen, Kiba…
It’s not just you.
Akamaru and you,
the two of you need
to become strong together.
With Akamaru… Together?
Akamaru…
That’s right.
Way to go Akamaru! You did it!
Mid-air Dynamic Marking!
Next is mid-air triple somersault!
Take your aim!
Yahoo!
We’ll be together forever
from now on too…
I’ll protect you from now on!
That jerk!
Setting up a trap on me!
I’ll kill you!
Hey! Sakon! Where are you?! Sakon!
Sakon!
Blah blah blah.
You’re such a nuisance, Big Brother.
Your yelling stings my eyes…
Big Brother!
I’ll kill him… is what I’d like to do,
but it’s almost time for my sleep.
Capture those bastards alive in my place.
When I wake up,
I’ll kill them.
All right, Sakon?
Capture them alive…
Yeah, I got it…
But…
The killing part,
we’ll do it together.
If I carelessly attack,
he dodges
and I end up attacking myself!
Behold!
Willow Dance!
You!
Bones?
This is my…Kekkei Genkai.
What’s with this guy…?
Is he attacking with bones sticking out
from all over his body?
He’s grabbed his own bone!
It’ll be soon…
He’s turning the bone…
into a sword!
It’s futile. It’s not just ordinary bone.
The highest density bone is hard as steel.
So what?! I’ll break that bone!
I possess Five Dances.
You’d better not think
you know my strength after just this much.
What?!
I’ll specially show you…
the Camellia Dance next .
Come!
I’ll crush you!
I did it!
It’s a Substitution?!
There!
Damn!
They’re getting closer and closer.
This isn’t good, traces of blood!
Damn, I did save Akamaru
for the time being,
but maybe I went too far.
This smell…
What does it mean?
Why… Why is it that even those guys
are headed to a place like this?!
I don’t understand anymore.
In any case,
we need to leave this place quickly.
I can’t…
I’m starting to feel light-headed
from the pain and loss of blood…
My body won’t move at all either…
Akamaru…
He left just his coat…
Huh?
So he fled by floating down the river…
Damn!
Damn…
This is it!
So, I’ve cornered you, you stinking rat!
Pretty impressive…
You timed it well to scatter
the three to attack.
You must have practiced quite a bit, huh?
Since it’s a pretty complicated song…
Well now…
Not only did you
immediately understand
that I’m manipulating these guys
with my flute,
you understood how difficult this song is.
You’re a pretty impressive punk.
But you can’t completely
understand this song.
You're so right…
since art is so foreign to me.
But since she uses that flute
to manipulate,
it means that song must contain
individually specific sound patterns
to control each and every movement
of those guys.
I’m pretty confident
when it comes to just analyzing,
but this time it’s not looking good.
The reason is that
I don’t understand
musical notes whatsoever.
There’s no one that’s heard
this song and lived.
Finale, Ninth Passage,
Demon Revolution!
The melody’s changed!
For the first time, I spoke to you
And you smiled
For the first time, I was able to speak
In my own words
Would you think it was
a bother if I approached you?
Despite my doubts,
I worked up my courage
My clumsy attempts with words
You listened without turning away
No wonder I get carried away by you
But you don’t feel anything for me, do you?
I feel so sad
But…
For the first time, I spoke to you
And you smiled
For the first time, I was able to speak
In my own words
For the first time, I spoke to you
And you smiled
For the first time, I was able to speak
In my own words
For the first time, I spoke to you
Attacks and defense without gaps
using three Summoned bodies.
I hate to admit, but she may
be a pretty good Shogi player.
Plus I don’t have much Ninja tools left…
Man, it feels like I’m playing
without rooks or bishops.
Now then…shall I go?
Cry or laugh,
I can only give it my all here!
Next time,
“Fakeout: Shikamaru’s Comeback!”